Chapter 693: Abrupt Interruption

"Are you two done catching up? What'll it be then, Huo Zhuozi? Will you continue to oppose us or become our ally?" Su Liu asked.

A serious look appeared on Chi Rong's face as he said, "There's no point in getting hung up on all of those past matters. Our master sent you away from the sect all those years ago as he cherished you as a disciple, and now, it's time for you to go back with me to see him."

All of the Fire Age Fireflies began to flicker incessantly as he spoke, and Immortal Lord Hot Flame took a glance at Chi Rong, then turned back to Han Li and Fox 3 with a torn look on his face.

A hint of wariness flashed through Bi She's eyes upon seeing this, and she distanced herself from him a little.

A faint smile appeared on Su Liu's face, and he began to prepare for battle, while Han Li also tightened his grip around his sword.

The atmosphere in the palace had become very tense once again.

However, right at this moment, a commotion suddenly rang out from outside the palace, and Han Li detected a burst of powerful spatial fluctuations.

His brows furrowed slightly as he turned to the entrance of the palace, just in time to see a purple figure stumbling inside while holding a woman in his arms.

These two were none other than Shi Chuankong and Feng Lin, and an immediately elated look appeared on Fox 3's face at the sight of them as he called out, "Brother Shi!"

Han Li could sense that Shi Chuankong's aura was in a state of disarray, indicating that he had just endured a grueling battle.

Su Liu also turned his gaze to Shi Chuankong, and his brows furrowed ever so slightly.

At this point, Feng Lin had already regained consciousness, and Shi Chuankong set her down after taking a moment to steady himself.

Feng Lin was still as pale as a sheet, and she said to Shi Chuankong, "Thank you, Young Master."

Shi Chuankong nodded in response, and his gaze roamed over everyone in the palace. He then faltered slightly upon catching sight of the three treasures in the palace, but his gaze only lingered on them briefly before he looked away.

After taking a moment to catch his breath, Shi Chuankong took a glance out of the palace, then declared, "They're coming, everyone."

Han Li immediately understood what Shi Chuankong was referring to, and his expression changed ever so slightly, while a grim look also appeared on Immortal Lord Hot Flame's face.

"Are you referring to the Gray Immortals?" Su Liu asked.

Shi Chuankong nodded silently in response.

"Could it be that these two were telling the truth earlier? Have those filthy scoundrels really crossed into our realm? If that's the case, then we have to report this matter right away," Chi Rong said with tightly furrowed brows.

"How many of them are there?" Su Liu asked.

Shi Chuankong hesitated momentarily, but ultimately still replied in a truthful manner, "I encountered four Gray Immortals, all of whom are roughly at the High Zenith Stage. On top of that, they're also accompanied by an indeterminate number of other Gray Realm creatures."

"Hasn't your Reincarnation Palace always been really close with the Gray Realm? If you ask me, you were the one who brought them here, weren't you?" Chi Rong suddenly accused as he turned to Han Li and Fox 3.

A peculiar look appeared on Fox 3's face upon hearing this, and he didn't deny these accusations.

Bi She's brows were tightly furrowed, and she also remained silent.

As for Han Li, he had no idea where these Gray Immortals had come from, so he naturally couldn't form any judgments.

The lack of denial from the trio was taken as an admission of guilt, and the expressions of everyone in the palace changed ever so slightly.

"Senior Martial Brother Huo Zhuozi, regardless of what happened all those years ago, the True Mantra Sect had always opposed the invasion of the Gray Realm. Are you going to collude with these treacherous bastards? These are outside enemies who must be killed!" Chi Rong yelled as he turned to Immortal Lord Hot Flame.

A conflicted look appeared on Immortal Lord Hot Flame's face as he turned to Han Li.

"Regardless of whether you believe us or not, we truly have no idea why these Gray Realm beings are here or how they managed to get here," Fox 3 sighed.

Chi Rong was clearly unconvinced, and he scoffed, "You can take those lies to the afterlife!"

Immediately thereafter, he thrust a palm forward, and an enormous crimson wheel of fire erupted out of his hand.

The wheel was revolving incessantly with crimson flames all over its surface, and the Fire Age Fireflies before him also began to buzz loudly, looking as if they were going to swarm Fox 3 at any moment.

Right at this moment, Han Li suddenly detected something, and he yelled, "They're coming!"

Everyone hurriedly turned to the entrance of the palace upon hearing this, but there was nothing there.

Due to the strange restrictions in this space, they weren't able to release their spiritual sense very far at all, and after waiting for a moment, there were still no further developments.

Chi Rong immediately flared with rage as he roared, "Don't try to play me for a fool!"

He swept a sleeve through the air as he spoke, and the fiery crimson wheel was immediately sent hurtling directly toward Han Li.

"Idiot!" Han Li sighed in frustration as a burst of golden light emerged over his body, and he used his Reversal True Axis ability to evade the attack with ease.

Immediately thereafter, a burst of rumbling rang out in the distance, much like the sound of an approaching sandstorm, and several indistinct figures quickly arrived at the entrance of the palace within a vast cloud of gray mist.

Chi Rong stopped in his tracks as he cast his gaze toward the entrance of the palace, while Su Liu turned to Han Li with a surprised expression, seemingly taken aback by how powerful Han Li's spiritual sense was.

The four indistinct figures emerged from the gray mist before entering the palace, and they were none other than Shi Chuankong and Feng Lin's pursuers.

The four of them were led by that skeletal figure, and he paid no heed to Han Li and the others as his gaze instantly settled upon the three treasures in the palace.

In particular, the stark white flames in his eye sockets flickered slightly at the the sight of the silver lute within the array, and he hurriedly yelled in excitement, "That's the Virata Lute! Once we obtain that lute, our realm defying array will be close to complete, and we'll be able to open up a stable passageway for our army to invade this immortal region! Secure the lute right away!"

The other three Gray Immortals hurriedly heeded his call, launching themselves at the three treasures in the array.

"You're not getting your hands on anything!" Su Liu roared, but instead of trying to stop the Gray Immortals, he turned to pounce on the three treasures himself.

Everyone else immediately followed suit, and no one tried to stop the Gray Immortals for fear that the three treasures would be taken by others while they were locked in battle against the Gray Immortals.

In contrast, Han Li chose to remain still on the spot as he secretly released his time spirit domain, but suppressed it to the extreme so that it only encompassed a tiny area around his own body.

The Gray Immortals were furious to see this, and the gray-haired young man raised his purple spear, upon which a thick gray tornado erupted out of the tip of the spear before sweeping directly toward Su Liu.

At the same time, the young woman lashed out with her whip, and a loud whip crack rang out as countless gray whip projections emerged, forming a giant gray net in mid-air to encompass Shi Chuankong and the others.

As for the hideous gray-robed elderly man, he spread his arms open to reveal a pair of extremely thin gray fleshy wings, and he shot through the air at an incredible speed, flying past Fox 3 and the others in the blink of an eye as he gained rapidly on Su Liu.

In response, Su Liu spread his right hand open, and an inky black rune appeared on the center of his palm to release a flash of radiant lightning.

A loud thunderclap rang out as a vast expanse of five-colored lightning erupted forth from between his fingers, then spread out as a screen of five-colored lightning that instantly vanquished the oncoming gray tornado.

At the same time, Su Liu sped up significantly with his body enshrouded within five-colored lightning, opening up more distance between himself and the others.

A resounding boom rang out not far behind him, and Chi Rong crashed through the gray net with what appeared to be a miniature crimson sun hovering in front of him, eradicating every obstacle in his path.

The gray skeleton raised his white bone staff up high upon seeing this, then began to chant an incantation, and bursts of gray flames instantly erupted out of the staff before hurtling toward all of the True Immortal Realm cultivators present, including even Han Li, who was playing no part in the fight for the three treasures.

Instead of taking any evasive measures, Han Li lashed out with his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, and arcs of Divine Devilbane Lightning converged toward the tip of the sword before erupting forth to clash against the gray flames.

A dull thump rang out, and there was no eruption of flames or lightning. Instead, as soon as the two attacks clashed, they immediately began whittling each other down.

Fox 3 and the others were also warding off these gray flames through different means, and as a result, they were inevitably slowed down.

Su Liu was the one being targeted the most, and the five-colored lightning around him was being rapidly worn down. As a result, he was forced to slow down, and the gray-robed elderly man overtook him to lead the charge toward the three treasures.

Right as he was about to rush into the array to secure the Virata Lute, Shi Chuankong abruptly vanished from the spot without any warning.

Almost at the exact same moment, a dark rift appeared in the space beside the array, and Shi Chuankong stepped out of the rift with his complexion deathly pale and blood flowing from the corners of his eyes, then reached out to make a grab for the silver lute.

Chapter 694: Frozen

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and a sense of foreboding welled up in his heart.

In the instant that the tip of Shi Chuankong's came into contact with the silver lute, its strings abruptly shuddered slightly, seemingly having been strummed by an invisible hand.

A melodious note rang out as a burst of silver light erupted out of the lute before sweeping forth in all directions.

Shi Chuankong was the closest to the lute, so he was struck first by the silver light, and his eyes widened in surprise as he was sent flying back, only to then be suspended in mid-air in a complete still fashion.

Before anyone else had a chance to do anything, the burst of silver light swept through the entire palace, and everyone rose up involuntarily into the air like Shi Chuankong. Regardless of how they struggled, they could only flounder on the spot, unable to move forward or descend back down onto the ground.

Immediately thereafter, the golden plate at the center of the array also seemed to have been triggered by this burst of power, and it began to revolve rapidly while a burst of golden light erupted out of its center, then also spread through the surrounding area like the wave of silver light.

Everyone could only look on helplessly as the wave of golden light washed over, following which they were all immobilized in mid-air.

In that instant, it was as if time had completely stopped. Even the vast cloud of gray mist outside the palace had fallen completely still, standing on the spot like a dirty gray wall.

Everyone had dazed looks on their faces, as if even their consciousness had been frozen, and only Han Li's eyes were still trembling slightly, but he was unable to move them at all.

Even so, he was already in a much better state than everyone else. At the very least, his consciousness hadn't been frozen, so he was still able to think, albeit only very slowly.

This wasn't because there was anything special about Han Li. Instead, it was simply because his compressed time spirit domain had acted as a barrier around his body to help him somewhat withstand the detrimental effects of the waves of silver and golden light.

A strange silence descended upon the entire palace, and everyone was hovering in mid-air in a completely still fashion.

Right at this moment, the space within the palace suddenly began to tremble violently, and a black spatial rift that was several dozen feet in length suddenly appeared behind the gray-robed elderly man, releasing bursts of formidable spatial fluctuations.

At the same time, another black rift that was around three feet in length abruptly appeared beside Feng Lin's neck, and it extended further to slice a gash into her ear.

However, both of them remained completely immobilized, and it seemed that they were oblivious to what was happening around them.

Han Li knew that there was a very good chance that the spatial balance in the entire set of ruins had most likely already been broken, and that this space was going to completely collapse soon.

With that in mind, he began to channel his Mantra Treasured Axis with all his might, but under the dual time and spatial restrictions, his consciousness and immortal spiritual power were both moving extremely slowly. As a result, his Mantra Treasured Axis was also failing to respond.

Right at this moment, a burst of dull rumbling rang out within the palace, and the two spatial rifts shuddered in unison before expanding at a far quicker rate than before.

Immediately thereafter, the black rift behind Feng Lin's ear abruptly swelled to several times its original size, forming a flat black hole that decapitated her in the blink of an eye.

Her head was hovering above the black hole, while her body remained beneath it, and it was as if they were separated by a black light barrier. There was no sound, nor any blood flowing out of her body, presenting a very strange sight to behold.

On the other side, the black rift behind the gray-robed elderly man had also expanded by about twofold, and it had torn through his chest like a spear, slicing through both his heart and his ribs, but there was also no blood flowing out of the wound.

The tip of the black spatial rift had already reached the back of Shi Chuankong's chest, and if it were to elongate any further, then it would impale him as well.

A hint of urgency surfaced in Han Li's eyes upon seeing this, but all he could do was channel his immortal spiritual power and his Mantra Treasured Axis with all his might in an attempt to regain his mobility. At the moment, his body was still completely immobilized, but he was now able to move his eyes left and right, and the rate at which his consciousness was recovering had also sped up significantly.

However, right at this moment, the dreaded rumbling rang out once again, but this time, the two existing spatial rifts remained very stable, and they posed no threat to him for now.

However, as he cast his gaze down below, he was horrified to find that a black rift that was around ten feet wide and over thirty feet in length had appeared beneath him.

It was like a gaping black mouth that was eager to devour him, and Han Li continued to channel his Mantra Treasured Axis with all his might, but progress was agonizingly slow.

In the past, he had been able to forcibly free himself from certain restrictions using his Mantra Treasured Axis, but this time, things were looking dire.

He was beginning to feel extremely agitated, unsure of what to do as he had never encountered a situation like this, where his will and his body were completely out of sync.

Right at this moment, a thought occurred to Han Li, and he began to channel his Spirit Refinement Technique, but once again, he was only able to do so very slowly.

As he did this, the same dull rumbling rang out a third time, and a spatial rift appeared beside Immortal Lord Hot Flame as well.

Han Li drew upon his spiritual sense with all his might, and a slight gleam suddenly flashed through his eyes as his Spirit Refinement Technique finally began to function.

With the help of his Spirit Refinement Technique, his consciousness was restored to normal, and the rate at which he was able to channel his Mantra Axis Scripture was sped up significantly. Finally, he was able to actually sense the Mantra Treasured Axis in his body.

All of a sudden, the spatial rift beneath him lurched open while also expanding upward by several feet, sucking in a corner of his robe.

Han Li's heart shuddered upon seeing this, and finally, a burst of golden light emerged behind him, following which his Mantra Treasured Axis appeared.

As soon as the axis emerged, it immediately began to radiate countless rays of golden light, and working in tandem with his time spirit domain, they were able to create a small area of golden light to resist against the restrictive law powers within this space.

As a result, Han Li was finally able to regain some of his mobility, and he was able to lift the fingers of his sword-wielding hand ever so slightly.

However, this was still nowhere near enough to free him from his current predicament.

Right at this moment, two of the time law threads wrapped around his Mantra Treasured Axis lit up at his behest.

Initially, they were only glowing very faintly, but the light quickly began to grow brighter and brighter until it appeared like a smoldering golden flame.

The flame analogy was quite apt here as Han Li really was burning his time law threads in order to release the time law powers imbued within them.

As the two time law threads were set alight, the Time Dao Runes on the Mantra Treasured Axis began to light up one after another, glowing far brighter than they ever had as they released bursts of extremely formidable time law power fluctuations in all directions.

Han Li attempted to move his own body, only to discover that everything still felt incredibly heavy, and even the slightest movement felt downright impossible.

He looked down at the spatial rift below, which was close to reaching the underside of his feet, and he gritted his teeth as a third time law thread around his Mantra Treasured Axis was set alight at his behest.

With the release of the time law powers that it contained, the golden light radiating from the Mantra Treasured Axis grew even brighter, and it began to tear at the surrounding space like a golden saw.

A hint of elation appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he began to move to the side with immense difficulty.

The invisible barriers formed by the time and spatial law powers in the palace were torn apart bit by bit in the face of the Mantra Treasured Axis, and Han Li began to move with great difficulty, as if he were trudging through a swamp.

After finally escaping from the spatial rift down below, Han Li immediately began to make his way toward the three treasures at the center of the palace without any delay.

At this point, the rumbling in the surrounding space was becoming more and more frequent, and Han Li's brows were furrowed tightly with concern, but there was a determined look in his eyes.

He had chosen to venture deeper into the palace instead of immediately fleeing as the three immortal treasures were extremely alluring, and on top of that, he really had no choice.

He had no idea just how large an area these restrictive time and spatial law powers encompassed, so blindly fleeing the palace would be no different from suicide. Hence, it was a much better course of action to try and secure the three immortal treasures, then attempt to disable the restriction from there.

Even if these ruins were about to completely collapse, at the very least, he could try to flee through a spatial rift.

Upon arriving by Immortal Lord Hot Flame's side, Han Li hesitated momentarily, then decided to take the time to grab onto Immortal Lord Hot Flame's shoulders before moving him several feet to the side, out of the way of the black rift that was posing an imminent threat to his life.

Thanks to the influence of the Mantra Treasured Axis, Immortal Lord Hot Flame's consciousness was temporarily restored during the brief moment in which he was in close proximity to Han Li, but he was still completely unable to move or even speak.

As Han Li continued onward, his consciousness was frozen once again.

After what seemed like an eternity, Han Li finally arrived in front of the three immortal treasures.

Chapter 695 (1): Saving Shi Chuankong

In contrast with when Shi Chuankong had tried to secure the three immortal treasures, they no longer felt as if they were enshrouded in invisible energy fluctuations. Instead, all that remained between them was an extremely faint and slightly peculiar aura.

A serious look appeared on Han Li's face as he reached out toward the golden plate, which was the nearest of the three immortal treasures to him.

This time, nothing out of the ordinary happened, and he was able to easily grab onto the golden plate.

A burst of golden light flashed past, and the golden plate vanished, having been stowed away into Han Li's storage bracelet.

As soon as the golden plate vanished, the flow of time in the palace instantly resumed.

The slowly expanding spatial rifts abruptly swelled to several times their original size in unison, and two dull thumps rang out as a large geyser of blood sprayed out of Feng Lin's neck before falling like rain, while bursts of gray mist also erupted out of the gray-robed elderly man's body.

The two of them didn't even get a chance to react before they were both devoured by the expanding spatial rifts, and everyone else hurriedly flew away from the spatial rifts in alarm.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame quickly darted away from the spatial rift that was close to him, and a hint of lingering fear welled up in his heart as he recalled that brief memory snippet from before. If Han Li hadn't stopped to help him on his way to the three immortal treasures, he would've most likely already met the same fate as Feng Lin and the gray-robed elderly man.

With the restrictive forces around Han Li's body lifted, he turned his gaze to his Mantra Treasured Axis, upon which he discovered that the three time law threads had already been incinerated into nothingness.

He immediately rushed forward once again as he attempted to grab the Miro Dhvaja, but right his hand was about to come into contact with the dvaja, a burst of powerful spatial fluctuations suddenly erupted forth.

A spatial rift that was far more fearsome than the other ones in the palace appeared without any warning behind the Miro Dhvaja and the Virata Lute, devouring half of the entire palace in an instant.

The Miro Dhvaja and the Virata Lute fell into the rift one after another, plunging into the boundless darkness.

Han Li peered into the enormous, all-engulfing spatial rift, and he could only heave a forlorn internal sigh. He didn't want to see such a powerful pair of treasures go to waste, but the risk was simply too great. With that in mind, he withdrew his Mantra Treasured Axis and sent it revolving in reverse, enhancing his own speed so that he could get away as quickly as possible.

Right at this moment, he noticed out of his peripheral vision that Shi Chuankong had put on a suit of strange black and silver armor, and the light around his body warped momentarily, following which he abruptly vanished from the spot.

In the next instant, Han Li turned to look deep into the abyssal spatial rift to discover that Shi Chuankong had reappeared next to the Virata Lute, then grabbed onto the lute, following which his body began to take on an indistinct appearance again.

He's insane!

Han Li was momentarily flabbergasted, but then paid no further heed to Shi Chuankong as he turned to fly out of the palace.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame and the others were already fleeing out of the palace, but the gray-robed skeleton was doing the opposite. He was rushing deeper into the palace, and he passed Han Li by en route to Shi Chuankong.

Immediately thereafter, a burst of radiant gray light emerged from the bone staff in his hand, and it swelled rapidly to become a white bone scythe that was over a hundred feet in length, unleashing a giant scythe projection that swept through the air toward Shi Chuankong.

Shi Chuankong had only just barely made it out of the abyssal rift, and his complexion was deathly pale, while the suit of armor that he was wearing had also become completely dull and devoid of luster, as if it had been drained of all spiritual qi. In his current state, it was impossible for him to withstand or evade the oncoming attack.

A look of resolution appeared on his face as a sharp white bone abruptly protruded out of the palm of his hand, and bright red blood that was gleaming with silver light was flowing out of the bone. He brushed the bone over the Virata Lute, then strummed his fingers firmly over the lute's strings to produce an indescribable, high-pitched sound.

Meanwhile, Han Li was just about to leap out of the palace gates when he was struck by a burst of invisible soundwaves, and he was rooted to the spot as if some type of peculiar force had latched onto him.

Immediately thereafter, he felt a burst of incredibly formidable spatial fluctuations erupt forth from behind him.

By the time he turned around, he was no longer even able to see Shi Chuankong or the gray-robed skeleton. All he could see was that the chaotic space had become even more fractures, and enormous black or gray spatial rifts and vortexes had appeared everywhere, completely tearing the entire palace apart.

Han Li's heart immediately sank upon seeing this, and it was already too late for him to burn through more of his time law threads. Inside the palace was an enormous gray vortex of mist that was over a thousand feet in size, and it was rapidly expanding, devouring him like an all-engulfing mouth.

He felt as if he had fallen into a rapidly spinning whirlpool, and as the world spun around him, he felt as if his entire body were falling apart at the seams, and even his consciousness was gradually fading.

After an indeterminate period of time, Han Li felt a burst of sharp pain spear through his mind, and only then did he regain consciousness.

He pressed his palms against the ground and struggled up into a seated position, and he discovered that his palms were pressed against some type of incredibly dry and fine powder.

He fought through the throbbing pain in his body as he brought his hand closer to his eyes for an inspection, only to discover that his vision was completely blurry, and that he was unable to focus his gaze onto the palm of his own hand at all.

He shook his head in exasperation as he channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique, and only after a long while did his vision begin to clear up.

After recovering his eyesight, he was able to see that there was a layer of gray powder over his hand, and he only had to rub his fingers together gently for this powder to stick together slightly.

His brows furrowed slightly as he dusted off his own hands, then swept his gaze over his surroundings to find that this gray powder stretched as far as the eyes could see in all directions.

What is this place?

The memory of being sucked into the spatial vortex earlier sprang into his mind, and he didn't know what to make of this situation.

The sky up above was very dark and forbidding, and it seemed that there was a layer of incredibly dense dark clouds overhead. As a result, there wasn't much distance between the sky and the horizon, presenting the illusion that heaven and earth were only separated by about a thousand feet.

Deep within the dark clouds, Han Li could just barely make out three orbs of dim yellow light hanging high up in the sky, and they appeared to be a trio of suns.

The low-hanging sky, the gray and lifeless color tones, and the indescribable feeling hanging in the surrounding air all made him feel very uncomfortable, and an oppressive feeling welled up in his heart.

Han Li took a moment to collect himself, then inspected his own internal condition to discover that he had no injuries. However, his expression then darkened slightly as he discovered that his connection with heaven and earth seemed to have been severed, and that his body was no longer able to absorb the world's origin qi.

Could it be that my immortal acupoints have been sealed?

Han Li hurriedly closed his eyes to conduct a more thorough internal inspection, and moments later, he reopened his eyes with a combination of relief and concern on his face.

His immortal acupoints were completely fine, the problem arose from the environment that he was currently in.

This place had no world's origin qi at all. Instead, there were only wisps of baleful qi interspersed throughout the surrounding air. Back when he first regained consciousness, he had thought that it was the baleful qi in his own body that was causing trouble, but he now realized that it was actually the surrounding environment.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li took a yellow pill, then slowly rose to his feet.

In any case, I have to figure out what kind of place this is.

With that in mind, he activated his Infernal Devilish Eyes while also releasing his spiritual sense to scour his surroundings.

Moments later, an intrigued look appeared on his face as he cast his gaze in a certain direction.

Due to how low the sky was hanging, all he could see was a vast expanse of murky grayness there. After a brief hesitation, Han Li rose up from the ground before flying in that direction as a streak of azure light.

After flying for close to ten kilometers, Han Li stopped in mid-air, and he could see an indistinct humanoid figure in the distance, seemingly in the process of sinking into a strange, brown area.

His brows furrowed slightly as he flew in that direction, and as he got closer, the humanoid figure became clearer to him. As it turned out, it was none other than Shi Chuankong.

At this moment, he seemed to be unconscious. His aura was extremely feeble, while his spiritual sense had all but completely faded, and he was sinking into a dark brown, bubbling swamp.

Chapter 695 (2): Saving Shi Chuankong

Han Li swept his gaze over the swamp, upon which he discovered that the baleful qi within it was several times more abundant than it was in the air, and this baleful qi was invading Shi Chuankong's body in a frenzy while the swamp was dragging him under.

Thankfully, there was a purple jade spirit pendant hanging from his waist, and even without any immortal spiritual power support, it was still automatically protecting its wearer. Otherwise, Shi Chuankong's physical body would've most likely already been completely destroyed by baleful qi.

However, the purple jade pendant was ultimately nothing more than an inanimate object, and there was no way that it could protect him for long without any magic power support. At this point, the spiritual light emanating from its surface had already become extremely thin, and it didn't look as if it would be able to keep Shi Chuankong sheltered for much longer.

Once the jade pendant ran out of spiritual power, Shi Chuankong would sink into the swamp and meet his demise.

When it came to Shi Chuankong, Han Li didn't have much of a positive impression of him. In fact, he had actively tried to distance himself from Shi Chuankong up to this point, firstly as he didn't want Shi Chuankong to discover his true identity, and secondly because he felt like Shi Chuankong was harboring too many secrets.

Having said that, he felt no animosity toward Shi Chuankong.

Hence, after a brief hesitation, he decided to sweep a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of azure light that enveloped Shi Chuankong's body before attempting to drag him out of the swamp.

However, as soon as he did this, he immediately detected a burst of powerful force opposing him as it attempted to drag Shi Chuankong's body deeper into the swamp.

Han Li was rather taken aback by this, and he hurriedly peered into the swamp beneath Shi Chuankong with his Infernal Devilish Eyes.

Earlier, his spiritual sense had only told him that there were some faint spiritual power fluctuations and a high density of baleful qi here, but he hadn't noticed any demon beasts lurking in the swamp.

As soon as he peered into the swamp with his Infernal Devilish Eyes, an alarmed look instantly appeared on Han Li's face, and he shot up into the sky like lightning.

He had only just risen up into the air when the earth down below began to tremble violently, and a series of massive bubbles emerged over the brown swamp before popping in rapid succession.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li saw the ground below split up into close to a hundred areas, each of which was over a hundred feet in size. They were like the petals of a black lotus flower, and they were rising up and converging toward the center in layers.

If Han Li hadn't detected that something was amiss in advance, he would've most likely already been swallowed up by the earth by now.

However, even though he had managed to evade whatever creature was lurking beneath the swamp, Shi Chuankong was on the verge of being completely inundated by the swamp.

What the hell is that?!

Han Li's brows were tightly furrowed as he summoned an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword, then slashed it through the air to release a streak of incredibly sharp azure sword qi.

The streak of sword qi had arcs of golden lightning revolving around it as it hurtled toward the strange swamp down below, and following an explosion of golden light, a burst of rumbling rang out deep within the swamp.

Immediately thereafter, the swamp also exploded, and Han Li channeled his Reversal True Axis ability, weaving from side to side to evade the fragments of the swamp as he descended upon Shi Chuankong, then grabbed him by the collar before rushing back in retreat.

After rising over a thousand feet up into the air, Han Li suddenly felt a sharp pain in his arm. He looked down to discover that there were around a dozen thin black tentacles on Shi Chuankong's back, and hundreds of black threads that were as thin as strands of hair had split off from these tentacles, many of which had already crawled their way onto his arm.

Accompanying this painful sensation was a burst of extremely aggressive and invasive baleful qi, which was flooding into his body in a frenzy through the tiny gashes that had been inflicted onto his arm.

Han Li's brows furrowed tightly upon seeing this, and the Flame of Essence appeared on his shoulder in its humanoid form at his behest, then slid down along his arm before descending onto these thin black threads.

As soon as it came into contact with the black threads, it immediately opened its mouth to release a burst of scorching silver flames, which flowed along the black threads all the way until they reached the black tentacles on Shi Chuankong's back.

As the tentacles were set alight, they released an acrid odor, and they immediately separated themselves from Shi Chuankong's body before plunging down toward the swamp below.

"Burn it all," Han Li yelled, and the Flame of Essence instantly sprang up into the air, then spread its arms before transforming into a silver fire raven that swooped down from above.

The silver fire raven slammed violently into the ground, and silver flames instantly spread in all directions, swallowing up the entire surrounding area within a radius of several thousand feet.

Han Li remained high up in the sky as he watched the ground below tremble violently. At this point, it was already beginning to collapse bit by bit, and in the end, all that remained was a giant crater with a radius of several thousand feet.

With its job done, the silver fire raven flew back to Han Li before landing on his shoulder as it reverted back to its humanoid form. However, its little face was slightly puckered, and it didn't seem to be elated by its victory at all.

"You don't like it here, do you?" Han Li asked as he turned to the silver figure.

The miniature silver figure hurriedly nodded in response.

"I don't like it here, either. You can go back now, and we'll leave this place right away," Han Li said with a smile, and the silver figure instantly vanished from his shoulder amid a flash of silver light.

Han Li stowed his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword away, then took a glance down at Shi Chuankong, who he was still carrying by the collar. Only then did he discover that there was a black patch of skin on the back of his neck, clearly a sign of baleful qi infiltration.

His brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he sped away in a certain direction.

Han Li's Infernal Devilish Eyes remained active during the course of the entire flight, and after some time, he descended into a valley that he deemed to be relatively safe.

After landing on the ground, he flipped Shi Chuankong's body over to conduct an examination, upon which he discovered that a great deal of baleful qi had already accumulated in his body. On top of that, he seemed to have sustained some rather severe injuries back in the True Mantra Sect ruins, so there was no way that he could wake up on his own.

Perhaps he could survive in his current state, but if left untreated, even if no further baleful qi infiltrated his body, this physical body of his would undoubtedly be ruined, and that would spell the end of his cultivation journey.

So be it. I've already saved him, so I might as well finish the job. As for whether he can make a full recovery, that'll be down to him.

With that in mind, Han Li flipped a hand over to produce a longan-sized black pill that was giving off a slightly spicy aroma.

This was one of the Baleful Quelling Pills that he had previously refined.

This pill was quite difficult to refine, and it was exceptional at expelling baleful qi, but unfortunately, it couldn't address the root of Han Li's condition. Hence, it could only be used as a means to suppress baleful qi backlash, and at this point, he only had two Baleful Quelling Pills left, including this one.

After a brief hesitation, Han Li pressed the pill into Shi Chuankong's mouth, then guided the pill down Shi Chuankong's throat and into his stomach.

A pained look instantly appeared on Shi Chuankong's face, and his brows became tightly furrowed in agony as he gave a muffled groan.

A sizzling sound rang out from the wound on his back, and wisps of black baleful qi began to rise up out of it.

Han Li monitored Shi Chuankong's condition for a moment, then walked away and sat down with his legs crossed.

First, he examined the injuries on his arm, and after verifying that they were only minor injuries, he flipped a hand over to summon an Immortal Origin Stone, using which he began to replenish his own immortal spiritual power reserves.

In this place, it was impossible to replenish his immortal spiritual power by absorbing the world's origin qi, so he would just have to rely on Immortal Origin Stones for now.

......

Time slowly passed by, and before long, the sky had turned dark, and the baleful qi imbued within the surrounding gray mist also became denser and denser.

Han Li slowly opened his eyes before sweeping his gaze over the surrounding area, then flipped a hand over to produce a stack of array plates and array flags.

Before long, an array had taken shape, producing a golden hemispherical light barrier that encompassed both Han Li and Shi Chuankong within it.

Han Li took a glance at Shi Chuankong to find that he was still unconscious and was displaying no signs of waking up at all. However, the pained look on his face had eased slightly, indicating that he was feeling a little better.

There were still wisps of black smoke rising up from the wound on his back before spreading through the surrounding air, and Han Li withdrew his gaze before looking upward, upon which he discovered that the clouds up above had become even darker under the night sky, further adding to the oppressive atmosphere in this place.

Deep within the dark clouds was a string of murky, glowing orbs, and it was a collection of six moons.

Chapter 696: Tally

Han Li observed the six moons concealed deep within the dark clouds, and a thought suddenly occurred to him as he pulled out his Heaven Controlling Vial, then placed it onto the ground and waited for the moonlight to shine upon it.

However, even after waiting for a long while, the vial displayed no reaction at all.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he took a glance up at the sky, then stowed the vial away again with a wry smile.

Even though there were six moons in the sky, their light was unable to pass through the thick cloud cover, so they weren't able to activate the vial's ability to produce its usual spirit liquid.

After stringing the vial back around his own neck, Han Li briefly inspected his surroundings before raising his right hand. A glowing floral design appeared on his middle and index fingers, following which a door of silver light that was around ten feet tall emerged in front of him.

As soon as the door of silver light was opened, bright radiance spilled out of it alongside rich world's origin qi that was a faint azure color, presenting a stark contrast with the drab and gray colors of the surrounding area.

Han Li stepped into the door of light, appearing directly inside the bamboo building behind the golden lotus pond, and Mo Guang was currently standing at the stairwell leading to the second floor, seemingly waiting for him.

"Why have you suddenly contacted me, Fellow Daoist Mo Guang?" Han Li asked.

A smile immediately appeared on Mo Guang's face at the sight of Han Li's arrival, and he said, "I wanted you to come and see me as I have something to discuss with you, Fellow Daoist Han."

"You want to leave the domain and go outside, right? If that's the case, then I'm afraid I'll have to let you down. The current circumstances outside are rather complex, so it would be best for you to stay in here for now," Han Li replied.

"Fellow Daoist Han, I presume you're still unaware of where you currently are right now, is that correct?" Mo Guang asked with a sheepish smile.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and Mo Guang faltered slightly upon seeing Han Li's reaction, then continued, "It seems like you already have some idea. I can confirm to you now that we're currently in the Gray Realm."

"It sounds like you're quite familiar with the Gray Realm," Han Li remarked with an inquisitive expression.

"Not at all, Fellow Daoist Han. The Gray Realm has always been strictly off-limits in all of the immortal regions, so very little is known about the Gray Realm. I was only able to hear some stories about the Gray Realm during my time with Ma Liang," Mo Guang replied in an ambiguous fashion.

"What exactly do you want to say, Fellow Daoist Mo Guang? I don't have much time," Han Li said.

"Given your current struggles with your baleful decay, it'll be quite detrimental for you to have to deal with the prevalent baleful qi in the Gray Realm. Hence, I was thinking that I could travel through the Gray Realm in your stead to lessen your burden," Mo Guang said with a smile.

"I appreciate the thought, but at the moment, I can still handle things myself," Han Li replied with a faint smile.

Mo Guang was just about to press his case further when Han Li continued, "Rest assured, if a suitable opportunity arises, or I require your services with something, I'll be sure to call upon you. Right now, the situation outside is still rather unclear, so it would be best for you to stay in here for now. On top of that, if you have any way to return to the True Immortal Realm, then please do tell me."

It was clear that Han Li had no intention of letting him out of the Flower Branch domain, so Mo Guang could only inform Han Li that he had no way of returning to the True Immortal Realm, then took his leave and returned to the second floor.

Han Li watched as Mo Guang departed, then took a glance at the body of the Gray Immortal that he had thrown into the bamboo building earlier before making his way into a silent cultivation chamber on the first floor.

Once inside, he conjured up an aura concealment array, then sat down with his legs crossed on the bed.

At this point, Mo Guang had already sat back down on the second floor, and he stared into empty space in a contemplative manner for a moment before closing his eyes to meditate.

During this past foray into the True Mantra Sect ruins, Han Li had reaped a great deal of rewards, including the complete versions of several time-attribute cultivation arts and the storage tools of Ren Hao, Gongshu Tian, and the Gray Immortal by the name of Fang Jin.

Now that he finally had some time on his hands, this was the perfect opportunity to tally his spoils.

First, he pulled out Ren Hao's blue storage ring, and he briefly refined it before emptying out its contents.

A small pile of glittering Immortal Origin Stones appeared on the ground in front of him, and a faint smile appeared on his face as he stowed the Immortal Origin Stones into his own storage bracelet without any hesitation.

After that, he tipped out a bunch of jars and vials from the storage ring, and he examined them one by one to discover that all of them contained various pills for recovery and cultivation enhancement purposes. Among them, there was an extremely valuable vial of pills suitable for consumption for mid-High Zenith cultivators, but aside from that, all of the pills were quite ordinary.

Of course, they could only be considered ordinary for someone like Han Li, who ate pills as if they were common fruits. For the average Golden Immortal, all of these pills were extremely precious and would be worth fighting over in the outside world.

Aside from those pills, the storage ring also contained many water-attribute materials, among which were some scale-like objects that were presumably kept as spare parts to repair that suit of blue scale armor of his.

There was also a particularly eye-catching blue crystal that was around the size of a human head, and it was riddled with wavy patterns while also giving off formidable water law power fluctuations.

Aside from that, all that remained in Ren Hao's storage ring were some water-attribute treasures, the most powerful of which were that giant blue sword and the suit of dragon scale armor, but unfortunately, both had already been completely destroyed.

However, sorting through Ren Hao's storage ring hadn't been a complete waste of time. During the process, he had discovered a longan-sized crimson bead with nine different flame patterns engraved upon them, and it was none other than the Nine Destructions Flame Bead that Ren Hao had used against him in the past.

This was an extremely formidable treasure, and there was no way that Han Li would've been able to emerge from the explosion completely unscathed if it weren't for his time law powers.

Han Li carefully examined the bead for a while with an elated expression, then carefully stowed it away to be used in a future battle.

After tallying the contents of Ren Hao's storage ring, Han Li pulled out Gongshu Tian's fiery red storage bracelet.

A burst of red light flashed past, and a collection of items appeared on the ground once again.

It was a small mountain of Immortal Origin Stones that wasn't any lesser in quantity compared with the haul that he had secured from Gongshu Jiu all those years ago, and there were even around two dozen mid-grade Immortal Origin Stones among them.

Han Li was very pleased to see this. With this massive haul, his pockets were once again full.

He stowed all of the mid-grade Immortal Origin Stones away separately, then stowed away the rest of the Immortal Origin Stones before moving onto the other contents of the storage bracelet.

There were many containers in Gongshu Tian's storage bracelet as well, all of which contained High Zenith Stage pills.

At this point, Han Li was already a very accomplished pill refinement master, and he had obtained many different types of High Zenith Stage pills in the past, so he was able to identify most of these pills, while only a small portion of them were unrecognizable to him.

At the moment, High Zenith Stage pills were a bit too powerful for him to consume. He could take them if he really wanted to, but most of the medicinal effect would be wasted, and it could do more harm than good.

Having said that, this collection of pills would be sufficient to support his cultivation for some time once he reached the High Zenith Stage.

Aside from that, there were also many scriptures and jade slips in Gongshu Tian's storage bracelet, most of which contained his fire-attribute cultivation arts and secret techniques, and there were also what appeared to be a few maps of different immortal regions.

Han Li briefly examined everything to find that the main cultivation art used by Gongshu Tian had been the Great Heaven Incinerating Arts, an advanced cultivation art that could allow one to attain fire law powers. There were also many cultivation insights from Gongshu Tian enclosed with the cultivation art, making it a very precious find.

As for the secret techniques, there were too many of them to go through, they all required fire law powers for support, so Han Li only conducted a rough examination of them before setting them aside.

The remaining maps came as a bit of a surprise to Han Li. Upon closer inspection, he discovered that not only were there maps of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region and the four allied immortal regions, there were also maps of the Calm Wind Immortal Region, the Golden Origin Immortal Region, and a part of the Middle Earth Immortal Region. The maps weren't very detailed, but they certainly saved him the trouble of having to collect them.

Han Li split the maps up into different categories before stowing them away, then turned his attention to a trio of familiar items, namely a golden plate, a golden badge, and a white disk.

The golden badge was Gongshu Tian's immortal envoy badge, while the golden plate was what immortal envoys used to communicate with each other, and the white disk was what they used to detect the aura of the Spirit Refinement Technique. Now that he was in the Gray Realm, he wasn't worried about being detected by cultivators of the Heavenly Court, so he stowed the three items away instead of immediately destroying them.

Gongshu Tian's storage bracelet also contained a large number of spirit materials, one of which was a golden flower with ten petals. As the white jade box that it was housed in was opened, rays of golden light shone out from within, and they were as warm and comforting as the light of the rising sun.

If he were to plant this flower in his spirit medicine garden, it would surely be beneficial to the growth of all of the other spirit plants there.

With that in mind, Han Li gathered all of the spirit plants that he had found in the True Mantra Sect ruins in one place.

After that, he turned his gaze to a palm-sized spherical silver box. The surface of the box was riddled with intricate and complex patterns, and there was a miniature golden talisman adhered to its surface, sealing the box tightly to ensure that the aura of its contents remained completely contained.

Han Li carefully examined the golden talisman to find that it was one of a very high caliber, and that it was commonly used to seal some extremely powerful natural flames.

Hence, whatever was inside this silver box had to be quite remarkable.

Chapter 697: Devouring the Pill Sand

A contemplative look appeared on Han Li's face as he stared at the spherical silver box and the golden talisman.

A short while later, he suddenly raised a hand to cast a few incantation seals into the talisman, thereby allowing him to remove it, and the silver box sprang open with a faint crack.

In the instant that the box was opened, a wave of heat surged out from within before spreading in all directions, drastically elevating the air temperature in the entire room.

Inside the box was a trio of longan-sized beads that were crimson, orange, and purple in color.

Is this Rainbow Fire Pill Sand? Han Li wondered to himself with an uncertain expression.

According to ancient records, Rainbow Fire Pill Sand came in a total of seven colors that corresponded with the colors of the rainbow. They were extremely rare fire-attribute objects that were more powerful than any natural flame, and they were truly capable of melting mountains and evaporating seas.

On top of that, these things were naturally occurring objects, and they could emerge high up in the heavens, or in impossibly deep valleys. It was impossible to reliably track them or create them artificially, making them as rare and precious as Profound Heavenly Treasures.

The problem was that there were only three of these beads here, and they didn't appear to be special in any way aside from the intense heat that they were giving off, so Han Li was rather hesitant about identifying them.

Right as Han Li was pondering how he should proceed, a burst of silver light emerged on his shoulder, and the tiny silver figure appeared, then rushed over to the spherical silver box and began running in circles around it in an ecstatic fashion.

"You want to eat this?" Han Li asked with a surprised expression.

The silver figure turned around and nodded firmly at him while gesturing frantically. At the same time, it was darting constant glances at the three beads, as if it were afraid that they would disappear if it looked away for too long.

"I can let you have them, but the problem is that I still don't know exactly what they are yet... Let's do it this way: you can have one of them for now, and if there are no adverse effects, then you can eat the other two as well," Han Li decided.

The silver figure was absolutely overjoyed to hear this, and it gave Han Li another firm nod before hurriedly turning back to the silver box, then began walking in circles around it, seemingly unable to decide which one it wanted to eat first.

Han Li was rather amused to see this, and he made no effort to hurry the silver figure as he set the silver box onto the ground and began to examine the other objects.

If he were dealing with Jin Tong, then she would most likely devour all three of the beads at once as soon as he turned his back on her. However, the Essence Fire Raven had always been very obedient to him, so he wasn't concerned.

Gongshu Tian's giant sword and those ten fiery flags were already in Han Li's storage bracelet, and there were still seven or eight more treasures in Gongshu Tian's storage bracelet, but most of them were ungraded immortal treasures.

There was only a golden bell that appeared to be an ninth-grade immortal treasure, and it contained some time law powers.

After refining the bell, Han Li discovered that when shaken, the bell would release bursts of golden ripples capable of hindering the spiritual sense of all targets that they came into contact with. If one were at or below the early-High Zenith Stage or possessed weak spiritual sense, then they would be completely immobilized.

However, this bell was far less effective against those cultivating time law powers or were at or above the mid-High Zenith Stage, and that was presumably why Gongshu Tian never used it against Han Li.

After sorting through these treasures, Han Li turned his attention back to the Essence Fire Raven, upon which he discovered that it had one hand resting on the crimson bead and the other on the orange one, while its gaze was fixed on the purple bead, and it still hadn't made a decision.

An amused smile appeared on his face as he flipped a hand over to produce a white talisman, which was something that he had found from the top of Gongshu Tian's head.

Earlier, he had noticed that the talisman was giving off peculiar aura fluctuations that were similar to spiritual power, and after a close examination, he was ecstatic to discover that it was an eighth-grade immortal treasure that could protect one from spiritual sense attacks.

This was what Gongshu Tian had used to ward off Han Li's Spiritual Sense Cage.

However, even with Gongshu Tian's cultivation base, he wasn't able to unleash the treasure's full power as it had a rather interesting property, which was that it drew upon the spiritual sense of the user, so the most powerful the user's spiritual sense was, the more formidable the treasure would be.

Han Li picked up the white talisman before pressing it to his own glabella, and a burst of white light flashed past as the talisman vanished into his consciousness, where it transformed into a white mountain.

The runes on its surface were flashing incessantly, and at its very center was a string of golden characters that read "Imperial Peak Spirit Restriction Talisman".

After that, Han Li flipped a hand over to produce a golden plate, and as soon as it emerged, a burst of formidable time law power fluctuations immediately spread through the entire room.

Even the silver figure's attention was drawn to the time law power fluctuations, and it looked up from the three beads to see what was happening, but it then quickly turned its attention back to the three beads.

Han Li gently stroked the golden plate to discover that its surface was riddled with subtle patterns, and the golden needle protruding out of its center was still revolving on its own. With each revolution that it made, a layer of golden light would flow over its surface.

Han Li attempted to refine the object, but was surprised to discover that he was completely unable to do so.

How could this be? Is it because this is a treasure of too high a caliber, so normal refinement incantations don't work on it?

Right as Han Li was pondering this subject, a burst of powerful energy fluctuations suddenly erupted behind him, and he hurriedly turned around to find the fiery silver figure with its fists tightly clenched, throwing its head back in a silent roar to the heavens.

Radiant red light was erupting out of all of its orifices, causing the concealment array that Han Li had set up to tremble violently.

Han Li made a beckoning motion to draw the silver box on the grand into his grasp, and he discovered that only the orange and purple beads remained, so it was clear that the crimson one had already been devoured by the Essence Fire Raven.

After stowing the silver box away, he heard a resounding boom ring out as the surrounding space shuddered violently, but the commotion was contained by the concealment array.

He turned to discover that the fiery silver figure was currently laying spread-eagled on the ground, and its body was swelling rapidly in size as it reverted back to its fire raven form.

At the same time, it was as if an outer garment of crimson flames had emerged over its body, and the silver and crimson flames were intertwining with each other to give off incredible heat that even Han Li was astonished by.

A string of loud thumps rang out as the array that he had set up completely collapsed, following which the entire bamboo building began to tremble and sway violently.

Mo Guang's eyes instantly sprang open as he detected this wave of heat and violent tremors, and he immediately stood up from the ground with tightly furrowed brows, then flew straight out of the bamboo building to avoid the scorching heat.

The walls and ground in the silent cultivation chamber were being scorched by the waves of fire, and it looked as if they were on the verge of exploding from the waves of tremendous heat.

Han Li was quite startled to see this, and he hurriedly conjured up layers of azure light barriers that forcibly suppressed the waves of fiery power erupting out of the Essence Fire Raven's body.

At the same time, the bamboo forest in the entire domain began to rustle incessantly, sending countless bamboo leaves raining down from the sky.

Wisps of spiritual qi were constantly being funneled toward the bamboo building through the underground roots of the bamboo trees, and the parched bamboo walls of the building were instantly revitalized.

Simultaneously, the water in the pond in front of the bamboo building was churning violently as if it were boiling, and all of the golden lotus flowers were swaying incessantly while releasing plumes of white spirit mist that enveloped the entire bamboo building from all directions.

The entire area was quickly enshrouded in mist, making it resemble an ethereal immortal abode.

Over at the newly constructed bamboo building near the spirit medicine garden, Daoist Xie was also snapped out of its meditation, and it flew onto the top of the bamboo building to see what was happening.

Inside the bamboo building, the crimson flame around the Essence Fire Raven's body gradually receded while fusing as one with its silver flames, and the fire-attribute energy fluctuations that they were releasing were also constantly diminishing.

Han Li was quite relieved to see this, and he began setting up restrictions in the surrounding area once again.

Some time later, the silver and crimson flames around the Essence Fire Raven's body completely receded, and it had transformed into a silver ball that was riddled with crimson patterns and was hovering in mid-air.

Han Li was ecstatic to see the constantly flashing crimson patterns on the silver ball.

It seemed that he really had obtained three balls of Rainbow Fire Pill Sand.

However, given the Essence Fire Raven's current state, it most likely wasn't going to be able to wake up anytime soon.

He communicated briefly with Mo Guang through voice transmission, then departed from the bamboo building to make his way over to the spirit medicine garden.

"What just happened, Fellow Daoist Han?" Daoist Xie asked while standing outside its bamboo building.

"The Essence Fire Raven devoured a ball of Rainbow Fire Pill Sand," Han Li replied in a truthful fashion.

"I see. No wonder there was such a massive commotion," Daoist Xie mused.

"Brother Xie, here are some storage tools that I don't have the time to sort through, so I'll have to trouble you to examine their contents for me. Aside from items that contain time law powers, you can take anything that catches your fancy without having to consult me," Han Li said with a smile.

"Alright, leave it to me," Daoist Xie replied with a nod.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air, and a large pile of storage bracelets and storage rings appeared in front of Daoist Xie.

Daoist Xie very rarely expressed any emotion, but even it couldn't help but display a look of surprise at the sight of all of the storage tools.

Han Li was rather amused to see this, and he bade farewell to Daoist Xie, then made a trip to the spirit medicine garden, where he planted all of the spirit plants that he had acquired.

After that, he picked out a good spot to plant the ruined remnants of the Twin Birth Tree, then watered it with some spirit liquid that he had prepared earlier.

He knew that the chances of reviving the tree like this were extremely slim, but he didn't have access to the Heaven Controlling Vial's spirit liquid for now, so this would have to suffice.

Seeing as he was currently in the Gray Realm, Han Li didn't dare to stay in the Flower Branch domain for too long for fear of something happening in the outside world, so he quickly emerged from the domain.

Chapter 698: Agreement

Seven days and seven nights flew by in a flash.

Han Li remained in the valley this entire time, and he noticed that in this area, the dark clouds in the sky were perpetually present regardless of whether it was daytime or nighttime.

There were three suns in the sky during the day and six moons at night, and the moons were perpetually full, never going through any type of lunar cycle.

With the ever-present dark clouds in the sky, Han Li wasn't able to produce any spirit liquid with his Heaven Controlling Vial.

At times, bursts of rumbling would ring out deep within the dark clouds at night, striking him with the impression that there could be certain powerful beasts lurking in the clouds, but nothing ever arose from that.

One morning, a layer of dense mist rose up from the ground, causing the surrounding baleful qi to become even denser.

While meditating, Han Li suddenly heard a faint cough, and he opened his eyes to discover that Shi Chuankong had regained consciousness.

He struggled into a seated position, then took a glance at Han Li before examining his own storage tools in a slow and methodical manner, following which a puzzled look appeared on his face as he asked, "Why?"

"Why did I save you, or why didn't I kill you?" Han Li asked in an expressionless manner.

Shi Chuankong massaged his own glabella as the memories leading up to his loss of consciousness gradually returned to him, and he said, "I was attacked by some type of demon beast as soon as I got here. Were you the one who saved me?"

"I don't think it was a demon beast. At the very least, it wasn't a demon beast in the sense that we're used to. Instead, it was a creature unique to this place," Han Li replied.

"What is this place?" Shi Chuankong asked as he inspected his surroundings.

"If I'm not mistaken, we were sucked into the Gray Realm through a spatial vortex in the True Mantra Sect ruins," Han Li replied.

Han Li had speculated that this was the Gray Realm upon his arrival, but he wasn't able to confirm that this was indeed the case. However, in light of the observations that he had made here and everything that he had learned about the Gray Realm in the past, he felt sufficiently confident in passing judgment on the matter.

"The Gray Realm?!" Shi Chuankong exclaimed in an incredulous fashion, then hurriedly began taking a closer look at his surroundings, following which a contemplative look appeared on his face.

"I didn't think that I would come to the Gray Realm under such strange circumstances," Shi Chuankong mused with a wry smile after a long silence.

"Earlier, your body was infiltrated by the baleful qi here, and I fed you a Baleful Quelling Pill to clear out some of it, but it looks like there's still some left. Now that you're awake, I'm sure you have a way to take care of it yourself," Han Li said.

"Why were you willing to feed me a Baleful Quelling Pill? Surely it would've been more beneficial for you to allow that thing to kill me or even kill me yourself so you can take my treasures," Shi Chuankong asked.

"If I'm not mistaken, you're no ordinary devilish being. Instead, you have very close ties with the Vast Origin House, right?" Han Li asked.

"You saved me because of my status? I don't think you're that type of person, Fellow Daoist Li," Shi Chuankong scoffed in an unconvinced manner.

"Regardless of what you think, you owe me your life now. Once we return to the True Immortal Realm, I need you to draw upon as much resources as you can from the Vast Origin House to help me find a person. That shouldn't be too difficult for you, right?" Han Li asked.

Shi Chuankong could tell from the look in Han Li's eyes that he seemed to be telling the truth, and he didn't know what to make of this situation.

"That's the only reason you saved me?" he asked in a skeptical fashion.

"There's no point in discussing this matter now, I'll give you more details once we return to the True Immortal Realm. At its core, the Vast Origin House is a business organization, so I'm sure it takes its reputation very seriously right?" Han Li asked.

Shi Chuankong was finally convinced upon hearing this, and he nodded in response. "I can help you find whoever you're looking for, and I can even do everything in my power to help you once at some later date should you ever encounter any trouble."

"What are your conditions?" Han Li asked.

"No conditions. My life isn't worth so little that I have to attach further conditions to my compensation," Shi Chuankong replied with a smile.

"Alright, in that case, we'll stay here for a few more days so you can rest and recuperate, but we'll have to leave after that. We have to figure out where we are right now, then find a way to return to the True Immortal Realm," Han Li said, then closed his eyes to resume his meditation.

Shi Chuankong took a long glance at Han Li, finding him to be a complete enigma. He then shook his head and took a pill before sitting down with his legs crossed to meditate.

Several days later, the two of them set off in a certain direction atop Han Li's green jade flying carriage, departing from the valley.

Even after flying for a few days, the surroundings were still as drab and gray as ever, and the terrain remained largely unchanged as well.

Han Li was standing at the front of the carriage, watching the monotonous scenery flash past.

Despite how drab the color tone here was, it wasn't actually completely barren. There was a great deal of vegetation on the ground, and Han Li had even spotted some insects and small beasts.

Somehow, these living creatures were completely unaffected by the great abundance of baleful qi in the environment, and it seemed that they were sustained by the baleful qi, just as living beings of the True Immortal Realm were sustained by the world's origin qi.

"Looks like this really is the Gray Realm. We may be in some trouble," Shi Chuankong mused as his brows furrowed slightly with concern.

"Why do you say that, Fellow Daoist Shi?" Han Li asked.

"I've never been to the Gray Realm, but I've heard that there are many powers in this realm that harbor a great deal of enmity toward cultivators of the True Immortal Realm and the Devil Realm like ourselves, so we'll be in a great deal of trouble if anyone finds out who we are," Shi Chuankong replied in a grim voice.

"I've heard about that as well. In that case, it would be a good idea to put up some disguises," Han Li mused as he made a hand seal, and a burst of black light surged out of his body to envelop the entire flying carriage.

Countless strands of black light then shot out at Han Li's behest before wrapping themselves around the flying carriage, and they were also releasing steady streams of black runes that were also surging into the carriage.

The green coloration of the carriage quickly turned black, as did the green light that it was emanating, and it was also giving off bursts of baleful qi fluctuations.

"I didn't know that you were such a skilled tool refinement master as well, Fellow Daoist Li. This carriage looks nothing like it did just a moment ago," Shi Chuankong praised.

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist Shi. Cosmetically altering the carriage is quite simple, but it'll be much more difficult to alter our auras," Han Li replied.

At the moment, his body was filled with baleful qi, and he also had Mo Guang with him, so it would be very easy for him to pass as a Gray Immortal. The problem was whether Shi Chuankong would be able to do the same.

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Li, I can handle that myself," Shi Chuankong assured with a faint smile.

Han Li nodded in response, then focused on piloting the flying carriage.

Meanwhile, Shi Chuankong flipped a hand over to produce a small white bead, then cast an incantation seal onto it.

The bead immediately began to release bursts of white light, and a rapidly revolving white vortex appeared within it.

All of the baleful qi in the nearby air instantly converged toward the bead, and the white vortex within it quickly turned gray, as did the light that it was giving off.

A hint of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this, and he took a glance at the bead before quickly looking away again.

After flying onward for close to half a day, the terrain down below finally began to change. The ground became flatter and more level, and countless dark gray wheat-like plants appeared down below, making the area resemble a grassland.

The gray plants in the grassland swayed in the wind like rippling waves, presenting a majestic sight to behold.

After flying onward for a while longer, Han Li suddenly raised an eyebrow as he brought the flying carriage to an abrupt halt before turning his gaze to a certain direction.

Shi Chuankong turned to the same direction, and there, he spotted a long procession slowly advancing forward close to a thousand kilometers away. At the forefront of the procession was a convoy of around a dozen large carriages that were drawn by giant rhinoceros-like beasts.

The convoy of carriages was accompanied by three thousand to four thousand tall and imposing humanoid figures.

These figures had humanoid lower bodies, but the heads of lizards, and their skin was also covered in gray scales.

At the very rear end of the procession was a herd of gray deer-like creatures with translucent, coral-like antlers growing on their heads. There were over ten thousand of them, and they were slowly being ushered along.

This procession appeared to be a traveling tribe of farmers migrating across the grassland.

These humanoid lizard creatures were clearly intelligent life forms, and their auras were also quite powerful. In fact, one of them was at the Grand Ascension Stage, and Han Li and Shi Chuankong exchanged an elated glance with each other at the sight of these creatures.

Finally, they had someone to enquire about their current whereabouts.

Han Li immediately stowed his flying carriage away, following which a vast expanse of gray mist surged out of his body. In the blink of an eye, his aura had changed drastically, and his entire body was releasing dense baleful qi, while his eyes had also turned a gray color.

In an instant, Han Li's aura had changed into one that was virtually identical to those of the Gray Immortals that had appeared in the True Mantra Sect ruins, and Shi Chuankong was astonished to see this.

For his part, he swallowed the bead that he had summoned earlier, and bursts of gray qi surged out of his body as well, while his eyes also took on a gray color.

Shi Chuankong's transformation wasn't as perfect as Han Li's, but it was quite convincing, nonetheless.

After completing their transformations, the two of them were just about to approach the process of humanoid lizard beings when a resounding boom suddenly rang out from up ahead.

"Looks like we're in luck!" Han Li said with a faint smile, then shot forth through the air, vanishing in a flash.

Shi Chuankong's eyes also lit up slightly as he flew along close behind Han Li as a streak of gray light.

At this moment, the procession of humanoid lizard beings had been thrown into a state of panic, and the reason for this was a flock of seven strange gray birds that were flying toward them from deeper within the grassland.

These birds were each over a hundred feet in length, and they resembled giant featherless bats with draconic heads. The sharp fangs in their mouths were giving off a cold gleam, and they had sets of sharp black claws that were several feet in length, resembling a series of lethal black swords.

The gray birds were squawking excitedly as they swooped down toward the herd of deer at the rear end of the procession with their claws extended.

Chapter 699: Tribe

"Get back!"

A cold roar rang out from one of the carriages at the front of the procession, and a humanoid lizard being shot out from within.

He was far more imposing in stature than his brethren, and he had a round head with facial features that very closely resembled those of a human. The only difference was that his face was covered in gray scales, and he was giving off a tremendous Grand Ascension Stage aura.

With a sweep of his hand, a burst of radiant gray light was released, and it contained a gray bone sword that hurtled directly toward one of the oncoming gray birds.

The bird immediately attempted to take evasive measures in a startled fashion, but it wasn't able to completely get out of the way, and a long gash was sliced into its lower abdomen as it let loose an agonized squawk.

Three more figures flew out of the other carriages, and all of them were giving off Body Integration Stage auras as they lashed out at the other gray birds with various bone treasures of their own.

The gray birds let loose fierce squawks as they opened their beaks to release flurries of blades of gray wind toward the humanoid lizard beings. At the same time, their black claws began to glow radiantly as they reached out to grab at the bone treasures.

A ferocious battle immediately ensued, and the procession of humanoid lizard beings were plunged into a state of complete chaos.

The gray deer began to flee in all directions in a blind panic, while the humanoid lizard beings hurriedly chased after them before herding them away from the battlefield.

Before long, the humanoid lizard beings had been forced onto the back foot.

They were outnumbered by the gray birds, most of which were at the Body Integration Stage, and the Grand Ascension Stage humanoid lizard being was the most powerful figure on the battlefield, but a the moment, he was completely preoccupied with dealing with three of the gray birds at once.

The other three humanoid lizard beings were clearly struggling to contend against the remaining four gray birds, and if it weren't for a gray bone shield that was blocking most of the attacks from the gray birds, the three of them would've already sustained injuries.

Even so, the situation was rapidly worsening, and the three humanoid lizard beings clearly weren't going to be able to last much longer.

"We're in trouble, Chief!" the humanoid lizard being wielding the gray bone shield yelled in an urgent voice after withstanding another claw swipe from one of the gray birds.

Their chief had already noticed the perilous situation that his three brethren were in, and he was desperate to do something, but he was being completely nullified by the three gray birds.

All of a sudden, an agonized howl rang out as one of the humanoid lizard beings was struck by a burst of claw projections in a momentary lapse in concentration. Several long gashes were instantly torn into his body, and one of his arms was almost completely amputated, only just barely hanging onto his body by some small shreds of skin and flesh.

At the same time, he was sent flying by the attack, and their triangular formation was instantly shattered.

One of the gray birds squawked with excitement as it set off after the wounded humanoid lizard being, and an alarmed and furious look appeared in the chief's eyes as he opened his mouth to release a burst of gray light into his gray bone sword.

The gray sword instantly swiveled around before transforming into a massive ball of gray light that was churning and flashing incessantly.

Formidable sword qi fluctuations were surging out of the ball of gray light, causing the nearby space to ripple violently.

Two of the three gray birds hurriedly flew back in retreat upon seeing this, while a cold gleam flashed through the eyes of the final bird, and it spread its wings before swooping down upon the chief of the humanoid lizard beings.

At the same time, it opened its beak to send a plume of black light raining down upon the chief, who hurriedly made a hand seal in response, upon which the ball of gray light abruptly exploded at his behest.

Countless thin, gray streaks of swordlight erupted forth in all directions, instantly encompassing the entire surrounding area in a radius of several thousand feet.

A shrill cry rang out before immediately trailing off, and the body of the gray bird came tumbling out of the sky.

Its entire body was riddled with countless sword holes, and its aura had completely faded.

However, a series of small black holes had also been punched into the left side of the chief's body, sending him stumbling back in an unsteady fashion, and wisps of black qi were spreading toward the rest of his body from those holes.

Before he had a chance to tend to his own injuries, the other two gray birds came swooping down upon him once again.

The chief hurriedly attempted to channel the baleful energy in his body upon seeing this, but the left half of his body was completely numb, thereby severely hampering his ability to draw upon his baleful energy, and a panicked look appeared in his eyes.

The two gray birds arrived before him in the blink of an eye, then lashed out with their black claws.

All of the humanoid lizard beings were horrified to see this. If their chief were to perish here, then the entire tribe would surely follow shortly thereafter.

Right at this moment, a streak of gray light descended from the heavens, piercing through the two gray birds with ease.

Immediately thereafter, countless thin threads of gray light erupted forth, tearing the two birds into shreds before they even had a chance to cry out.

Almost at the exact same moment, a black flying sword appeared out of thin air above the other three humanoid lizard beings, and it released streaks of black sword qi that enveloped the other four gray birds in the blink of an eye before also tearing them to shreds.

The four humanoid lizard beings were completely dumbstruck by what they saw.

Right at this moment, Han Li and Shi Chuankong appeared without any warning before slowly descending out of the sky.

The chief's expression changed drastically at the sight of them, and he hurriedly flew over to Han Li's duo before extending a respectful bow.

"Thank you for saving our Gray Lizard Tribe, esteemed immortals."

The other three Gray Lizard beings also flew over to extend grateful bows while gazing upon Han Li and Shi Chuankong with awe and veneration in their eyes.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong exchanged a glance with one another, following which the former said, "It's fine, we just so happened to be passing through."

The Gray Lizard beings extended another collective bow, then backed away to await further instructions.

Han Li was rather perplexed to see this, and after taking a moment to consider his words, he said, "The two of us were traveling through the area, and we got lost in a storm. What is this place?"

They had indeed run into quite a large gray storm not too long ago, and even with their combined powers, it had taken them some effort to escape from the storm.

"This is the northwestern region of the Six Moon Grassland, esteemed immortals. The storm that you encountered was most likely a gray tide that's unique to the local area," the chief of the Gray Lizard Tribe informed in a respectful fashion.

"I see," Han Li murmured.

The chief could see that Han Li's duo was looking a little disheveled, so he said in a careful manner, "You must be weary from your travels, esteemed immortals. If you don't mind, how about coming to our tribe to have a short rest? Our tribe isn't very large, but the White Antler Tea that we produce is quite unique."

Han Li was eager to interact more with the Gray Lizard Tribe in order to learn more about the Gray Realm, so he naturally wasn't going to turn down the invitation.

The chief of the Gray Lizard Tribe was ecstatic that Han Li had taken him upon on his offer, and he hurriedly began to lead the way.

As soon as the trio descended out of the sky, all of the Gray Lizard beings on the ground below immediately knelt down and kowtowed to them.

Han Li was rather perplexed to see this.

While it was true that his cultivation base was far above theirs, these Gray Lizard beings were still acting far too respectfully. It was almost as if they were a group of beggars that were meeting the emperor.

Despite his befuddlement, Han Li didn't ask any questions.

The herd of gray deer at the back of the procession were still fleeing in panic, and they were yet to be reined in, so the process was still looking quite disorderly.

"Get those things in check! We're making a fool out of ourselves in front of these esteemed immortals! Also, pass down my orders to everyone, we're going to set up camp here today," the chief said with a stern expression.

One of the Body Integration Stage Gray Lizard beings hurriedly flew away to carry out the instructions, while the chief led Han Li's duo to the carriage at the very front of the procession.

"Please take a seat inside, esteemed immortals."

The carriage was over a thousand feet in length and around two hundred to three hundred feet wide, roughly equivalent in size to a small plaza, and there were around a dozen large tents set up on it.

A series of gray runes had been engraved onto the edges and the underside of the carriage, forming an array that was constantly releasing plumes of gray clouds to lift the carriage up from the ground.

As Han Li descended onto the carriage, he felt as if he had landed on a cloud, and it immediately became clear to him why a single rhinoceros-like beast was sufficient to draw such an enormous carriage.

The chief led the two of them to the largest tent on the carriage, and Han Li made his way inside without any hesitation.

Shi Chuankong was trailing along behind Han Li, and he knew that his aura alteration wasn't perfect, so he wanted to attract as little attention as possible. Hence, he was more than happy to follow Han Li's lead.

The interior space of the tent was quite large, and it was split up into two sections, one of which was a guest hall of sorts. At the center of the guest hall was a long table, on either side of which was a soft beasthide cushion.

The other section of the tent seemed to be the resting quarters, and the two sections were divided by a thick curtain.

Han Li didn't know what material the tent was made from, but as soon as he entered it, all of the outside sounds instantly faded.

"Please take a seat, esteemed immortals."

The chief gestured for Han Li's duo to sit down at the table, while he stood respectfully off to the side.

Right at this moment, a servant entered the tent, carrying three deer antler cups that were filled with white tea, which were giving off wisps of white mist and a faint fragrance.

"This White Antler Tea is made from the antlers of our Gray Lizard Tribe's Coral Antler Deer, combined with deer milk and over ten other ingredients. It has a cultivation enhancement effect, but of course, that won't apply to esteemed immortals of your lofty cultivation bases. Having said that, the tea is still quite delectable, so please give it a taste," the chief said with a fawning smile.

Han Li picked up the cup before taking a sip, then nodded as he said, "This a fine tea."

In reality, he didn't swallow the mouthful of tea. Instead, he funneled it straight into his Flower Branch domain as a safety precaution.

The chief was ecstatic to see this, and he immediately ordered the servant to bring Han Li's duo some more delicacies of the Gray Lizard Tribe.

Chapter 700: Acting Skills

"Thank you for the kind hospitality, Chief, but we didn't come here to taste the delicacies of your Gray Lizard Tribe," Han Li said after briefly sampling the food laid out before him.

"Of course. If you have any instructions, feel free to state them, esteemed immortal," the chief hurriedly said.

"Do you have any maps of this place and information regarding the Six Moon Grassland?" Han Li asked in a direct and straightforward fashion.

"We do. Please wait for a moment, esteemed immortals, I'll get someone to organize what we have and bring it to you right away," the chief replied as he rose to his feet.

"There's no need to organize anything, just bring all of the scriptures that you have on the geography and customs and traditions of this place, and we'll look through them ourselves," Han Li said with a wave of his hand.

The chief faltered slightly upon hearing this, but then immediately gave an affirmative response before leaving the tent.

In contrast with Han Li's calm and collected demeanor, even though Shi Chuankong had been sampling fruits and tea this entire time, there was a hint of concern in his eyes, clearly indicating that he was rather worried about his own disguise.

Before long, the chief returned with two other Gray Lizard beings, both of which were carrying thick stacks of books that totaled in excess of a hundred at a rough visual estimate.

Han Li was quite pleased to see this. With all this material, they wouldn't be completely in the dark here in the Gray Realm.

He had already come into contact with the language of the Gray Realm from items in Dragon 4's storage pouch. The language used here was a type of ancient language of the True Immortal Realm, so he wasn't worried about not being able to understand it.

"These are all of the scriptures that we have on the local geography and customs and traditions. Our Gray Lizard Tribe is but a small tribe in the Black Teeth Region, so I'm afraid we don't have much information to offer," the chief said in an uneasy manner.

"It's fine, we'll make do with what you have. We're only passing through the area and are interested in learning about the Six Moon Grassland," Han Li replied.

The chief heaved a faint sigh of relief upon hearing this, then gestured for the two Gray Lizard beings to set down the scriptures.

"Take all the time you need, esteemed immortals. I've stationed some people outside your tent, so if you have any instructions, feel free to call upon them anytime," the chief said, then promptly departed with the other two Gray Lizard beings.

Following his departure, Han Li immediately swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of gray light, which formed a gray light barrier around the entire tent.

The concern in Shi Chuankong's eyes eased slightly upon seeing this, and the two of them began to read through the provided scriptures.

They had been presented with a lot of material, but with their cultivation bases and memorization abilities, they were quickly able to read through everything and get a good grasp on where they currently were.

This was indeed the Gray Realm, but just like the True Immortal Realm, the Gray Realm was a vast place, and it wasn't made clear in any of the scriptures exactly where in the Gray Realm they were right now.

The Gray Lizard Tribe was only a small tribe that had always been settled in the Six Moon Grassland. Hence, most of the scriptures only contained information regarding the grassland, and for the vast majority of normal Gray Lizard beings, the Six Moon Grassland was their entire world.

The Six Moon Grassland was a massive place that was abundant with underground baleful veins. Not only was it rich in all types of vegetation, it also produced many types of ore and materials, and there were many other tribes residing here as well.

The Six Moon Grassland was situated in the northwestern part of the Black Teeth Region.

There wasn't much information in the scriptures regarding the Black Teeth Region. All that was stated was that it was an extraordinarily vast place, and that the Six Moon Grassland was only a tiny place in the region.

That was all of the information that Han Li's duo had managed to gather in terms of geography. As for customs and traditions, the Gray Realm was a little similar to the primordial land in that all of the living beings here resided in tribes, which ruled over different territories. The Six Moon Grassland was ruled over by a monarch by the name of San Miao, but there wasn't any detailed information on this person in any of the scriptures.

Above the monarchs was the regional ruler, and there was even less information in the scriptures about the Black Teeth Regional Monarch.

At this moment, Han Li was looking at a scripture that he was holding with a contemplative expression.

There was no concrete information on the Black Teeth Domain Ruler, but judging from the praise that was being heaped onto them in the scripture, Han Li could deduce that they had to be at least at the Great Encompassment Stage.

"The Gray Realm must be quite powerful if it's able to oppose the True Immortal Realm. With that in mind, it's a blessing that we're in a secluded place like the Six Moon Grassland. If we were in a more busy place, our covers could easily be blown," Shi Chuankong said in a slightly concerned manner.

"In that case, let's stay with this Gray Lizard Tribe for now. We won't have to worry about being exposed, and we can take this opportunity to learn more about the Gray Realm," Han Li said.

"I suppose that's our best course of action," Shi Chuankong replied with a nod.

After a brief discussion, Han Li withdrew the surrounding restrictions, then called out for one of the Gray Lizard beings outside the tent.

A tall Gray Lizard being strode into the tent, then immediately fell to his knees as he asked in a trembling voice that was filled with awe and veneration, "What can I do for you, esteemed immortals?"

There was a very clear hierarchy system in the Gray Realm.

The Gray Lizard Tribe was a low-ranking tribe, and the more prestigious a tribe was, the closer they were to human in form. This was why the Gray Lizard beings had been so respectful to Han Li and Shi Chuankong from the very beginning.

"I have something to discuss with your chief. Get him to come and see me," Han Li ordered as he put on a haughty facade.

"Yes, esteemed immortal," the Gray Lizard being hurriedly replied before departing, and the chief of the tribe arrived shortly thereafter.

"What are your instructions, esteemed immortals?" the chief asked as he maintained a respectful bow.

"There's no need to be so formal, Chief. Come to think of it, I haven't even asked for your name yet," Han Li said, and despite the humble content of his words, his demeanor was a lot colder than before.

Earlier, he had been a little too approachable, which was unbefitting of his status, so he had to make subtle changes.

The chief's heart jolted slightly at the sight of Han Li's calm demeanor, and he bowed even lower as he replied, "My name is Xi Yan, esteemed immortal."

"I see. I called you here as I wanted to ask if your Gray Lizard Tribe is traveling to the Tamda Festival," Han Li declared.

Once every a hundred years, all of the tribes across the Six Moon Grassland would gather at Wave Edge Lake on the border of the grassland for the Tamda Festival.

In the language of the Gray Realm, Tamda meant "bountiful harvest".

The festival was held by Monarch San Miao, and some sparring matches took place during every edition of the festival.

Of course, these sparring matches weren't held for no purpose. Almost all of the tribes on the Six Moon Grassland lived off agriculture or mining, and in order to avoid conflicts, the outcomes of these sparring matches were used to decide the territories of the tribes for the coming century.

Hence, this was an extremely important occasion, and all of the tribes took these sparring matches very seriously.

During the festival, an exchange convention would also take place, where all of the tribe traded everything that they had saved up over the past century for things that they needed.

The Six Moon Grassland was quite vast, and all of the tribes were very spread out. Hence, trade was very difficult to facilitate between tribes under normal circumstances. As a result, it became a tradition to gather at the festival to trade off their wares.

For these two reasons, the Tamda Festival was the most important event in the Six Moon Grassland, and there were very detailed records of the occasion in the scriptures.

"Yes," Chief Xi Yan replied with a nod.

"My senior martial brother and I aren't from the Black Teeth Region, but we've heard of the Tamda Festival. We're planning to accompany your Gray Lizard Tribe to Wave Edge Lake to see the festival for ourselves," Han Li said.

Chief Xi Yan fell silent upon hearing this.

"Is there something wrong?" Han Li asked as a cold look appeared in his eyes.

"Not at all. In fact, this is a great honor for our Gray Lizard Tribe. The only problem is that our tribe will be traveling very slowly by your standards, and I'm worried that you'll grow bored during the trip," Chief Xi Yan hurriedly explained.

He was very glad that Han Li's duo was willing to accompany his Gray Lizard Tribe. They were clearly both very powerful, but Xi Yan could tell that they weren't cruel or bloodthirsty individuals.

On top of that, with their accompaniment, not only would the Gray Lizard Tribe no longer have to fear gray beast attacks for the rest of their journey, perhaps they could even borrow their power during the Tamda Festival.

"At this current rate, how long will it take for you to arrive at Wave Edge Lake?" Han Li asked.

"It's going to take four to five years, and there are some places that we'll have to go around as there are powerful gray beasts lurking there," Xi Yan replied.

"There's no need for that. Just go straight through those areas, and we'll take care of any gray beasts that show up," Han Li ordered.

Xi Yan was ecstatic to hear this, and he replied, "In that case, we should be able to get there about a year earlier."

"Alright, that's all, you can go now," Han Li said with a dismissive wave of his hand, and Chief Xi Yan immediately turned to depart.

"By the way, does your tribe have any other types of books and scriptures? Bring them all to us so we have a way to kill time over the trip," Han Li suddenly said.

Xi Yan faltered slightly upon hearing this, then gave an affirmative response before hurriedly exiting the tent.

As soon as Xi Yan departed, the haughty look on Han Li's face instantly vanished.

Shi Chuankong was rather amused by the changes in Han Li's demeanor, and he jibed, "I must say, I'm very impressed with your acting skills, Fellow Daoist Li."

"Once you've experienced enough in life and endured enough hardships, these skills will naturally come to you," Han Li replied in an indifferent voice.

"Looks like you have a lot of stories to tell, Fellow Daoist Li," Shi Chuankong remarked, then put on a serious expression as he continued, "This Tamda Festival will be a good opportunity for us to see more of the Gray Realm."

Chapter 701: Provocation

"Indeed. Hopefully, this will be a fruitful trip," Han Li said as he looked into the distance.

Chief Xi Yan quickly returned with a group of Gray Lizard beings, carrying close to a thousand scriptures and some jade slips, but those were far rarer than the books.

It seemed like there weren't many avid readers in the Gray Lizard Tribe, and their books weren't very well-preserved, with many of them covered in dust and in a state of disrepair.

Chief Xi Yan apologized profusely for this, but Han Li and Shi Chuankong didn't really care, and they promptly dismissed him.

These scriptures varied drastically on their subject matter, which was perfect as the two of them were looking to learn as much about the Gray Realm as possible.

The next day, the Gray Lizard Tribe continued onward, but altered its planned itinerary in accordance with Han Li's instructions.

Han Li's duo remained in the tent, maintaining an air of regal mystique while also reading through the scriptures that had been provided.

The two of them were like sponges that were rapidly absorbing information on the Gray Realm.

Over three years flew by in the blink of an eye, and the Gray Lizard Tribe finally arrived at its destination, Wave Edge Lake.

Wave Edge Lake was situated in the central region of the Six Moon Grassland, and it was tens of thousands of kilometers in size. Its name was derived from a type of special crystal produced in the lake, known as Wave Edge Rocks.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong were standing in their tent, looking out at the massive lake up ahead.

The water in the lake was extremely clear, and there were only a few white birds flying over its surface, which was rippling slightly from the light breeze.

Han Li took a deep breath. The color tone of Wave Edge Lake was a little monotonous, but it was still quite a scenic location, much like some of the large lakes that one would find in the Immortal Realm, and the moist air blowing in from the lake was very cool and refreshing.

At this moment, there was already a massive gathering on a giant plot of flat land to the south of the lake. Even though there was still some time until the commencement of the Tamda Festival, most of the tribes had already arrived.

All of a sudden, a white cloud suddenly appeared in front of the Gray Lizard Tribe.

Standing atop the cloud were several white-robed figures, all of whom had human bodies, but bird avian heads with gleaming eyes.

Their white robes were made from a high-end material and were embroidered with all types of shimmering designs, completely outmatching the attire of the Gray Lizard Tribe.

The group was led by a tall young man who was giving off a True Immortal Stage aura.

The man's face was devoid of feathers, and his facial features were very close to those of a normal human, except his nose was still a little long, and his eyes were slightly sunken, giving him a cold and haughty appearance.

"Are you the Gray Lizard Tribe?" the tall young man asked in a high and mighty fashion.

Xi Yan hurriedly rushed over to the white cloud, then extended a respectful bow toward the tall young man as he said, "Xi Yan of the Gray Lizard Tribe pays his respects to the esteemed Envoy Miao."

"Who is that, Xi Feng?" Han Li asked.

Xi Feng was one of the Gray Lizard Tribe's Body Integration Stage elders, and he had been ordered by Xi Yan to explain the festival's affairs to Han Li and Shi Chuankong.

"That man's name is Miao Kui, and he's one of the enforcers under Monarch San Miao," Xi Feng replied in a respectful manner.

"I see," Han Li mused in an indifferent voice.

......

"Your Gray Lizard Tribe sure arrived nice and early. There are only two months left until the Tamda Festival, and most of the good spots have already been taken by the other tribes," Miao Kui remarked in an indifferent voice.

"What? Only two months left? Shouldn't there be at least over a year left until the festival is scheduled to begin?" Xi Yan exclaimed.

In order to avoid disrupting the order of the festival, all of the tribe's settlement spots and trade areas had already been assigned in advance.

The settlement locations didn't really matter, but the location of a tribe's trade area had a strong impact on their business.

"Our monarch decided to hold the festival early this time. Does our monarch need to consult you before making such decisions?" Miao Kui sneered.

"No, no, of course not," Xi Yan hurriedly replied in an apologetic fashion. "My sincerest apologies for speaking out of turn, esteemed Envoy Miao. Here is a small offering from our Gray Lizard Tribe, please assign us a good spot."

He approached Miao Kui as he spoke, then stuffed a small black pouch into his hand.

Miao Kui inspected the contents of the pouch briefly with his spiritual sense, and only then did his expression ease slightly.

"All of the good spots have already been taken, but you can have Area twenty-two," Miao Kui said as he tossed a white jade badge to Xi Yan.

Xi Yan immediately caught the badge before cupping his fist in a respectful salute, and Miao Kui departed atop his white cloud.

Xi Yan heaved a faint sigh as he watched Miao Kui depart, then led the Gray Lizard Tribe to their assigned position.

Their spot wasn't too far back, but it definitely wasn't a good one, either. There were many tribes already spread out in front of them, and their spot wasn't very prominent at all.

Inside the tent, Han Li and Shi Chuankong were observing the surrounding tribes, all of which varied drastically in appearance, and it was quite an eye-opening sight to behold.

At this point, around twenty to thirty tribes had already arrived.

Furthermore, all of the nearby tribes were quite large, severely outnumbering the Gray Lizard Tribe, and most of them had True Immortals among their ranks.

In contrast, the Gray Lizard Tribe was made to look quite feeble.

Han Li naturally didn't really care about this, and he turned to another massive clearing beside the lake.

That area had also been split up into different sections, every single one of which was filled with stalls that were laden with all types of different wares.

Countless people were moving through that area, presenting a lively and bustling sight to behold.

Han Li's eyes lit up slightly upon seeing this, and Shi Chuankong also turned in that direction.

All of a sudden, the Gray Lizard Tribe's procession was stopped in its tracks by another group.

A hideous middle-aged man emerged from the opposing group as he jeered, "Well, well, well, if it isn't Chief Xi Yan. Your Gray Lizard Tribe hasn't grown at all over the past century! You used to be such a powerful tribe, but you've really fallen from grace. What a pity."

The man had a long and sunken face, but his nose was very flat and wide, presenting a very unbalanced sight to behold.

Despite his hideous appearance, he was at the early-True Immortal Stage, making him far more powerful than anyone from the Gray Lizard Tribe.

"What does it matter to you, Yun Zhao? Get out of our way!" Xi Yan said in a cold voice.

"Of course it matters to me! Back in the day, our tribes were rivals. Now that your Gray Lizard Tribe has fallen so far, it truly saddens me," Yun Zhao said with a mocking sneer, displaying no intention to move.

A furious look appeared on Xi Yan's face upon hearing this.

The attention of all of the nearby tribes was drawn to the commotion, but not only did no one intervene, everyone was looking on with schadenfreude on their faces.

"Who's that, Xi Feng?" Han Li asked inside the tent.

"That man is Chief Yun Zhao of the Shadow Snake Tribe. Our two tribes got into a conflict over a mine some years ago, and we've been enemies ever since. He's an extremely petty man who picks on us every Tamda Festival," Xi Feng replied with a dark expression.

"How did your Gray Lizard Tribe ever stand up to them?" Han Li asked with an intrigued expression.

An embarrassed look appeared on Xi Feng's face as he explained, "Chief Xi Yan was once also a True Immortal, and our Gray Lizard Tribe had two Grand Ascension Stage elders as well. However, we were attacked by an extremely formidable True Immortal gray beast several hundred years ago.

“Both of our Grand Ascension Stage elders perished in that battle, and our chief also sustained severe injuries. We managed to save his life, but he reverted back to the Grand Ascension Stage from his injuries. Otherwise, there's no way our tribe would be in such a state of ineptitude."

"I see," Han Li replied with a nod.

Meanwhile, Yun Zhao was still standing firmly in front of the Gray Lizard Tribe procession, displaying no intention to move.

"I'm not here to bicker with you today, Yun Zhao. The Tamda Festival is overseen by Monarch San Miao. By standing here and blocking our way, you're going directly against Monarch San Miao's arrangements!" Xi Yan declared.

Yun Zhao's expression stiffened slightly upon hearing mention of Monarch San Miao, but he then chuckled, "Don't be so quick to pile on the accusations, Chief Xi Yan. I'm just catching up with an old friend here, so why don't we have a nice little chat? Could it be that you're afraid of me?"

Many of the spectating tribes burst into laughter upon hearing this, while a look of fury and indignation appeared on Xi Yan's face, an expression that was mirrored by all of the other Gray Lizard beings.

Han Li's expression also darkened slightly upon seeing this.

Inside the tent, Xi Yan was so furious that he was trembling uncontrollably, and he suddenly turned to Han Li before extending a deep bow as he implored, "Esteemed immortal, the Shadow Snake Tribe has gone too far! Please..."

Han Li took a glance at Xi Feng, then made his way back into the tent.

Xi Feng's face complexion instantly turned deathly pale upon seeing this. If Han Li didn't stand up for them, then the Gray Lizard Tribe was going to suffer extreme humiliation here.

"Hurry up, Xi Yan, I don't have time to waste waiting for you to bicker with these fools," Han Li said as he sat down in the tent.

His voice wasn't very loud, but it reverberated throughout the surrounding area like rumbling thunder, instantly drawing everyone's attention to the tent.

Some of the people gathered nearby immediately put away their mocking expressions upon hearing this, while Yun Zhao's brows also furrowed slightly.

Xi Yan was ecstatic to hear Han Li's scolding voice, and he turned to the tent and extended a deep bow as he replied, "Yes, esteemed immortal!"

He then turned back to Yun Zhao, and his demeanor completely changed as he said in a cold voice, "Get out of the way, Yun Zhao. I have no time to waste with you here."

"So you're suddenly acting all tough now just because you have someone to back you up. Who exactly have you got in that tent? Why don't you get them to come out so everyone here can take a look?" Yun Zhao sneered as he turned to the tent.

Chapter 702: A Quick Lesson

Not long after Yun Zhao's voice trailed off, a cold voice rang out from within the tent.

"If you don't want to die, then get out of the way."

The voice wasn't very loud, and it was completely devoid of emotion. The nearby commotion instantly died down, and everyone began looking back and forth hesitantly between the tent and Yun Zhao.

Yun Zhao was staring intently at the tent in a completely expressionless manner, and it was unclear what he was thinking.

The atmosphere had suddenly become quite tense.

"You can talk all you want, but why hide in that tent? If you truly have the power to back up your words, then why not show yourself?" Yun Zhao sneered after a brief silence.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a streak of gray light flew out of the tent like lightning, appearing in front of Yun Zhao in an instant before piercing directly toward him.

Yun Zhao's expression changed drastically as he let loose a loud roar, and a layer of black flames emerged over his body.

Within the black flames were countless twisted human faces that were howling in agony, but right at this moment, the streak of gray light split up into nine identical streaks of swordlight before converging toward Yun Zhao from all directions.

The black flames stood no chance in the face of the streaks of swordlight, and before Yun Zhao had a chance to do anything, the nine streaks of swordlight had already pierced through his body.

He let loose a blood-curdling howl as nine large holes appeared over his body, and he toppled to the ground like a broken doll.

The nine streaks of swordlight vanished in a flash, as if they had never even appeared at all.

Everyone had fallen deathly silent, and all of the spectators were looking on with dumbstruck expressions.

In their eyes, the early-True Immortal Stage Yun Zhao was an extremely powerful figure, yet he had been struck down in the blink of an eye without being able to put up any resistance, and they didn't even dare to imagine just how powerful the figure inside the tent was.

Before long, everyone returned to their senses before turning their attention back to the Gray Lizard beings, but all of the mockery had faded from their eyes.

The Gray Lizard beings were also momentarily dumbstruck before reacting with elation, and they felt an immense sense of catharsis at the sight of Yun Zhao's terrible injuries.

"Hurry up, Xi Yan! Stop wasting time!"

The same cold voice rang out from within the tent once again, and Xi Yan hurriedly gave an affirmative response before waving a hand through the air.

The faces of all of the Gray Lizard beings were flushed with excitement, and they continued onward with renewed vigor.

The Shadow Snake beings up head hurriedly parted down the middle, and a pair of Grand Ascension Stage elders picked up Yun Zhao before moving him away.

Some True Immortal Stage beings from other nearby tribes also turned to that tent with awe and veneration on their faces.

The attack just now had come with extraordinary speed and power, and none of them were of the opinion that they could've withstood it.

"Who did that?!"

Right at this moment, a furious roar erupted like thunder in the air, and several figures appeared amid a flash of white light. They were the group of enforcers under Monarch San Miao, and Miao Kui was the one who had just spoken, but at this moment, there was a white-robed young woman beside him.

The woman was wearing a five-colored phoenix crown, and her facial features were virtually identical to those of a human. Even among humans, she would've been quite the beauty, but her features were very cold and expressionless, making her appear rather unapproachable.

Xi Yan's expression instantly changed drastically at the sight of Miao Kui's group.

In order to maintain order in the Tamda Festival, private battles were strictly prohibited.

Having said that, all of the tribes on the Six Moon Grassland were quite competitive and hot-blooded, so conflicts still regularly took place. However, as long as no grievous injuries were inflicted, the people under Monarch San Miao generally turned a blind eye, but it was clear that this situation had escalated too far.

Xi Yan hurriedly approached the group as he said, "Esteemed Envoy Miao, I can explain..."

"Xi Yan, your Gray Lizard Tribe has only just arrived, yet you're already causing trouble! Do you wish to be banished from the Tamda Festival?" Miao Kui interjected coldly.

Xi Yan hurriedly lowered his head as he said, "My sincerest apologies..."

"Hand over the culprit!" Miao Kui harrumphed coldly as he turned his gaze to the tent that Han Li was in.

A hesitant look appeared on Xi Yan's face. This was the situation that he had feared the most.

A furious look appeared on Miao Kui's face, and he was just about to exert more pressure upon Xi Yan when Han Li's voice rang out from within the tent.

"I'm the culprit. If you want me, then come and get me."

The white-robed young woman turned to the tent that Han Li was in with her brows slightly furrowed, while Miao Kui immediately began to make his way toward the tent.

The white-robed young woman raised a hand to stop him as she said, "It's fine, there's no need to kick up a big fuss. Take Chief Yun Zhao to have his injuries treated, I'll take care of things here."

Her voice was as pleasant as the song of an oriole, and it struck the listener with a sense of calm serenity.

The tense atmosphere melted away with her words, and even though Miao Kui was clearly reluctant to stand down, he ultimately conceded, seemingly quite fearful of the white-robed young woman.

He descended onto the ground, then picked up Yun Zhao before flying away.

"My name is Miao Xiu. May I ask yours? It would be an honor for me to make your acquaintance," the white-robed young woman said as she clasped her fist in a salute toward the tent.

After a brief silence, a cold voice rang out in response from within the tent.

"There's no need for us to be acquainted. I'm only passing through and decided to attend this festival on a whim, and I'll be leaving soon."

Everyone nearby was quite surprised to hear this, and the entire place was soon buzzing with discussion.

On the Six Moon Grassland, Monarch San Miao's authority was absolute, so it was downright unthinkable to them that someone would dare to turn down such an invitation.

Miao Xiu's expression remained unchanged as she said, "If you don't wish to show yourself, then I won't force the matter. However, the Tamda Festival is a very important occasion for our Six Moon Grassland, so please exercise some restraint. The patience of our monarch is limited, so do not test it."

Following Miao Xiu's departure, all of the bystanders in the area also departed, but it was clear that they were looking at the Gray Lizard Tribe through new eyes.

An immense wave of relief washed over Xi Yan as he led the Gray Lizard Tribe onward.

Inside the tent, Han Li was also feeling quite relieved.

Given his and Shi Chuankong's power, they didn't have to fear Monarch San Miao. In fact, if they wanted to escape, then no one would be able to stop them, but it was best to avoid conflict as they had an objective for coming here.

The Gray Lizard Tribe soon arrived at their designated spot and began setting up camp.

Shortly thereafter, Xi Yan arrived in Han Li's tent and extended a deep bow with an excited look on his face.

"Thank you for saving our tribe from humiliation, esteemed immortal. We'll never forget what you've done for us. If you need anything from us in the future, we'll be forever at your service."

Xi Feng was also barely able to contain his own excitement.

"There's no need for such formalities," Han Li said with a wave of his hand, and Xi Yan expressed his gratitude once again before standing up straight.

The Gray Lizard Tribe had been forced to endure much humiliation over the past few centuries, and morale had been significantly boosted in the wake of this small victory.

Yun Zhao was a coward who only bullied the weak, so after sustaining such severe injuries, he definitely wouldn't dare to pick on the Gray Lizard Tribe in the future.

"Is there something that you wanted to do at the Tamda Festival, esteemed immortals? If so, I would be honored to help," Xi Yan said.

"We're just here to take a look, so there's no need for your services. You can both go now," Han Li said with a dismissive wave of his hand, and Xi Yan and Xi Feng promptly departed.

As soon as they left, Han Li immediately put on a black cloak and a conical bamboo hat to conceal his entire body, while Shi Chuankong also put on some more covert clothing.

The main objective for them was to gather information on the Gray Realm through this Tamda Festival, and their human appearances were bound to create quite a stir, so it was best to conceal themselves.

There were going to be many other people in disguises in the trading area, so they weren't going to stand out there.

After exchanging a glance with each other, the two of them vanished into the ground as a pair of black shadows, then reappeared near the trading area an instant later.

They weren't able to see much from afar, but from up close, they could see that the trading area was enormous. It had a radius of several dozen kilometers, and it was split up into different sections that were separated by small paths.

Most of the wares being sold on the stalls consisted of things like ore, gray beast materials, and spirit plants, and there were countless people filing through the trading area, searching for things that they needed.

"This really is quite the grand occasion," Han Li remarked with a smile, and Shi Chuankong was also inspecting his surroundings with a hint of excitement in his eyes.

"This place is really big, so let's split up and gather information independently. That should be a bit more efficient," Han Li said through voice transmission.

Shi Chuankong gave an affirmative response before departing, while Han Li wandered off in another direction, and he quickly stopped in front of a stall belonging to a large tribe.

All of the wares being sold on the stall were of a very high quality, and standing behind the stall were three brawny men with tiger heads, each of which was over twenty feet tall, and they were giving off Grand Ascension Stage auras.

On the way here, Han Li had read the Gray Lizard Tribe's scriptures closely, and he was able to identify many of the tribes on the grassland based on their characteristics.

These three were most likely from the Yin Tiger Tribe, which was one of the most powerful tribes on the Six Moon Grassland, far higher on the pecking order than the Gray Lizard Tribe.

Chapter 703: Price Difference

"Have any of our wares caught your eye?" a Yin Tiger being with a scar on his face asked.

"I'm not here to buy anything. Do you do acquisitions here?" Han Li asked.

The three men exchanged a slightly surprised glance upon hearing this, and the scar-faced Yin Tiger being replied, "If you have something good to offer, then we'll naturally be open to acquiring it."

Han Li flipped a hand over to summon a palm-sized black jade box before handing it over.

The scar-faced man accepted the jade box before opening it a sliver, and his expression instantly changed slightly as he hurriedly closed the box again.

He then made a respectful inviting gesture to Han Li, indicating to a black room behind the stall as he said, "Please come with me."

On the way here, Han Li had noticed that almost every single stall here had such a black room behind it, and these rooms were used for private deals.

The furnishings in the room were extremely simple, consisting of only a table and two chairs, and there was some type of restriction inscribed onto the walls.

The two of them sat down across from each other, and only then did the scar-faced man take a deep breath before opening the jade box again. Inside the box was a fist-sized dark gray crystal that was riddled with countless tiny holes, looking much like a honeycomb.

Wisps of gray mist were flowing out of all parts of the crystal, giving it a rather mysterious appearance.

"This is a Nightmare Honeycomb Crystal of an extremely high quality. How many gray crystals do you want for it? Alternatively, you can trade it for other items as well," the scar-faced man said with an excited expression.

"Looks like coming to your Yin Tiger Tribe was a wise decision. In that case, let's not waste any time. I want three hundred gray crystals," Han Li said.

"Three hundred is a little expensive. I'll take it for 160," the scar-faced man bartered.

"270," Han Li countered.

"180 is the most that I'm willing to offer," the scar-faced man said in a firm voice.

After some bartering, the price was ultimately decided at two hundred gray crystals.

The scar-faced man flipped a hand over to produce a bone storage bracelet before handing it to Han Li, who accepted the bracelet before inspecting its contents with his spiritual sense.

Inside the bracelet was a small pile of gray crystals with visible wisps of gray qi flowing within them.

These gray crystals were used as a form of universal currency in the Gray Realm, and they were similar to Immortal Origin Stones, but they contained baleful origin power.

The Nightmare Honeycomb Crystal was something that Han Li had found in Dragon 4's storage pouch.

He was going to require some funds if he wanted to gather information, so it was definitely wise to have some gray crystals on hand, and he was quite elated by this outcome.

The Nightmare Honeycomb Crystal was one of the least remarkable materials in Dragon 4's storage pouch, so two hundred gray crystals was already a very good price.

In light of that, it seemed like Dragon 4's storage pouch was far more valuable than he anticipated.

"Do you have any more Nightmare Honeycomb Crystals or any other precious materials, Fellow Daoist? Don't bother going to other tribes, just sell them all to our Yin Tiger Tribe. Don't worry about the price, our tribe has always had an immaculate reputation, and you won't be disappointed trading with us," the scar-faced man said with a hopeful expression.

"I'm afraid not. This Nightmare Honeycomb Crystal was something that I only stumbled upon by chance," Han Li replied with a shake of his head, much to the scar-faced man's disappointment.

"I don't have anything to sell now, but I want to buy some things from your Yin Tiger Tribe," Han Li continued with a smile.

"Oh? What would you like to buy?" the scar-faced man asked.

"I want to buy some scriptures," Han Li replied.

"What type of scriptures?" the scar-faced man asked as a hint of apprehension appeared in his eyes.

"Rest assured, I don't want any of your tribe's cultivation arts or secret techniques. Instead, I want your scriptures on the local culture and geography. Ideally, I want scriptures that contain information about places outside the Six Moon Grassland or even outside the Black Teeth Region. The Yin Tiger Tribe is one of the most powerful tribes on the Six Moon Grassland, so I'm sure you have many such scriptures, right?" Han Li asked.

On the way here, he hadn't spotted even a single book on the stalls that he had passed by.

Then again, everyone was here to exchange resources, and no one would focus their attention on collecting scriptures.

"I see," the scar-faced man replied as his expression eased slightly. "We can sell those scriptures to you, but they weren't easy to come by for our tribe, so they won't be cheap."

"As long as they contain valuable information, I'll take as much as you have," Han Li replied.

"Alright, please wait here for a moment," the scar-faced man said before departing.

Close to an hour later, Han Li left the Yin Tiger Tribe's stall with a faint smile on his face.

He had obtained many scriptures from the Yin Tiger Tribe, and after briefly skimming through them, he discovered that many of them contained information about places outside the Six Moon Grassland and the Black Teeth Region.

Han Li continued onward without pause, and close to an entire day passed by in the blink of an eye.

At this point, it had already gotten quite dark, and giant cages had been hung up in each of the trading areas, within which were numerous fluorescent white insects that illuminated the entire area with their radiance.

As it grew deeper into the night, the trading area only became more lively and bustling.

Han Li wandered past one stall after another, and he was in a good mood.

After leaving the Yin Tiger Tribe, he had sold some materials to two other tribes and purchased some more books pertaining to the Gray Realm.

All three of the tribes that he had chosen were large tribes, and they had far more scriptures to offer than the Gray Lizard Tribe.

For now, he had decided that he wasn't going to purchase any more scriptures.

He had already gathered a lot, and information was quite isolated in the Six Moon Grassland, so there was a lot of overlapping content between the scriptures of all tribes.

On top of that, purchasing scriptures was very strange during the Tamda Festival, and doing so excessively could attract unwanted attention.

With that in mind, Han Li began to inspect the wares on the stalls that he was passing by.

Having read all of the Gray Lizard Tribe's scriptures on the way here, he had developed some ability to appraise items of the Gray Realm, and with his immense spiritual sense, he was quickly able to discover many precious items.

All of a sudden, he drew to a halt in front of a stall, and a hint of excitement appeared in his eyes.

The stall wasn't very large, and most of the wares on it consisted of things like spirit plants, ore, and materials. The two men standing behind the stall each had a pair of horns on their heads and fish scales on their faces, indicating that they were some type of humanoid fish tribe.

"Has something caught your fancy, my friend?" one of them asked in an enthusiastic fashion.

Han Li turned his gaze to a box on one corner of the stall, within which were dozens of semi-transparent plants with translucent leaves, within which the veins were clearly visible.

These were none other than Bitter Ornament Herbs, the main ingredient for refining Baleful Quelling Pill.

This was an extremely precious ingredient in the Immortal Realm, yet it was being casually displayed here in such a large quantity.

"How much for these spirit plants?" Han Li asked.

"Oh, you want Ice Crystal Herbs? It'll be three gray crystals per plant," the humanoid fish being replied in a casual manner, suddenly losing his enthusiasm.

Han Li was rendered speechless upon hearing this.

In the Immortal Realm, Bitter Ornament Herbs were premium spirit plants that were extremely expensive, yet they were dirt cheap in the Gray Realm.

All of a sudden, he recalled that he had read about Ice Crystal Herbs in the Gray Lizard Tribe's scriptures.

After some recollection, his hazy memory of the information quickly became clear.

It was said that his herb grew in dark and cold places, and deep within the Six Moon Grassland was a bottomless swamp that was filled with these things.

However, Ice Crystals Herbs were useless to beings of the Gray Realm, and there was only a brief description of the plant in that scripture with no accompanying illustration. Otherwise, Han Li would've been able to identify it right away.

Bitter Ornament Herbs were able to expel baleful qi, which made them harmful to living beings of the Gray Realm, so it was no wonder that they were so cheap.

"Is this all you have?" Han Li asked.

The two humanoid fish beings were both rather surprised to hear this.

Ice Crystal Herbs were only used when refining certain poisons, and they weren't rare at all. Anyone could easily gather a bunch at the swamp, so it was very surprising that there was someone who wished to purchase them in bulk.

"There aren't many uses for this plant, so this is all that we picked. My apologies," the other, slightly older humanoid fish being replied.

"I see. In that case, I'll take everything that you have here," Han Li said.

Having already obtained a map of the Six Moon Grassland from the Gray Lizard Tribe, he knew where the swamp that was home to the Bitter Ornament Herbs was situated, so he could go and harvest a batch at any time.

For now, these ones would be more than enough to satisfy his pill refinement needs.

The two humanoid fish beings eagerly packed up all of the Bitter Ornament Herbs before handing them to Han Li, and the transaction was quickly completed.

"My friend, if you need any other spirit plants, make sure to come to us. Our Yearn Fish Tribe excels at collecting all types of spirit plants. Take a look at this Lake Orchid, it's over ten thousand years old, and this Wither Tuber Herb was freshly picked, so it hasn't lost any of its medicinal effects," the elderly humanoid fish being eagerly introduced.

Han Li had seen descriptions of both of these plants in the Gray Lizard Tribe's scriptures, and they both contained immense baleful qi, making them quite precious in the Gray Realm.

However, they were useless to him, so he naturally wasn't going to purchase them.

Hence, he shook his head before departing with a contemplative look in his eyes.

Given the differences in resources in the Gray Realm and the True Immortal Realm, things that were worthless in the Gray Realm could be extremely precious in the True Immortal Realm.

Now that he was in the Gray Realm, he might as well take the opportunity to gather some things like these Bitter Ornament Herbs so that he could sell them for a profit upon his return to the True Immortal Realm.

He wasn't lacking in Immortal Origin Stones at the moment, but it certainly couldn't hurt to have more. There was no telling when he would suddenly require a huge sum of Immortal Origin Stones someday, so it was best to have a large stash in advance.

The problem was that the same item often had different names in the two realms, so illustrations weren't always reliable, so he would just have to try his luck.

Thinking back to the precious yin-attribute spirit plants and ore in the Immortal Realm, he began to release his spiritual sense to carefully scour through the nearby stalls.

Chapter 704: Unprecedented Honor

Here in the Gray Realm, Han Li made sure to be extremely cautious in everything that he did for fear of attracting attention, so he hadn't spread his spiritual sense very far up to this point.

However, following the Shadow Snake Tribe incident, he had developed a grasp on the power levels of the tribes on the Six Moon Grassland, and he knew that he could avoid detection as long as no unforeseen circumstances arose.

As he walked along, he inspected all of the wares laid out on the stalls that he passed by, and he quickly found a type of ore that also existed in the Immortal Realm.

However, this ore was also quite expensive in the Gray Realm, so there wasn't much resale value.

Right as he was about to continue his search, he suddenly raised an eyebrow as he cast his gaze forward, where he spotted two tall and imposing cloaked figures walking toward him.

Both of them were wearing some type of mask that could keep out spiritual sense, and even though their auras were being concealed, Han Li was immediately able to see through the concealment thanks to his tremendous spiritual sense, and he could tell that both of them were Golden Immortals.

A pair of Golden Immortals posed no threat to the current Han Li, but Golden Immortals were quite rare in this setting, so they had to have at least been tribal chiefs.

The two figures seemed to have noticed Han Li's gaze, and they immediately lowered their heads and quickened their pace, vanishing into the crowd shortly thereafter.

Their sneaky demeanor only aroused more suspicion in Han Li, but he had no intention of investigating any further, and he continued onward.

In the end, he wasn't able to find much aside from the Bitter Ornament Herbs.

There were many things with price disparities between the two realms, but none as large as the price disparity for Bitter Ornament Herbs, so there wasn't much profit to be made unless such items were resold in bulk.

Han Li wasn't very surprised by this. After all, the two realms differed drastically, and it naturally wasn't going to be easy to find things that could be found in both realms and varied drastically in price.

Instead of continuing his search, he returned to the Gray Lizard Tribe's designated area, where he discovered that Shi Chuankong still wasn't back yet.

He returned to the tent, then summoned all of the scriptures that he had purchased earlier before reading through them one by one.

His top priority at the moment was to find a way to return to the True Immortal Realm.

Close to half a day passed by in the blink of an eye.

All of a sudden, Shi Chuankong emerged from the ground under the tent, and there was a faint smile on his face.

"You look like you're in a good mood, Fellow Daoist Shi. Have you found a way back to the Immortal Realm?" Han Li asked.

"I saw that there were many cheap materials here that could be sold for large profits in the True Immortal Realm, so I got caught up purchasing materials and forgot about finding ways to return to the True Immortal Realm. My apologies," Shi Chuankong replied in a slightly awkward manner.

"It's fine, we still have time. If we can't find a way back in this Six Moon Grassland, then we can try our luck elsewhere. By the way, I didn't think that you would be so interested in the business of buying and selling," Han Li said with a faint smile.

"It's not every day that I get to come to a new realm, and if I can make use of this opportunity, then I could make an absolute killing! As one's cultivation base improves, the amount of resources they'll need to support their cultivation will increase exponentially.

“There are many powerful immortals who end up stuck at a certain cultivation base for countless years, not because of any bottlenecks, but simply due to lack of resources," Shi Chuankong said with an excited look in his eyes.

"If a pathway can be established between the two realms, then that would indeed be an incredible business opportunity. However, all of that can only come into fruition if we can find a way to return to the True Immortal Realm," Han Li replied with a nod.

"You're right, Fellow Daoist Li. Our top priority is still to find a way back. Only then can we think about what's to follow," Shi Chuankong agreed.

......

Over a month later.

It was nearing nighttime, and the three suns hadn't completely set yet, but the six moons had already risen.

Light was rippling over the surface of the nearby Wave Edge Lake, and dozens of huge bonfires had already been set up along the bank of the lake, filled with large quantities of flammable materials.

All of the tribes that had come to attend the Tamda Festival had temporarily set aside all of their other affairs, and they were gathered around the bonfires.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong had also accompanied the Gray Lizard Tribe to the lake.

Chief Xi Yan was walking along at the very front, having changed into a clean light gray robe that draped over his broad frame. There was also a round Gray Lizard Tribe pendant hanging in front of his chest, and he was holding a torch that was lit with a white flame.

As for Han Li and Shi Chuankong, both were wearing gray cloaks, and they were trailing along behind Xi Yan with their faces concealed within their hoods.

Up to this point, they hadn't been able to find any useful information on how to get back to the Immortal Realm, so they had taken their time to continue learning more about the culture of this place while also hoping that useful discoveries could be made once the festival commenced.

Upon arriving at a bonfire, Xi Yan turned to Han Li's duo with a look of veneration and gratitude in his eyes as he said, "During past editions of the Tamda Festival, our Gray Lizard Tribe was never granted the right to light one of these bonfires. It's only thanks to your presence that we've been given this privilege. If you were willing to show yourselves, I'm certain you would be granted front-row seats to the Saya Festival."

"It's fine. We're not from your Black Teeth Region, so it would be best for us to keep a low profile," Han Li replied.

If he weren't mistaken, the young woman by the name of Miao Xiu was most likely the one who had arranged this.

Han Li cast his gaze toward a giant black stone platform that was situated a little further away from the lake. The area surrounding the platform was brightly lit, and there were all types of Gray Realm beings dressed in different attire gathered around it.

Just like Tamda, Saya was another word from the dialect of the Black Teeth Region, and it roughly translated to "fight between courageous warriors". As the name suggested, the Saya Festival was the occasion where the sparring matches between tribes took place.

As a wandering tribe with no set territory, the Gray Lizard Tribe naturally had no right to participate in the event.

Some time later, the three suns in the sky completely set, and the sound of a horn rang out from the black stone platform.

Chief Xi Yan immediately threw up his torch into the bonfire, igniting all of the flammable materials to create a huge white flame that was crackling and popping incessantly.

All of the dozens of bonfires were lit in rapid succession, releasing flurries of white sparks into the sky, resembling a swarm of fireflies. Due to the pervasive dark clouds in the sky, Han Li had never seen any stars in the Gray Realm, but all of a sudden, he felt as if he were witnessing a starry night sky again.

Right as Han Li was looking up at the sky with a slightly dazed expression, the collective voices of the tribes gathered began to ring out around him. They were all speaking slightly different Black Teeth Region dialects, and it seemed that they were singing some type of ancient war song.

After the singing subsided, a chorus of loud cheers rang out from the bonfires, and all of the tribes began to gather around the black stone platform.

Han Li's duo arrived at the stone platform with the Gray Lizard Tribe, and they looked up to find that there was a large tent set up to the north of the platform.

The tent was opened to reveal three elders of the San Miao Tribe sitting inside, alongside the chiefs of several of the Black Teeth Region's most prominent tribes.

Sitting at the very center of the tent was none other than Miao Xiu.

Her gaze roamed over the people gathered around the platform, and it lingered momentarily on the Gray Lizard Tribe before moving on again.

"Are you still looking for the powerful cultivator concealed within the Gray Lizard Tribe, Young Mistress?" Miao Kui asked in a low voice.

Miao Xiu shook her head in response.

"What an arrogant fellow he is! To think that he refused to show himself even after you visited him in person. Once the festival comes to an end, I'll be sure to capture him and bring him to you to apologize," Miao Kui said in a disgruntled voice.

"Don't talk about him like that, Cousin. He must have his reasons for not wanting to see me. As long as he doesn't harbor any sinister intentions, we should leave him alone and respect his decision," Miao Xiu said with slightly furrowed brows.

Despite this, internally, she was also a little irked by Han Li's refusal to meet her. At the same time, she couldn't help but wonder exactly what this mysterious powerful figure was like.

"You're right, Young Mistress, please forgive me," Miao Kui hurriedly apologized.

"It's about time. You can announce the commencement of the Saya Festival now," Miao Xiu instructed.

Miao Kui gave an affirmative response, then departed from the tent.

Upon arriving at the platform, he strode over to a black war drum and beat it thrice. The commotion below the platform gradually subsided, and only then did he declare, "I hereby declare the commencement of the Saya Festival. Which tribe would like to set their warriors up first to be challenged?"

As soon as his voice trailed off, two inky-black figures landed on the platform one after another.

"I am Wu Heli of the Bone Spike Tribe."

The first figure was a humanoid creature with their entire body covered in black scales, and there was a white bone spike protruding out of their face, elbows, and knees, presenting a fearsome sight to behold.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a chorus of loud cheers instantly rang out from below the stone platform, particularly from the Bone Spike Tribe, as if getting to step on the platform first was a huge honor for them.

"I am Mu Ze of the Water Tiger Tribe."

The second figure was a man with a human body and the head of a tiger, but there were gills on either side of his face.

The gills on his face were constantly moving, and there was a hint of excitement on his face. Compared with the chorus of cheers for Wu Heli, he seemed to be a far less popular figure.

"Would you like to fight to the death or until an outcome arises?" Miao Kui asked.

Chapter 705: Internal Conflict

"Aren't these supposed to be sparring matches? Why is there an option to fight to the death?" Han Li asked as he turned to Xi Yan.

"Allow me to explain, esteemed immortal. The Saya Festival is not only an occasion for the brightest cultivation prodigies of all of the tribes to make a name for themselves, it's also where many tribes settle their differences. Monarch San Miao prohibits battles between tribes, so this is where everyone settles vendettas and disputes," Xi Yan explained.

"I see. This is not a bad method of conflict resolution," Han Li replied with a nod.

"I have to agree with you on that one, Fellow Daoist Li. This is a very simple and efficient process," Shi Chuankong said to Han Li through voice transmission.

"The fact that this is feasible at all indicates that most of these tribes value their integrity. In the Immortal Realm, all of the tribes would've simply targeted each other without engaging in open battle, and vendettas would most likely escalate to the point where they're entirely unresolvable before such a method can be employed," Han Li replied.

Shi Chuankong contemplated this notion for a moment, then nodded in agreement.

At this point, the battle on the platform had already begun. Wu Heli's aura was clearly more powerful than his opponent's, and there was immense baleful qi swirling around his body as he forced Mu Ze back in retreat.

Despite this, Mu Ze remained calm and collected, and his eyes were still flashing with excitement as he ducked and weaved while wielding a trident.

The more ferocious Wu Heli's attacks became, the faster Mu Ze was forced to take evasive measures, and all of the spectators were cheering loudly at the enthralling battle.

Han Li was rather perplexed by what he was seeing. He could see that Mu Ze was suppressing his own aura, employing a classic tactic of luring the opponent into a false illusion of superiority. At this point, Wu Heli had already tired himself out from the ferocious assault that he was unleashing, and Mu Ze could easily retaliate for the kill, but he refused to do so for some reason, continuing to humor his opponent as he dodged from side to side.

After a while, Han Li felt as if he were a staged match, and he lost interest as he turned his gaze to Wave Edge Lake in the distance.

At this moment, there were still countless specks of flames drifting over the lake, and their light was reflected on the rippling waves down below, making it appear as if there were countless fluorescent fish swimming through the lake.

All of a sudden, Han Li spotted something rather strange on the surface of the lake.

Right as he was about to take a closer look, a thunderous buzzing sound suddenly rang out from behind him, and he was struck by a dull sensation in his mind, as if he had been dealt a heavy blow to the back of his head.

The Imperial Peak Spirit Restriction Talisman in his mind consciousness instantly lit up, releasing a burst of white light to quell the sensation of dullness.

Meanwhile, all of the Gray Lizard beings around him crumpled to the ground.

Out of the corner of his eye, Han Li could see that Mu Ze was standing on the stone platform with blood flowing out of all of his orifices, and he was holding a black seashell-like object aloft with a fervent look in his eyes.

Over at the tent, everyone was slumped in their chairs, and they were still conscious, but they were too feeble to move.

Right at this moment, Han Li felt a tug on his sleeve, and he turned to discover that Shi Chuankong was laying on the ground and was encouraging him to do the same.

Han Li was rather amused to see this, and he pretended to also slump to the ground like everyone else.

Right at this moment, a tall and imposing gray-robed figure among the Water Tiger beings lifted the hood of his cloak to reveal a set of azure ape-like features.

Han Li was surprised to discover that the man was very similar in appearance to the azure apes that he had encountered in the True Mantra Sect ruins. However, his aura indicated that he was at the mid-Golden Immortal Stage, and he was clearly more intelligent than the apes from back then.

The man leaped onto the platform, then strode over to Mu Ze's side and took the black seashell from him before carefully stowing it away.

Mu Ze immediately crumpled to the ground, clearly dead.

The chief of the Water Tiger Tribe rose to his feet from his chair in the tent, then made his way over to the azure ape-like being before extending a deep bow.

"Everything went exactly as you predicted. I am truly in awe of your foresight."

"Mu Qiu! How dare you collude with someone from the Nirarbuda Region? Are you betraying the Black Teeth Region?" Miao Xiu yelled in a furious voice, but she sounded very feeble.

"My apologies, Young Mistress, but the Bone Spike Tribe has forcibly occupied the territory of our Water Tiger Tribe for hundreds of years, and my brother and cousin also died by their hands. Such a vendetta cannot be settled with just a single life!" Mu Qiu said in an expressionless manner, then made his way over to Wu Heli before smashing his head into a pulp.

All of the Water Tiger beings below the platform erupted into thunderous cheers as they rushed toward the Bone Spike beings, and a one-sided massacre ensued, while the chief of the Bone Spike Tribe could only look on from inside the tent with a furious and devastated expression.

"Are you acting on the orders of Monarch Gu, or is your Azure Ape Tribe solely responsible? Are you not afraid that our Black Teeth Region will no longer remain neutral and ally ourselves with the Reincarnation Region?" Miao Xiu spat through gritted teeth.

"Don't bother with these empty threats. We already know that the Reincarnation Region has sent people to meet your father, and it's only a matter of time before you turn on our Nirarbuda Region," the Azure Ape being scoffed.

"You're just saying that to excuse your actions! My father has always been firmly against the Reincarnation Region's actions, and he's done everything in his power to persuade our allies against joining the Reincarnation Region!" Miao Xiu countered.

"Your Black Teeth Region has always thought far too highly of itself. This is what you get for allowing an envoy from the Reincarnation Region to set foot in your territory," the Azure Ape being said with a cold sneer.

He turned to Wave Edge Lake as he spoke, then let loose a loud roar, and the surface of the lake instantly began to churn incessantly as the Azure Ape beings and other Nirarbuda forces that were laying in ambush emerged from the depths, numbering in the tens of thousands.

Upon reaching the shore, they stormed toward the Black Teeth Region tribes, and a horrific massacre ensued.

Han Li and the Gray Lizard beings weren't very far away from the lake, and it wasn't going to take long before the Nirarbuda forces reached them. Neither Han Li nor Shi Chuankong would be able to defend themselves as doing so would expose them to be cultivators of the Immortal Realm, and if that were to happen, then they would be targeted by both the Nirarbuda and Black Teeth Region's forces.

In the Gray Realm, even the most vicious vendettas could temporarily be set aside in order to unite against the threat of the Immortal Realm.

Given Han Li and Shi Chuankong's powers, even if they were exposed, he was confident that they would be able to get away. However, in that scenario, their covers would be blown, and it would become much more difficult for them to find a way back to the Immortal Realm.

"What do we do? They're about to get to us," Shi Chuankong asked in an urgent manner through voice transmission.

Han Li's brows were slightly furrowed, and he didn't immediately respond. Instead, he was looking over at the Azure Ape being on the stone platform, who had summoned a large club, with which it was smashing the heads of the Black Teeth Region chiefs.

Mu Qiu was standing before the chief of the Bone Spike Tribe with a long black saber resting on his neck, preparing to decapitate him.

Despite the dire situation that the chief of the Bone Spike Tribe was in, there was no fear in his eyes at all as he met Mu Qiu's gaze with one of righteous fury.

As the Nirarbuda forces drew closer and closer, Shi Chuankong's agitation was mounting by the second, and even his aura fluctuations had become rather unstable as he said, "It looks like we're not going to be able to maintain our covers. If worse comes to worst, we'll just have to kill everyone here, then get away from this place."

"Don't be rash, I have a way out of this," Han Li immediately replied.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a plume of black mist rose up from beneath him, and it circled around in mid-air for a moment, then descended onto the black stone platform.

As soon as Shi Chuankong detected the aura emanating from the plume of black mist, his expression instantly changed drastically.

He could sense a High Zenith Stage Gray Immortal inside!

Upon arriving above the stone platform, the plume of mist instantly crashed violently down upon the platform, causing it to shatter into countless pieces as cracks spread over its entire surface.

The stone platform exploded violently from the center, following which all of the black mist converged to form a tall and handsome young man wearing a tight-fitting black robe.

He was holding a black folding fan, and his High Zenith Stage aura was completely unrestrained.

The man was none other than Mo Guang in his Gray Immortal body, but prior to emerging from the Flower Branch domain, he had adopted this youthful appearance.

Everyone was completely caught off guard by this abrupt turn of events, and on one knew what to make of Mo Guang's sudden emergence.

As soon as the club-wielding Azure Ape being's gaze fell upon Mo Guang, his expression instantly changed drastically as he exclaimed, "You're from the Void Integration Tribe! This is impossible! How could there be a Void Integration being here?"

"The Void Integration Tribe? Judging from your reaction, that seems like quite a powerful tribe," Mo Guang chuckled.

Chapter 706: Invitation

Han Li didn't have full trust in Mo Guang, so he was intently observing the unfolding scene on the stone platform, and his heart also stirred slightly upon hearing mention of the Void Integration Tribe.

The Void Integration Tribe had appeared in the scriptures that Han Li had gathered on more than one occasion, but all records about them were rather ambiguous in their wording, not because this was an extremely secretive tribe, or because the Gray Lizard Tribe's information gathering abilities were lackluster.

Instead, it was because the Void Integration Tribe was an extremely high-ranking noble tribe even in the context of the entire Gray Realm.

In contrast, the Gray Lizard Tribe was a bottom feeder, even in the Black Teeth Region, so the separation between the two tribes couldn't have been any larger, and it was no wonder that the Gray Lizard Tribe wasn't able to gather much information at all.

All Han Li knew was that the Void Integration Tribe ruled over the Young Dawn Region, which was allied to the Reincarnation Region, thereby making it an enemy of the tribes of the Nirarbuda Region.

Aside from that, Han Li knew nothing else about the Void Integration Tribe, and he had no idea that the body that Mo Guang had taken over had once belonged to a Void Integration being.

Despite this unexpected turn of events, the Azure Ape being was too stunned to issue any orders for the Nirarbuda forces to stop what they were doing, so the massacre continued, and many Gray Lizard beings had already been slain.

"Stop them, Mo Guang," Han Li instructed through voice transmission.

Mo Guang didn't immediately spring into action upon hearing this. Instead, he took a glance in Han Li's direction.

Everyone was rather perplexed to see this, and they all turned in the same direction as well. Han Li cursed under his breath as he hurriedly concealed his aura and pretended to be unconscious.

At the same time, the Heavenly Devil Contract that he had signed with Mo Guang was already beginning to appear in his consciousness.

Thankfully, Mo Guang didn't make any false moves, and he turned to the Azure Ape being as he put away his black folding fan, then cracked his knuckles as he grinned to reveal two rows of pristine and even teeth.

As Miao Xiu stared at Mo Guang, all of her fear and panic suddenly faded, and his smile resembled a warm and shining beacon in her eyes.

In direct contrast with Miao Xiu, the Azure Ape being was absolutely horrified by the sight of Mo Guang's smile, and he felt as if his entire body had been plunged into a glacial pit.

He gritted his teeth tightly as he tightened his grip around the black seashell, hoping that this treasure that had been bestowed upon him by his monarch would be able to save him.

However, before he had a chance to do anything else, the voice of a devil suddenly rang out beside his ears.

"What are you thinking?"

Mo Guang had transformed into a plume of gray mist, which had wrapped itself around the Azure Ape being like a snake completely without his detection. The only part of Mo Guang's body that remained intact was his head, and it was hovering right next to the Azure Ape being's head.

The Azure Ape being screamed in horror, and as soon as he opened his mouth, the plume of gray mist that Mo Guang had transformed into instantly surged into his body through all of his orifices.

An agonized look appeared on the Azure Ape being's face as he dropped his club and black seashell, then clasped his hands tightly around his own neck and stumbled a few steps backward before toppling to the ground.

Only after he fell completely still did the plume of black mist re-emerge from his body before reverting back to form Mo Guang's body.

Mo Xiu and the others were all astonished to see this, and their mouths were gaped open slightly in a stunned silence.

Meanwhile, Mo Guang merely picked up the black seashell from the ground, upon which his entire body stiffened momentarily, but wisps of baleful qi then surged out of the palm of his hand to envelop the seashell to commence the refinement process.

Moments later, he gently flicked the seashell with his finger, and a burst of black light instantly erupted out of it before sweeping in all directions, stirring up faint ripples over the surface of Wave Edge Lake.

As the burst of black light washed over all of the Black Teeth Tribe beings, the sense of feebleness that was plaguing them instantly vanished, and they sprang to their feet to battle against the Nirarbuda forces.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong also sprang up from the ground, but instead of participating in the battle, they rushed toward the stone platform.

On the stone platform, Mu Qiu's face had turned deathly pale at the sight of the Azure Ape being's demise, and he immediately turned to flee toward Wave Edge Lake, but the chief of the Bone Spike Tribe had already appeared in his path before he had a chance to move.

The other chiefs in the tent that were still alive immediately sprang into action as well to surround Mu Qiu from all directions, while Miao Xiu ordered in an expressionless manner, "Kill him."

The tribal chiefs instantly executed the order without any hesitation.

"Chiefs of the Mountain Ghost, Wind Ermine, and Gray Scythe Tribes, gather your tribesmen for a counterattack!"

"Members of the Azure Carp, Mud Ox, and Earth Core Tribes, enter Wave Edge Lake to pursue the enemy! We don't have a numbers advantage, so there's no need to surround them, just kill as many of them as possible..."

"Miao Zong, lead the other tribe to go after the enemy tribal chiefs and the fleeing enemy forces."

Miao Xiu issued a string of commands to the Black Teeth Tribe tribal chiefs, and a counterattack quickly took shape.

With their commander dead, the Nirarbuda forces were instantly thrown into a state of panic and disarray. To further compound their woes, the Black Teeth Region's tribes were eager for revenge, and it didn't take long before the Nirarbuda forces were pushed back into Wave Edge Lake.

Mo Guang also refrained from further participation in the battle as he casually strolled over to the edge of the stone platform, where he watched the unfolding battle with an intrigued look on his face.

At this point, Han Li and Shi Chuankong had also descended onto the stone platform after ducking and weaving their way through the chaotic battlefield.

Shi Chuankong's expression remained unchanged at the sight of Mo Guang, but internally, he was utterly astonished, and he turned to Han Li with a hesitant expression as he asked through voice transmission, "Who is this, Fellow Daoist Li?"

"You can call him Fellow Daoist Mo Guang. I suppose you can say that he's a contracted ally of mine. He was unable to appear prior to this due to some special reasons, but he'll be around a lot more from now on," Han Li explained in a concise fashion.

Mo Guang gave Shi Chuankong a smile and a nod, in response to which Shi Chuankong cupped his fist in a salute and gave a self-introduction.

"I read in the records of the Gray Lizard Tribe that the Void Integration Tribe has three main surnames, namely Tusu, Dongling, and Jiang. From now on, your name will be Jiang Gu, and we are your servants," Han Li said through voice transmission.

Mo Guang nodded in response, but then pursed his lips as he objected, "I don't really like that name. It sounds like I'm about to die soon." [1]

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly, and he was just about to say something when he spotted Miao Xiu approaching them.

She stopped quite a few steps away, then extended a respectful curtsey as she said, "I am Miao Xiu, the daughter of Monarch San Miao of our Black Teeth Region. May I know your name, Senior?"

Mo Guang turned to Miao Xiu with a smile, then blatantly scoured his gaze over her body, and he was just about to reply when Han Li's voice rang out in his mind.

"Fellow Daoist Mo Guang, we are in a different realm right now, so please do be careful with your words and actions."

"Ah, so you're a young mistress of the San Miao Tribe. My name is Jiang Gu, and these are my servants, Li Han and Shi Chuankong," Mo Guang said with a smile.

"It's extremely fortunate for us that you're here today, Senior Jiang. Otherwise, all of our Black Teeth Region tribes would've suffered extremely severe losses," Miao Xiu said as she extended another curstey.

"I just so happened to be passing through the Black Teeth Region, and I wasn't going to get involved, but that green monkey was really annoying me," Mo Guang said in a casual manner.

"This attack from the Nirarbuda tribes is a declaration of war against our Black Teeth Region, so I have to get back to our San Miao Tribe to report everything to my father. You are the savior of our Black Teeth Region, so please allow us the opportunity to show you our hospitality," Miao Xiu said with a serious expression.

Mo Guang didn't immediately respond to the invitation. Instead, he appeared as if he were mulling over the offer while internally asking Han Li about how to proceed.

"We can go with her. We have no set objective at the moment anyway, so it wouldn't be a bad thing to go somewhere more safe and secure. On top of that, there should be more information at the San Miao Tribe as well," Han Li communicated through voice transmission.

"I suppose it would be rude to turn down such an earnest invitation. Having said that, I'm trying to keep a low profile at the moment, so please keep this a secret. Ideally, don't even tell your father about me for now," Mo Guang said in a serious manner.

Miao Xiu was ecstatic to hear this, and she immediately replied, "Rest assured, Senior, I won't tell anyone about you before we arrive at Serene Millet City. I'll only inform my father of your arrival once we get there, and of course, I'll ask him to keep your presence in our tribe a secret as well."

"That would be best," Mo Guang said with a nod.

"In that case, please allow me to take care of the matters at hand, and after that, I'll make arrangements for our journey to Serene Millet City," Miao Xiu said.

Mo Guang offered no response, merely dismissing her with a wave of his hand.

Following Miao Xiu's departure, Mo Guang turned his gaze back to the battlefield, which was filled with baleful qi from the slaughter that had just taken place, and he inhaled deeply with a content look on his face.

"Fellow Daoist Li, are we not taking too much of a risk here?" Shi Chuankong asked with a concerned expression.

"It's fine. With Fellow Daoist Mo Guang's identity as a Void Integration being, the people of the San Miao Tribe wouldn't dare to examine us too closely. All we have to do is be on our guard, and we should be able to maintain our covers," Han Li replied.

Shi Chuankong didn't say anything further, but the concern in his eyes didn't fade away, either.

[1]. The name that Han Li proposed (将古) can translate to imminent history, implying that Mo Guang is about to become history. Having said that, 古 (Gu) is also a pretty common name, and as far as I can tell, there's no intentional foreshadowing here or anything like that.

[Back]

Chapter 707: Spoils

Several days later, Miao Xiu arrived at the Gray Lizard Tribe's tent with only a few of her most trusted subordinates, waiting for Han Li's trio to join them on their journey back to Serene Millet City.

Han Li's trio was already prepared, and they bade farewell to Xi Yan and the others, then made their way toward the San Miao Tribe's tent.

Chief Xi Yan couldn't help but feel a little forlorn as he watched the trio depart.

He had already learned from Miao Xiu that the two people who had saved their Gray Lizard Tribe were both extremely distinguished figures, and he was thinking to himself that if he had done just a little better, perhaps this could've been a massive opportunity for the Gray Lizard Tribe.

Right at this moment, Miao Kui hurriedly returned to Xi Yan, then extended a respectful bow.

Xi Yan was horrified to see this, and he hurriedly returned the bow as he asked, "Esteemed Envoy Miao, to what do I owe this honor?"

"My apologies for how I treated you earlier, Chief Xi Yan. The Gray Lizard Tribe has made an immense contribution during this festival, and our young mistress has ordered me to reward you with two thousand gray crystals. On top of that, once we get back to Serene Millet City, she'll ask our monarch to grant you a portion of the Water Tiger Tribe's territory," Miao Kui said.

Xi Yan was completely rooted to the spot upon hearing this, following which tears began to well up in his eyes, and he fell to his knees to thank Miao Kui.

Miao Kui hurriedly lifted him back to his feet, then continued, "There's no need for such formalities, Chief Xi Yan. Our three esteemed guests have spoken quite highly of you, and you've made some very valuable allies for our Black Teeth Region, so the Gray Lizard Tribe is deserving of this reward."

"Thank you, esteemed Envoy Miao. Thank you, Young Mistress. Thank you, esteemed immortals," Xi Yan said in an earnest and heartfelt voice.

At this point, Han Li's trio had already arrived at the lake with Miao Xiu, and there was an enormous three-story louchuan waiting for them. The louchuan was completely black in color, and its design was very sharp and angular. There were all types of complex patterns engraved onto its surface, and even though it was completely devoid of color, it was still extremely opulent, nonetheless.

Laying in front of the louchuan were three horse-like giant beasts that were each over a hundred feet tall. There were white exoskeletons on their faces and a corkscrew horn on each of their heads. On top of that, each of them had two pairs of giant gray fleshy wings that were tucked tightly against their sides.

"This louchuan is able to fly in the sky, and it may not be as fast as some of the flying treasures in your possession, but it's quite stable. I've already cleared out the guest rooms on the third floor, so you can stay there over the course of the journey," Miao Xiu said to Mo Guang upon landing on the deck of the louchuan.

"I'll be in your care then," Mo Guang replied with a smile and a nod.

After that, Miao Xiu led Han Li's trio up to the third floor, making some conversation with Mo Guang in the process. Han Li and Shi Chuankong remained standing silently on either side of Mo Guang the entire time, acting as obedient servants.

While speaking with Mo Guang, Miao Xiu's gaze passed over Han Li briefly, and there seemed to be a hint of befuddlement in her eyes, but Han Li merely pretended as if he didn't see anything.

Upon arriving on the third floor of the louchuan, Han Li's trio each chose a guest room to stay in, while Miao Xiu departed to arrange for the louchuan to set off.

The three giant winged horse-like creatures rose to their hooves, then galloped forward for over ten thousand feet before spreading their wings and flapping them vigorously, sweeping up powerful white air currents that lifted them and the louchuan up into the sky.

Standing in his room, Han Li looked out the window to find that it was impossible to see anything through the dense mist and baleful qi outside.

His brows were tightly furrowed as he swept a sleeve through the air, conjuring up an azure light barrier over all of the windows to keep the baleful qi outside at bay.

In order to avoid arousing suspicions, Han Li didn't set up any restrictions with prominent spiritual power fluctuations in his room. Instead, he only set up some simple aura concealment restrictions.

By the time he was done, the louchuan had also broken through the dense layer of baleful clouds, arriving in the sky above.

The black mist outside faded away, and Han Li removed the azure light barrier as he cast his gaze toward the sky outside.

Even without the baleful clouds in the way, the sky remained a murky gray color. The three suns were hanging high up in the sky, giving off white light that wasn't exactly cold, but wasn't very warm, either, and it was rather disconcerting.

In the sky above the layer of clouds, the baleful qi was clearly far less abundant, and that eased the strain on Han Li significantly.

After meditating for some time, Daoist Xie's voice suddenly rang out in his mind.

"Fellow Daoist Li, I've already sorted out all of the storage tools that you gave me earlier. Would you like to see me now?"

"Sure," Han Li replied, then swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up a door of silver light, and Daoist Xie stepped out of the bamboo building to enter Han Li's room.

The two of them sat down at the round table in the room, and Han Li flipped a hand over to produce a flagon of floral wine.

He had constantly been busying himself with various tasks upon arriving in the Gray Realm, and only now did he have an opportunity to relax and have a drink.

"I've sorted through all of the items in the storage bracelets, and in total, they contained 15,317 top-grade spirit stones, 58,312 Immortal Origin Stones, and 321 mid-grade Immortal Origin Stones, all of which are in here," Daoist Xie said as it flipped a hand over to produce a white storage bracelet.

These storage tools were all from the True Mantra Sect ruins, and most of them belonged to Heavenly Court cultivators and True Mantra Sect disciples ranging between the early-True Immortal Stage and the late-Golden Immortal Stage, so they didn't have much use for top-grade spirit stones.

On top of that, mid-grade Immortal Origin Stones were quite difficult to come by for cultivators of this caliber, so Immortal Origin Stones were most common in their storage tools by far.

Han Li took a sip of wine as he waited for Daoist Xie to continue.

"In here are some miscellaneous items for setting up arrays, including array flags, array plates, and some larger array stones and spirit patterns pillars. I've picked out some of them to be buried around the bamboo building near the spirit medicine garden to construct another array. Having said that, the construction of the Flower Branch domain is extremely advanced to begin with, so I'm not sure how much use this new array will be," Daoist Xie continued.

"Thank you for your efforts, Brother Xie," Han Li replied with a smile.

"In here are some treasures of various different attributes, out of which over two hundred are immortal treasures, but only one of them is a graded one. It's a lightning-attribute blade that I was hoping you would temporarily lend to... No, sell to me. As for the price, you can decide, and I'll compensate you at a later date," Daoist Xie continued.

It set down a black storage bracelet onto the table as it spoke, then flipped a hand over to produce a long black saber.

The saber was riddled with spirit patterns, and there were eight longan-sized purple beads wight lightning flashing within them embedded into its blade.

It was an eighth-grade immortal treasure, and as Daoist Xie injected a burst of immortal spiritual power into it, the seven purple beads on the blade instantly began to glow radiantly, sending powerful lightning-attribute energy fluctuations erupting in all directions.

Han Li was given quite a fright, and he hurriedly stifled the energy fluctuations as he said, "I'm not going to sell or lend this blade to you."

A hint of disappointment flashed through Daoist Xie's eyes upon hearing this, but it immediately faded away as it began to set the blade down onto the table.

However, Han Li reached out to stop it as he said, "I can give this saber to you, but I want to ask you some things, and I hope you can be truthful with me."

A hesitant look flashed through Daoist Xie's eyes, and only after a long silence did it nod in response.

"Have you recovered most of your memories?" Han Li asked.

"I've recovered a lot of my memories, but they're a little bit jumbled, and I've been trying to sort through them this entire time, but to no avail. If you want to ask about that, then I'm afraid I don't have any answers for you," Daoist Xie replied with a shake of its head.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he asked, "What is the wish that your former owner wants me to fulfill?"

"I'm afraid that's a memory that I'm still yet to recover, Fellow Daoist Han. However, what I'm certain of is that it's definitely no easy feat to complete," Daoist Xie replied with a wry smile.

"Well, that didn't help at all," Han Li sighed. "It's fine, you can have the saber."

Daoist Xie hesitated momentarily before stowing the saber away, then said, "Judging from the inscriptions on the blade, its name appears to be Heavenslash. Looking at the forging methods employed and the patterns on its surface, it seems to have come from the same origins as Thunderslash, except it appears to be a bit older and also of a higher quality.

“In any case, both are extremely formidable weapons, and I'll be sure to repay you for this in the future."

Han Li merely waved a hand in response as he stowed away the storage bracelets on the table.

"There's one final thing I have for you. Inside this storage are the pills and spirit plants that I gathered from the storage tools that you gave me. I'm sure there are many precious items in there, but most of them are unrecognizable to me, so I'll let you sort through them," Daoist Xie said.

Han Li nodded in response and picked up the storage ring, then briefly refined it before examining its contents, upon which his mood was instantly lifted significantly.

Not only did the storage ring contain all types of recovery and cultivation pills, there were also large quantities of rare and precious spirit ingredients and spirit plants, some of which even he couldn't identify.

What caught his eye the most was the dozen of fist-sized Profound Zoysia Crystals in the storage ring. This was a vital ingredient for refining Baleful Quelling Pills, and with the Bitter Ornament Herbs that he had purchased during the Tamda Festival, he now had both the primary ingredients required to refine Baleful Quelling Pill.

This was something that he was going to have to do as soon as possible. Otherwise, if his baleful decay were to rear its ugly head here in the Gray Realm, then that could easily spell his end.

However, this wasn't a process that could be hurried, so he would have to wait until he reached a safer and more secure place before he commenced his pill refinement.

After stowing the storage ring away, Han Li asked Daoist Xie about how the domain was looking, upon which he was informed that all was well in the spirit medicine garden. The Dao Warriors that had been planted were about to reach maturity, but the remnants of the Twin Birth Tree were still completely devoid of vitality.

The Essence Fire Raven was still encased within that silver ball, displaying no signs of waking up anytime soon.

Han Li wasn't overly concerned about this. Having witnessed the power of the Rainbow Fire Pill Sand, he wouldn't be surprised even if the Essence Fire Raven were to hibernate for over a decade.

Chapter 708: Meeting

After some further conversation, Daoist Xie returned to the Flower Branch domain, while Han Li drank by himself for a short while longer before suddenly leaving his room.

In a guest room at the end of the louchuan's third floor, Mo Guang was meditating with his eyes closed when his eyes suddenly sprang open, and he said, "Come in, Fellow Daoist Li. I've been waiting for you for quite some time."

The door of the room swung open, and Han Li made his way inside.

After casually setting up a restriction in the room, Han Li closed the door and asked, "You knew I was going to come?"

He swept his gaze across the room as he spoke to find that it was a lot larger than his, and the furnishings were also more intricate. On top of that, there was a dish of black fruits with fiery patterns on them placed on the table.

"Given the delicate situation that we're in, I figured that you would come and give me some advice on how to speak and act," Mo Guang said with a smile as he picked up one of the black fruits before biting into it, releasing the dark purple juices and wisps of black baleful qi inside.

"Not at all, Fellow Daoist Mo Guang. You've already lived for countless years, and you possess far more knowledge and experience than I do. On top of that, we're connected by the Heavenly Devil Contract, so there's no need for me to tell you how to conduct yourself. Instead, I've come here as I have something to ask you," Han Li said in a seemingly nonchalant fashion.

"Oh? What is it?" Mo Guang asked with a perplexed expression.

"I secured this bone bracelet from the body of that Gray Immortal on the first floor, and it looks to me like a storage tool used by Gray Immortals. I attempted to refine it using immortal spiritual power, but to no avail, and I've also tried to inject baleful qi into it, but that didn't work, either," Han Li explained as he pulled out the bracelet before tossing it at Mo Guang.

Mo Guang accepted the bracelet, and following a brief inspection, he smiled and confirmed, "This is indeed a storage tool."

After that, he chanted an incantation, and wisps of baleful qi surged out of the palm of his hand as began to refine the bracelet.

Moments later, the baleful qi emanating out of his hand dissipated to reveal the bracelet again, and it released a burst of gray light onto the ground.

A small pile of gray crystals clattered onto the ground, accompanied by several weapons and a bunch of peculiar Gray Realm materials.

Han Li inspected the contents of the bracelet momentarily, then swept a sleeve through the air to stow half of the gray crystals into his own storage bracelet, while the rest of the items remained on the ground.

"What are you doing?" Mo Guang asked.

"You can keep what's here. We can't have a high-grade Void Integration Tribe cultivator walking around without a storage tool," Han Li explained, then promptly withdrew the restriction that he had set up in Mo Guang's room before bidding him farewell.

Following Han Li's departure, Mo Guang stood in his own room with a contemplative look on his face.

......

Over three years flew by in a flash.

The louchan had been soaring above the baleful clouds this entire time, but it was finally beginning its descent, having arrived at Serene Millet City.

Han Li and the others were standing on the deck of the louchuan, looking down below, and they could see a vast plain that was dotted with gray forts of different sizes, interspersed throughout which were around a dozen black rivers.

These gray forts all had conical rooves, and they were situated quite close to one another. The area wasn't bordered by any city walls, and it appeared that this was a concentrated settlement formed by countless stone forts.

At the center of the plain was a giant plaza and a dense cluster of these stone forts.

Before long, the louchuan descended onto the plaza, and Han Li and the others flew down from it.

"It's still quite early, so why don't you come with me to meet my father, Senior Jiang?" Miao Xiu proposed to Mo Guang as she led the way from the front.

"I'll follow your lead, Ms. Miao," Mo Guang replied with a dazzling smile.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong were trailing along behind him like a pair of obedient servants, even making it a point not to look around much.

After the group passed over the plaza, they made their way through a series of intricately crafted corridors before arriving at a giant stone palace, in front of which was a staircase of around a dozen steps.

They were approached by a gray-robed elderly man, who extended a deep bow toward Miao Xiu with an ecstatic expression as he greeted, "Welcome back, Young Mistress."

"Where's my father right now, Uncle Zhong?" Miao Xiu asked with a smile.

The elderly man took a glance at Han Li's trio, then pointed to the palace behind him as he replied, "Our monarch is currently entertaining some guests, so I'm afraid he won't be able to see you now."

"Uncle Zhong, these three behind me are Void Integration beings who've saved my life. Can you pass on a message to my father to see if he can meet with us first and postpone his current meeting to another time?" Miao Xiu asked.

The elderly man's expression instantly changed slightly upon hearing this, and he hurriedly replied, "Ah, these are esteemed guests from the Void Integration Tribe? Please wait a moment, Young Mistress, I'll pass on the message right away."

With that, he rushed into the palace, then returned shortly thereafter as he said, "You can go in, Young Mistress."

An elated look flashed through Miao Xiu's eyes upon hearing this, and she led Han Li's trio to the palace.

Right as they were about to enter the palace, the door suddenly swung open, and a young man from the San Miao Tribe emerged from the palace with a serious-looking middle-aged man behind him.

The man had a set of authoritative facial features, and he was giving off tremendous baleful qi fluctuations.

Han Li's pupils instantly contracted slightly at the sight of the man.

Even though he was wearing a black robe, and his hair had also turned black, Han Li was certain that this man was none other than the first dao lord of the Blaze Dragon Dao, Baili Yan!

They had last met briefly back when Han Li was fighting over the High Zenith Pills in the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, and he certainly wasn't expecting to see Baili Yan again in the Gray Realm.

Right as these thoughts were flashing through Han Li's mind, he passed Baili Yan by, the latter didn't even take a glance at him, clearly having failed to recognize him.

Upon entering the palace, Han Li spotted a middle-aged man seated on the main chair inside. His facial features bore some resemblance to Miao Xiu's, and it appeared that he was Monarch Miao Gao of the Black Teeth Region.

There were several black-robed figures standing beside him, and all of them appeared to be quite advanced in age. All of them turned to Miao Xiu with benevolent smiles on their faces, clearly very pleased with her safe return.

"Miao Xiu pays her respects to her father and elders," Miao Xiu said as she extended a slight bow.

"Greetings, Monarch Miao Hao, I am Jiang Gu of the Void Integration Tribe," Mo Guang said as he stepped forward while crossing an arm over his chest and touching his fist to his own shoulder.

"We pay our respects to Monarch Miao Gao," Han Li and Shi Chuankong said in unison while extending bows of their own.

Miao Gao had already stood up from his chair, and he returned Mo Guang's salute as he said, "I've already been informed of what happened at Wave Edge Lake by our carrier Gray Light Pigeon. Thank you for saving our Black Teeth Region and my daughter, Brother Jiang. Our Black Teeth Region may be secluded, but we're aware of the importance of repaying favors, so I've prepared a small gift for you. Please don't refuse it."

As soon as his voice trailed off, a white-haired elderly man approached Mo Guang before offering him a bone ring with both hands.

"You're too kind, Monarch Miao Gao," Mo Guang replied with a smile as he accepted the ring.

"Why have you come all this way to our Black Teeth Region from the Young Dawn Region, Brother Jiang? If you need anything, feel free to tell me, and our San Miao Tribe will do everything in its power to help you," Miao Gao said.

After communicating briefly with Han Li through voice transmission, Mo Guang replied, "I was out traveling with my servants here when I encountered an extremely powerful great demon and I pursued it all the way to the Six Moon Grassland. After that, I encountered the Gray Lizard Tribe by chance, and I heard that the Tamda Festival was coming up soon, so I decided to accompany them top broaden my horizons."

"I see. In that case, it sounds like it was fate that brought us together today. May I ask what is the great demon that you were hunting? Perhaps we can help you," Miao Gao said.

"That thing's already long gone. Otherwise, I wouldn't have decided to stay with the Gray Lizard Tribe. From here, I'm planning to complete my travels and return to the Young Dawn Region," Mo Guang replied with a smile.

"If you're traveling anyway, then why don't you stay in our Serene Millet City for a while? It would give us an opportunity to show you our hospitality," Miao Gao offered with a smile.

"In that case, I'll be in your care," Mo Guang replied.

"Xiuxiu, go and arrange a place for guests to stay, then come and see me in the inner manor," Miao Gao said.

Miao Xiu gave an affirmative response, then led Han Li's trio out of the palace toward a cluster of stone forts.

There were some huge, leafless flowers planted around the cluster of buildings, releasing wisps of black baleful qi, and the closer the deeper they went into the cluster of buildings, the more concentrated these flowers became.

Han Li wasn't surprised to see this. In the Gray Realm, baleful qi was essentially equivalent to the world's origin qi, and it stood to reason that the San Miao Tribe would arrange for its guests to stay in a place where baleful qi was most abundant.

Sure enough, Miao Xiu only stopped in her tracks upon arriving at the stone fort in the very heart of the cluster of buildings.

"This palace is reserved for our San Miao Tribe's most esteemed guests. Please enjoy your stay here, and if you need anything, feel free to inform me," Miao Xiu said with a smile.

"Thank you," Mo Guang replied with a smile.

Miao Xiu still had to see her father, so she bade Han Li's trio farewell before departing.

Han Li's trio entered the palace, then picked out rooms for themselves, and Shi Chuankong entered his room, while Mo Guang followed Han Li into another room.

Chapter 709: Predicament

Right as Han Li and Mo Guang arrived at the entrance of the room, the former suddenly stopped cold in his tracks as his body shuddered violently.

"What's wrong, Fellow Daoist Han?" Mo Guang hurriedly asked.

Han Li offered no response. At this moment, a layer of gray light had emerged over his eyes, and his facial muscles were beginning to spasm, indicating that he was enduring some type of severe pain.

Immediately thereafter, his entire body began to tremble, while his complexion turned deathly pale.

For some reason, the baleful qi in his immortal acupoints had suddenly begun to churn violently in an uncontrollable fashion.

All of a sudden, bursts of inky-black baleful qi began to erupt out of his body, and they were flailing around like devilish tentacles, causing the surrounding air temperature to plummet.

"Let's go in the room first," Mo Guang said, and Han Li pushed the door open before making his way inside.

Could it be that my baleful decay is rearing its head again? What a terrible time for this to happen...

It had already been several centuries since the previous onset of baleful decay, and the delaying effect of the threads of time had already worn off, so this wasn't too much of a surprise.

With that in mind, he swept both sleeves through the air, releasing hundreds of array flags that landed around the room to set up several sturdy restrictions.

Mo Guang also contributed to the effort, raising a hand to release a burst of black light, which created another black restriction in addition to Han Li's.

This restriction was filled with black mist, and a series of interlocking black chains could be seen within it.

A burst of mellow baleful qi fluctuations was emanating from the array, interspersed with law power fluctuations, and it was immediately able to contain the majority of the baleful qi that was flowing out of Han Li's body.

Thanks to their combined efforts, all of Han Li's baleful qi fluctuations had been contained, but everything had happened so abruptly that they weren't able to contain the initial eruption of baleful qi.

At the same time, all of the baleful qi in the surrounding area was drawn to the palace in a frenzy, creating an enormous phenomenon that was no less formidable than what one would expect to see from a breakthrough for a Gray Immortal.

At this moment, Miao Xiu was on her way to the inner manor, and she suddenly turned in the direction of the palace as a hint of amazement flashed through her eyes.

"Such immense baleful qi fluctuations! As expected of a Void Integration being..." Miao Xiu murmured to herself with a contemplative look in her eyes.

Shi Chuankong was currently seated with his eyes closed on the bed in his room. The silver lute was hovering above his head, and he seemed to be refining the treasures, but all of a sudden, his eyes sprang open as he cast his gaze toward the entrance of his room.

......

Inside Han Li's room, Daoist Xie appeared amid a flash of golden lightning.

"I'm going to need your help, Fellow Daoist Mo Guang, Brother Xie," Han Li said as he sat down with his legs crossed and began to channel his cultivation arts.

In the next instant, a burst of radiant golden light erupted out of his body, accompanied by bursts of time law power fluctuations.

Mo Guang and Daoist Xie exchanged a glance with each other, then each made their way to a corner of the room before sitting down with their legs crossed.

Right as Han Li was channeling his time law powers to protect his immortal acupoints, he discovered that something wasn't quite right.

At this moment, only the immortal acupoints in his body that had been infiltrated by baleful qi were in a state of unrest, while his remaining, clean immortal acupoints remained normal, and that was different from the previous onset of baleful decay.

Could this not be an onset of baleful decay?

If this were an onset of baleful decay, then even though he was confident in his ability to suppress it, it was going to take him some time. At the moment, he was in the Gray Realm, so if anyone were to detect that he was enduring a baleful decay, then his cover would be instantly blown.

With that in mind, Han Li channeled his immortal spiritual power and time law powers to suppress the churning baleful qi in his body with all his might.

However, despite his best efforts, the baleful qi in his immortal acupoints only became more and more restless, as if they were being stimulated by something.

Han Li could feel his agitation growing by the second, and a burst of irrepressible impulses were arising within his heart.

At this moment, his eyes were glowing red, and his aura was becoming more and more violent.

On top of that, the baleful qi in the surrounding space was rapidly converging toward him as if it were being attracted before fusing into his immortal acupoints.

The amount of baleful qi in his immortal acupoints was rapidly increasing, and it was becoming more and more restless.

Han Li bit down onto the tip of his own tongue, using the pain to ensure that he remained lucid and in control, and he conjured up a door of silver light before stepping into the Flower Branch domain.

Upon entering the Flower Branch domain, the baleful qi converging toward him was also brought into the domain. As a result, the baleful qi in the room instantly became a lot sparser, while the amount of baleful qi in his immortal acupoints also ceased to compound any further.

Han Li's expression eased slightly upon sensing this, and he sat down with his legs crossed before summoning a Baleful Quelling Pill, which he promptly devoured.

The pill quickly melted away, and two enormous auras, one hot and one cold, appeared before flowing through his entire body.

All of his pores opened up involuntarily, and bursts of incredibly dense baleful qi surged out of his entire body.

When did I accumulate so much baleful qi? Han Li wondered to himself with a bewildered expression.

Thanks to the three Baleful Quelling Pills that he had taken last time, much of the baleful qi in his body outside of his immortal acupoints had been expelled, so it didn't make sense for so much of it to have returned in such a short time.

Could it be that the baleful-qi-rich environment in the Gray Realm is what's doing this to me?

After some contemplation, Han Li shook his head to rid himself of that train of thought before focusing on refining the Baleful Quelling Pill.

Right at this moment, Mo Guang appeared behind him, then began to chant an incantation before raising both hands to release two bursts of black light, which quickly converged to form a thick pillar of black light.

The pillar of black light took on the form of a giant beastly projection that appeared to be somewhere between a tiger and a lion, and it opened its mouth up wide, devouring all of the baleful qi that was surging out of Han Li's body.

Not only that, but the suction force released by the projection was enveloping his entire body, significantly increasing the rate of baleful qi expulsion.

Thanks to the Baleful Quelling Pill and Mo Guang's assistance, the baleful qi in his body was rapidly being expunged, and the baleful qi in his immortal acupoints gradually subsided as well.

Around a week flew by in a flash.

The baleful qi surging out of Han Li's body gradually diminished until it disappeared altogether, and he slowly opened his eyes, which had returned to their normal, lucid state.

At the same time, Mo Guang dispelled the pillar of black light, and Han Li inspected his own internal condition to find that the unrest in the baleful qi in his immortal acupoints had subsided.

However, the amount of baleful qi in his immortal acupoints hadn't decreased at all. In fact, it had increased slightly from the baleful qi that it had absorbed from the outside world, and he couldn't help but heave a forlorn sigh upon seeing this.

The baleful qi lingered in his immortal acupoints like persistent spirits, constantly threatening to rear its ugly head again.

"Thank you for your help, Fellow Daoist Mo Guang," Han Li said.

"It's fine, don't worry about it," Mo Guang replied with a wave of his hand.

"Fellow Daoist Mo Guang, given that you've occupied this Gray Immortal body for all this time, I'm sure you must've become quite familiar with baleful qi. Were you able to make any observations these past few days? Why did the baleful qi in my immortal acupoints suddenly become so violent?" Han Li asked.

"At the moment, you're in the Gray Realm, so your body is constantly in contact with baleful qi from the outside world. Given your current struggles with baleful decay, there's a large amount of baleful qi in your body, and the two attract each other.

“Hence, ever since you entered the Gray Realm, the amount of baleful qi in your body has been rapidly increasing without your detection, and it was most likely the excessive abundance of baleful qi in your body that triggered the unrest in the baleful qi in your immortal acupoints," Mo Guang explained.

"I see," Han Li replied with a nod.

Upon entering the Gray Realm, it initially seemed as if he could acclimate himself to the environment here. However, due to the abundance of baleful qi in his body and the fact that he had used a Gray Realm cultivation art in the past, his body had undergone some changes, essentially making him half a Gray Immortal.

Under these circumstances, the baleful qi in his body would go into this state of unrest over and over again, causing his body to slowly acclimate to this environment. At this rate, it would most likely only take about a thousand years for him to completely become a Gray Immortal with no possibility of turning back.

"The baleful qi in other parts of your body can be easily expelled using Baleful Quelling Pills, but there's no way to expel the baleful qi in your immortal acupoints. We've managed to suppress your baleful qi this time, but I'm not sure how many more times we'll be able to do this," Mo Guang said with a serious expression.

"It looks like the only two options open to me are to return to the True Immortal Realm or overcome my baleful decay," Han Li said with a wry smile.

Clearly, it wasn't going to be easy to leave the Gray Realm in a short time, but overcoming his baleful decay in the Gray Realm was going to be next to impossible, and thus, he was faced with a very difficult predicament.

Chapter 710: Baleful Cleansing Pond

Following Mo Guang's departure, Han Li sat back down with a contemplative expression, and it was unclear what he was thinking.

A short while later, Han Li received a visit from Shi Chuankong, and he opened the door to let him in.

"Fellow Daoist Li, I could sense that you were busy these past few days, so I didn't dare to come and disturb you. During this time, Miao Xiu came to visit on two occasions, and I had to make up excuses both times to send her away. I'm worried that if you don't show up soon, the San Miao Tribe will begin to grow suspicious," Shi Chuankong said.

"Why did she come to visit?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"She didn't go into detail, but it seems like she'll be leaving the Black Teeth Region soon, and she wants to visit Jiang Gu, or Fellow Daoist Mo Guang, before she goes. However, I think she most likely came to investigate the irregular baleful qi fluctuations from last time," Shi Chuankong replied.

"In any case, if she comes again, then we'll just have to meet her. With Fellow Daoist Mo Guang acting as our cover, they wouldn't dare to do anything out of line," Han Li said after a brief moment of contemplation.

Shi Chuankong nodded in response, and that seemed to be the end of the matter, but he remained seated in Han Li's room, and both of them fell silent.

"Is there something else you need, Fellow Daoist Shi?" Han Li asked.

"Fellow Daoist Li, I have a request, but I'm not sure it's appropriate," Shi Chuankong said in a hesitant fashion.

"Go ahead," Han Li prompted.

"Would you be able to give me another Baleful Quelling Pill? Here in the Gray Realm, I have to constantly expend a huge amount of immortal spiritual power to keep the surrounding baleful at bay, and some of it has still wormed its way into my body," Shi Chuankong said with furrowed brows.

"That's going to be problematic," Han Li sighed with a forlorn expression.

"I know these pills are extremely precious, and I'm willing to purchase them from you, so feel free to state your price, Fellow Daoist Li," Shi Chuankong hurriedly added.

"That's not the problem, Fellow Daoist Shi. It's just that I only had two of those pills left, and I used one to save you and the other one to quell my baleful qi backlash during the past few days, so I don't have any left now," Han Li sighed.

A hint of disappointment flashed through Shi Chuankong's eyes upon hearing this, and he asked, "In that case, would it be possible to refine more of these pills? Alternatively, do you have any similar pills in your possession?"

"I don't have any similar pills, but I do still have some Baleful Quelling Pill refinement ingredients left. I was planning to refine a batch a bit later, but it seems like I'll have to make haste," Han Li replied with a wry smile.

"Please sell me some pills after you've refined them. I already owe you my life, so it couldn't hurt to owe you a bit more. Once we return to the Immortal Realm, I'll make sure to compensate you with interest," Shi Chuankong promised.

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Shi. We're both stuck in the same predicament right now, so we naturally have to look out for each other," Han Li replied with a smile.

The two of them chatted for a while longer before Shi Chuankong departed, following which Han Li sat back down again and fell into deep thought.

......

As night fell, a layer of dark baleful qi rose up outside.

Han Li opened his eyes, then concealed his own aura and left his room.

He passed through a series of stone forts as he searched through the nearby area, and after pausing momentarily at another stone structure only several thousand feet away from the stone fort where he was staying, he set off once again, this time flying out of Serene Millet City.

Only after arriving at a dark river outside the city did he descend onto the ground, where he stood facing the river with his hands clasped behind his back.

Some time later, a streak of black light descended out of the sky, then faded to reveal a tall and broad figure.

"Long time no see, Dao Lord Baili," Han Li said as he turned to the newly arrived figure.

The figure's brows were tightly furrowed as he asked, "Who are you? Why have you invited me to meet you here in secret?"

"Don't be alarmed, Dao Lord Baili, it's me. We've met several times in the past, but we've never had a chance to talk to each other," Han Li replied as he revealed his true appearance, and Baili Yan observed him for a moment, following which his expression changed drastically.

"Fellow Daoist Li? What are you doing here?" he exclaimed in surprise.

"I was exploring a set of ruins and was inadvertently transported here after being sucked into a spatial vortex. Why are you also here in the Gray Realm, Dao Lord Baili?" Han Li asked.

He wasn't surprised that Baili Yan was able to identify him, given his ties with Daoist Hu Yan.

"I came here through the Reincarnation Palace," Baili Yan replied with a smile.

"Through the Reincarnation Palace? Dao Lord Baili, may I ask how the Reincarnation Palace and the Reincarnation Region are connected?" Han Li asked.

Baili Yan contemplated the question momentarily, then replied, "That's a rather difficult question to answer. The Reincarnation Palace is in the Immortal Realm, while the Reincarnation Region is in the Gray Realm, but the two share one similarity, which is that the Reincarnation Palace Master is also the Reincarnation Region Monarch. Does that make sense?"

Han Li was astonished to hear this. He had thought that the Reincarnation Region was most likely just a power in the Gray Realm that was working with the Reincarnation Palace, but he didn't think that they would be one and the same, and he certainly didn't think that the mysterious Reincarnation Palace Master would have such a strong influence in the Gray Realm as well.

"So that means you came to the Gray Realm by accident, right?" Baili Yan suddenly asked. "It's truly remarkable that you were able to survive in this completely foreign realm up to this point. No wonder Fellow Daoist Hu Yan spoke so highly of you."

"I've only been able to survive up to this point by hiding my identity, it's hardly anything to be proud of," Han Li replied with a wry smile.

"Staying in the Gray Realm is not a long-term plan. Your body will constantly be infiltrated by baleful qi, and once your immortal body completely decays, your cultivation foundation will surely be damaged, and you'll either perish or descend to become a Gray Realm being, so you should get back to the Immortal Realm as soon as possible," Baili Yan cautioned with a solemn expression.

"It's not that I don't wish to return to the Immortal Realm, I simply don't know how. Otherwise, who would be willing to stay in this place?" Han Li sighed with a wry smile.

Baili Yan's brows furrowed tightly upon hearing this, and after a long hesitation, he said, "The way to return to the Immortal Realm is a closely guarded secret of our Reincarnation Palace that isn't to be passed onto outsiders, but it was only thanks to the High Zenith Pill secured by Fellow Daoist Hu Yan in the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor that I was able to suppress my karmic flames, and you played a vital role there, so I must return the favor. Take this badge."

He flipped a hand over as he spoke, producing a round, palm-sized badge that he handed to Han Li.

"What's this?" Han Li asked, and he didn't immediately accept the badge.

"This is my Reincarnation Badge. With this badge, you'll be able to go to any monarch-level city in the Reincarnation Region to find a Reincarnation Palace branch, and they'll tell you how to return to the Immortal Realm. Of course, they'll only supply a route, whether you succeed will be up to you," Baili Yan explained.

Han Li accepted the badge before examining it for a moment to find that its material was quite special. Unlike something from the Immortal Realm, it contained pure baleful qi, and on the front side of the badge were engraved the words "Reincarnation Palace".

"This is too precious for me to accept. I presume that you only have one such badge, right? If you give it to me, how will you be able to return to the Immortal Realm yourself?" Han Li said with a shake of his head as he offered the badge back to Baili Yan.

"As I'm sure you're aware, my body has already been infiltrated by baleful qi as a result of my karmic fire remission. Thanks to the High Zenith Pill, I was able to reach a faux High Zenith Stage, and only then was I able to suppress the baleful qi to prevent complete degradation of my body. I came to the Gray Realm in order to permanently resolve this issue. If I can't do that, then there's no need for me to leave the Gray Realm," Baili Yan sighed.

"If I'm not mistaken, karmic flames and baleful qi are essentially the same thing, except they're manifested in different forms, so why have you come to the Gray Realm, a place that's rife with baleful qi, to find a solution to your karmic flames?" Han Li asked in a perplexed manner.

"The world is a very strange place sometimes. Just as you say, the Gray Realm is rife with baleful qi, but in this realm exists a thing known as a Baleful Cleansing Pond, which contains Bone Rinsing Golden Lightning, a pure yang-attribute lightning capable of eradicating all yin-attribute baleful entities.

“By soaking yourself in a Baleful Cleansing Pond, one will be cleansed of their baleful qi and also have their body and soul refined, culminating in many benefits," Baili Yan explained.

Han Li was ecstatic to hear this, and he hurriedly asked, "Do you know where this pond is in the Gray Realm?"

"Baleful Cleansing Ponds are extremely rare, and at the moment, and at the moment, I've only been able to track down a single one in the Infernal Region. It's a sacred area to all of the tribes in the region, and outsiders are barred from entry. Are you interested in Baleful Cleansing Ponds as well, Fellow Daoist Li?" Baili Yan asked

"Truth be told, I'm currently struggling with my baleful decay, and it's a constant threat that's hanging over my head," Han Li replied with a wry smile.

Baili Yan took a closer look at Han Li upon hearing this, particularly staring into his eyes for a long while, upon which a grim look appeared on his face.

"Fellow Daoist Li, your baleful decay backlash and my karmic fire remission are two different things. Unless you're in an absolutely dire situation where you have no other alternatives, I suggest you return to the Immortal Realm to find another solution to your problem," Baili Yan said.

"Why is that?" Han Li asked with slightly furrowed brows.

Chapter 711: Risk

"The Infernal Region is the most conservative and the most brutal out of the Gray Realm's three most major powers. Even beings from other regions in the Gray Realm are strictly barred from entering the region, let alone someone from the Immortal Realm like you. If you enter the Infernal Region and are discovered, your fate will be sealed," Baili Yan explained.

"I've heard of the three major powers of the Gray Realm, but I've never learned what they were. Would you be able to enlighten me, Dao Lord Baili?" Han Li asked.

"I suppose it couldn't hurt. In the Gray Realm, the regions under the command of the Reincarnation Palace Master are considered to be the radical faction, and they're proponents of combining the Gray Realm's forces to attack the Immortal Realm. The conservatives are the regions led by the Infernal Region, and they think that the Reincarnation Region is to blame for the constant invasion of the Gray Realm from the Immortal Realm's forces.

“Hence, they propose uniting the Gray Realm's forces, but they don't wish to attack the Immortal Realm. As for the third faction, that consists of the regions led by the Black Rope Region, and they wish to maintain the status quo, keeping things as they are now," Baili Yan explained.

"I see. Why is it that all of them hold such different views of the Immortal Realm?" Han Li asked.

"That's mostly decided by the makeup of the different factions. The Reincarnation Region consists primarily of Three Corpse Immortals, who hold very strong fixations on the Immortal Realm, so they naturally want to return there. The Infernal Region is mostly inhabited by native Gray Immortals who wish to defend their territory and to avoid conflict against the Immortal Realm.

“As for the Black Rope Region, most of its inhabitants are also native Gray Immortals, but they're against the autocratic rule of the Infernal Region, and they don't trust the Three Corpse Immortals of the Reincarnation Region, so they're stuck somewhere in the middle," Baili Yan explained.

"What are these Three Corpse Immortals that you speak of, Dao Lord Baili?" Han Li asked.

"Before a Great Encompassment cultivator becomes a Dao Ancestor in the Immortal Realm, they must sever three corpse souls in order to renounce all of their worldly ties, and the things that are severed are called the three corpses, most of which consist of the most deep-rooted fixations that Great Encompassment cultivators develop during their cultivation journeys.

“Upon being severed, these three corpses become enemies of the cultivators that they were severed from, and due to certain reasons, these three corpses have entered the Gray Realm to become Three Corpse Immortals," Baili Yan explained.

Han Li was still had many more questions about this subject, but right as he was about to raise them, Baili Yan waved a hand as he continued, "The severance of the three corpses is a secret and taboo subject that no Great Encompassment cultivator would be willing to speak about. I'm still far from reaching that level, so I know very little about the subject, and I won't be able to answer any other questions for you."

"So you're saying that the Infernal Region is an option that I definitely shouldn't consider?" Han Li asked with a wry smile.

"In the past, it would've been impossible for you to enter the Infernal Region. Right now, it's possible for you to go there, but your chances of finding the Baleful Cleansing Pond are next to zero, and that's not even mentioning the life-threatening danger associated with entering the pond," Baili Yan replied with a shake of his head.

"Truth be told, my baleful decay is quite special, and I've tried many methods to remedy the problem but to no avail, so perhaps the Baleful Cleansing Pond is my only hope left of reaching the High Zenith Stage. If there's a way to enter the Infernal Region, then please disclose it to me, and I'll be extremely grateful," Han Li said in a solemn fashion as he cupped his fist in a salute.

Baili Yan was silent for a long while upon hearing this, seemingly grappling with an internal conflict.

Han Li didn't try to rush him, and he merely waited patiently for a response.

"So be it. I've already told you many secrets that I shouldn't have disclosed to you, but I'm indebted to you, and I'm certain that you're not affiliated with the Heavenly Court, so I'll tell you what you want to know. I've come to Serene Millet City on this occasion to try and win over the Black Teeth Region on behalf of the Reincarnation Region.

“My objective is to secure their vote for the upcoming Three Region Conference, which will be held in Asura City of the Infernal Region," Baili Yan finally revealed after a long think.

"In that case, would I be able to accompany you to enter the Infernal Region and attend this conference?" Han Li asked as his eyes lit up slightly.

"The Three Region Conference has a very strong bearing on the Gray Realm's overall attitude toward the Immortal Realm, so it's an extremely important event. At the moment, I've been tasked with approaching many more neutral regions under the Black Rope Region, such as this Black Teeth Region, in order to try and secure an advantage for the Reincarnation Region.

“On top of that, you're not a true member of the Reincarnation Palace, so I can't bring you with me," Baili Yan replied with a shake of his head.

"I see. In that case, I think I have another solution. Seeing as you're here to win over Monarch Miao Gao, the Black Teeth Region will definitely be attending the conference, so I could just accompany them to the Infernal Region," Han Li said.

"Do you really want to go to the Infernal Region? This conference does present an opportunity, but at the same time, the tribes of the Infernal Region will be sure to bolster the defenses around the Baleful Cleansing Pond. You are taking an enormous risk here," Baili Yan cautioned in a concerned manner.

"Rest assured, Dao Lord Baili, I've made up my mind," Han Li replied with a smile and a nod.

Baili Yan could tell that there was no dissuading Han Li, so he smiled and said, "Fellow Daoist Hu Yan has always had an eye for talent, and he told me that you were destined for great things. Having said that, I never anticipated that we would be reunited under such strange circumstances."

"He's currently living the good life, while we have to toil away just to survive. Thankfully, I learned a lot of wine brewing methods from him, so I still have a decent supply of wine. Would you like to have a drink with me, Dao Lord Baili?" Han Li asked with a smile.

"Gladly!" Baili Yan replied with a wide smile of his own.

The two of them chatted with one another until it was close to daybreak, and only then did they part ways.

Shortly thereafter, Baili Yan left Serene Millet City.

That same afternoon, Miao Xiu visited Mo Guang once again, informing him that she was going to be accompanying her father to Asura City to attend the Three Region Conference.

Under Han Li's instructions, Mo Guang immediately expressed interest in this conference, requesting to accompany Miao Gao to the conference and to travel the Infernal Region along the way.

Miao Xiu didn't immediately agree to the proposal. Instead, she declared that she would inform Miao Gao of the request and leave the decision to him.

Not long after that, she returned to inform Mo Guang that Miao Gao had agreed to his proposal.

Initially, Han Li was a little taken aback, but he then quickly understood the reasoning behind Miao Gao's decision.

The Nirarbuda Region that had attacked during the Tamda Festival was a small region under the Infernal Region, indicating that the relationship between the regions leading up to the conference was a little rocky.

With Han Li's trio accompanying them on their trip to the Infernal Region, they would have an added layer of protection, which was certainly good news.

However, due to the large number of tribes attending the conference, there was still some time left until the scheduled time of assembly, and there was still close to half a year left until they were set to depart for the Infernal Region.

......

Several months later, the date of departure finally arrived.

A massive three-story louchuan was docked on the plaza in front of the monarch's manor, and it was the same one that Han Li and the others had traveled on, but the horse-like beasts drawing the louchuan were far larger than last time, and each of them had three pairs of wings instead of two.

Han Li's trio, Miao Gao, Miao Xiu, and a gray-robed hook-nosed man emerged from the entrance of the manor.

"Fellow daoists, we'll be traveling to Black Teeth City to meet up with the regional monarch, and from there, we'll be setting off to the Infernal Region together," Miao Gao said to Han Li's trio.

"We're just coming along for the trip, so we'll take your lead, Monarch Miao," Mo Guang replied with a smile, while Han Li and Shi Chuankong remained silent, continuing to play the role of obedient servants.

"This conference is an extremely important event that's taken very seriously by all regions. Please accept these guest elder badges so that your identities don't come under question during the conference," Miao Gao said as he flipped a hand over to produce three black badges.

Han Li's trio accepted the badges before expressing their gratitude, following which Mo Guang asked, "Monarch Miao, may I ask how long it'll take for us to get to Black Teeth City?"

"Black Teeth City is located in the heart of the Black Teeth Region. These six-winged Horned Horses will be a lot faster than their four-winged counterparts, but even so, it'll still take us over ten years to reach our destination," Miao Gao replied.

Mo Guang nodded in response, which Han Li's brows furrowed ever so slightly upon hearing this.

He had only been in the Gray Realm for several years, yet his body had already accumulated enough baleful qi to stir up unrest in his immortal acupoints. If he couldn't find a way to resolve this problem, then a journey of over ten years was going to be a real struggle for him.

"Let's all board the ship, everyone," Miao Gao said as he made an inviting hand gesture to Mo Guang, and only after Han Li's trio had boarded the louchuan did he also do the same.

The gray-robed young man made his way over the front of the ship before making a hand seal, and the Horned Horses immediately took flight.

Miao Xiu arranged rooms for Han Li's trio to stay in, and they were still the same rooms that they had stayed in last time.

As soon as Han Li entered his room, he immediately closed the door and set up several layers of restrictions, then swept a sleeve through the air to summon Daoist Xie, following which he instructed, "Please keep a lookout for me, Brother Xie."

Daoist Xie nodded in response, and Han Li conjured up a door of silver light, then stepped through it into the Flower Branch domain.

By staying in the Flower Branch domain, his body wouldn't be in contact with the baleful qi in the outside world, thereby significantly slowing down the accumulation of baleful qi in his body.

After sitting down with his legs crossed in a secret chamber, Han Li flipped a hand over to produce a pile of Baleful Quelling Pill refinement ingredients.

He had collected many of the supplementary ingredients required to refine Baleful Quelling Pills, and now that he had come into possession of Profound Zoysia Crystal and Bitter Ornament Flowers, he could finally begin refining some more Baleful Quelling Pills.

After arranging all of the ingredients, Han Li didn't immediately commence his pill refinement. Instead, he flipped a hand over to produce a map of the Black Teeth Region, and he traced a finger along the route between Serene Millet City and Black Teeth City, following which a faint smile appeared on his face.

After that, he stowed the map away and closed his eyes.

Chapter 712: Twin-headed Fox Saber

Half a year flew by in a flash.

One night, Han Li emerged from his Flower Branch domain in his room on the louchuan.

Daoist Xie was seated on the ground with its legs crossed, and it immediately rose to its feet at the sight of Han Li.

"Please continue to keep a lookout, Brother Xie, and inform me right away if someone comes to visit," Han Li said to Daoist Xie, then made a hand seal before flying out of his room as a blurry shadow.

The restrictions in the room opened up a sliver on their own to allow him to fly through them, and Han Li emerged into the darkness outside.

There were several fluorescent white stones embedded onto the body of the louchuan outside, but the white light that they were giving off was very faint, and it failed to illuminate the darkness.

There was not a single person on the deck of the louchuan with the exception of the gray-robed man, who was piloting the ship.

There was a black restriction around the louchuan that was flashing with misty black light, and Han Li took a glance at the gray-robed man, then cast his gaze toward the black restriction before flying toward it.

In the instant that he came into contact with the restriction, his body transformed into a cloud of faint mist that quickly passed through the black restriction without causing any disturbance.

The mist then converged to reform Han Li's body, and he descended rapidly, quickly reaching the ground below.

Down below was a vast grassland that was still part of the Six Moon Grassland, and the ground was undulating slightly in a wavy fashion.

Han Li flipped a hand over to summon his map of the Six Moon Grassland while releasing his spiritual sense throughout the surrounding area, and an elated look quickly appeared on his face as he flew away in a certain direction.

Close to an hour later, a swamp that was filled with bubbling black mud appeared up ahead, and gusts of freezing wind were occasionally rising up from the swamp's depths.

There was a cloud of gray mist hanging in the air, and it was giving off an acrid, sulfurous odor.

"This is the place," Han Li murmured to himself as he flew deeper into the swamp without any hesitation.

This was the boundless swamp in the Six Moon Grassland, the place where Bitter Ornament Herbs could be found.

The boundless swamp just so happened to be on the way from Serene Millet City to Black Teeth City, presenting Han Li with the opportunity to pick some Bitter Ornament Herbs.

Once he began refining Baleful Quelling Pills, it would take two to three years to complete the process, so he had held off this entire time.

After taking a deep breath, he sped up a little more, quickly flying deeper into the boundless swamp.

The glacial qi here was abnormally abundant, and the air temperature was plummeting rapidly.

Han Li slowly scoured the surrounding area with his spiritual sense, and his eyes soon lit up as he flew in a certain direction, then descended in front of a small mound of soil.

Next to the mound of soil were three Bitter Ornament Herbs, each of which was around a foot tall.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face as he swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of azure light, yet right as the burst of azure light was about to uproot the three Bitter Ornament Herbs, a black shadow suddenly darted out from the side, pouncing at Han Li's left foot at an incredible speed.

A dull thump rang out as an azure light barrier emerged over Han Li's foot, keeping the black shadow at bay and sending it flying back.

At the same time, a streak of azure swordlight shot out of Han Li's sleeve to slice the black shadow into two.

As it turned out, the shadow was a small black snake with a triangular fleshy growth on its head. Its mouth was filled with hooked teeth, and even though it had been sliced into two, it continued to struggle and writhe on the ground instead of perishing right away.

Han Li paid no further heed to the snake as he uprooted the three Bitter Ornament Herbs before stowing them away, then continued onward.

A few minutes later, his eyes lit up as he flew over to a pond, within which were two more Bitter Ornament Herbs.

He stowed those two Bitter Ornament Herbs away as well, then continued his search.

Close to a day flew by in a flash, and the sky was beginning to brighten.

Han Li flew out of a giant crater that was several thousand feet in size deep within the swamp, and he was looking rather weary, but there was an excited look in his eyes.

His search had yielded close to a hundred Bitter Ornament Herbs, which was a massive haul.

With so many Bitter Ornament Herbs, he wouldn't have to worry about running out again, and once he returned to the True Immortal Realm, these Bitter Ornament Herbs would net him an enormous profit.

There were still many more Bitter Ornament Herbs in the swamp, but he had already spent an entire night here, so he couldn't keep searching.

Han Li took a deep breath, and the weariness on his face faded a little. He took a moment to ascertain the louchuan's location, then began to set off in that direction.

However, he wasn't able to get very far before a resounding boom suddenly rang out in his mind, and his entire body began to tremble uncontrollably.

A sense of nausea began to rise up from all of his internal organs, and all of the blood in his body began to gush toward his heart.

He hurriedly channeled his cultivation arts to suppress the unrest in his body, and he was just about to examine his surroundings when all of the discomfort that he was experiencing suddenly disappeared, as if it had been nothing more than a figment of his imagination.

He was left feeling a little dazed as he stopped in his tracks, then began to examine his surroundings with his spiritual sense, but didn't discover anything amiss.

A contemplative look appeared on his face as he slowly flew back in the same direction that he had come from, and it didn't take long before the sense of nausea appeared again.

Han Li's brows were furrowed tightly as he suppressed the sense of discomfort and scoured the landscape down below with both his eyes and his spiritual sense, and his gaze quickly fell upon a pond.

That was the source of his discomfort.

Han Li flew through the area around the pond for a while, and he discovered that the sense of nausea only arose whenever he entered an area within a radius of around two hundred to three hundred feet of the pond.

The surface of the pond was very placid, and after some hesitation, Han Li was unable to suppress his curiosity as he dove into the pond.

The pond wasn't very deep, and he was quickly able to reach the bottom, which was quite flat, with a pile of loose rocks on the ground.

These rocks all differed in shape and size, but they were all black in color, and there were some strange patterns on their surfaces, indicating that they were no ordinary rocks.

At the bottom of the pond, the nausea that Han Li was experiencing had intensified even further, and that pile of black rocks was the root cause.

All of a sudden, he swept a leg through the water, releasing a crescent-shaped burst of azure light that struck the pile of black rocks, scattering them to reveal what was underneath.

As it turned out, there was a black saber plunged diagonally into the ground beneath the rocks.

The saber was entirely black in color and resembled a piece of charred wood. It was impossible to tell what type of material it had been forged from, and there was a fearsome-looking twin-headed fox engraved onto the saber's guard.

The blade of the saber was quite large and slightly curved, and there was a dark red line running all the way down the length of the saber from its hilt to its tip.

A tremendous, nauseating aura was emanating from the saber, and it was several times stronger than when the saber had been buried under the pile of rocks.

Han Li's complexion paled significantly as he took a step backward, and only after conjuring up a golden light barrier around himself did the sense of nausea abate somewhat.

His brows furrowed slightly at the sight of the black saber.

Ever since he had come to the Gray Realm, everything here had been either black, white, or gray, and the dark red line on the saber was the first time that he had seen any other color in this realm.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he released his spiritual sense toward the saber, and in the instant that the two came into contact with each other, his spiritual sense was instantly devoured by a burst of cold power.

Han Li's complexion paled even further as a burst of excruciating pain shot through his mind, and it felt as if a chunk of flesh had been torn off his body.

At the same time, a burst of black light emerged over the saber, and a series of twisted human faces appeared within the black light before letting loose deranged roars.

A burst of extremely evil power was surging out of the saber, running along that wisp of spiritual sense to directly infiltrate Han Li's mind.

His clear and pure consciousness instantly turned dark and gray, and threads of black light emerged before piercing directly toward his soul.

A sense of extreme nausea welled up in his body, making him feel as if all of his organs were revolting against him, and his senses also became very muddled.

Han Li dry wretched as his expression changed drastically, and he hurriedly darted back in retreat while releasing his time law powers with all his might, allowing him to keep this burst of evil power at bay.

Before long, his spiritual sense had returned to normal, and he was panting heavily as he continued to dart back in retreat, only stopping once he was as far away from the saber as possible.

An indignant roar rang out from within the burst of evil power, and it slowly retreated back into the black saber.

What the hell is this thing? Not only is it able to devour spiritual sense, it can directly attack one's soul as well!

Even with Han Li's immense powers, he had almost fallen prey to that burst of evil power.

Right at this moment, a burst of white light emerged from the twin-headed fox on the saber's guard, and it instantly spread over the entire saber, following which an intrigued voice rang out.

"I didn't think that anyone in the Gray Realm would be able to master the laws of time!"

The black light emanating from the saber struggled briefly in an indignant fashion, but was ultimately suppressed by the white light and completely faded.

Immediately thereafter, an indistinct white humanoid figure emerged from the twin-headed fox. The humanoid figure resembled a middle-aged man, and he was observing Han Li with an intrigued expression.

The man was wearing a white robe, and he was looking a little disheveled, but he was clearly quite handsome.

Chapter 713: Setting a Trap

A hint of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes at the sight of the white-robed projection.

The man struck him with a sense of familiarity, but he couldn't recall exactly where he had seen this man before.

"Ah, I see, so you're a human cultivator from the Immortal Realm. How courageous of you to have ventured into the Gray Realm," the white-robed man remarked with a smile.

Han Li was astonished to hear this, and he immediately asked, "Who are you?"

His disguise was near-perfect, yet this man had managed to see through him in an instant.

Even though he had emerged from the black saber, the white-robed man didn't seem to harbor any ill will.

"Who am I? That's a good question. You can call me Shi Qinghou," the white-robed man replied with a faint smile.

"Could it be that you're the artifact spirit of this saber?" Han Li asked.

At the same time, he was thinking back over all of the Gray Realm scriptures that he had read, but he couldn't recall such a name, and he wasn't sure if he was being told the man's real name.

A hint of resentment flashed through Shi Qinghou's eyes upon hearing this, but it then immediately faded, and he replied, "Artifact spirit? I suppose so."

Han Li had noticed the minute change in Shi Qinghou's expression, but he made no comment about it.

Right as he was about to ask another question, Shi Qinghou raised a hand to stop him and said, "You've already asked me two questions, surely it's my turn to ask you some questions now."

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, then replied, "I suppose that would only be fair. Go ahead."

"My questions are similar to the ones that you just asked me. Who are you, and why are you here?"

A sharp gleam suddenly appeared in Shi Qinghou's eyes as he spoke, and a fearsome aura erupted out of his body.

The black light emanating from the saber also brightened significantly, and a giant twin-headed demon fox projection appeared within it, glowering intently at Han Li as if it were threatening to tear him to shreds.

Han Li remained completely unfazed by Shi Qinghou's display of intimidation, and he replied, "My name is Li Han, and I came to the Gray Realm purely by accident. I was sucked into a spatial vortex while exploring a secret area in the Immortal Realm, and that's how I ended up here."

Shi Qinghou's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and it seemed that he was trying to judge whether Han Li's words were trustworthy or not.

Shi Qinghou observed Han Li for a long while before finally replying, "I don't know if you're telling the truth, but it doesn't look to me like you were sent here by Yin Chengquan. In that case, we are not enemies."

At the same time, he swept a sleeve through the air, and the fearsome aura emanating from his body faded, as did the black light being released by the ancient saber.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon hearing this. He had no idea who this Yin Chengyuan was, but at the moment, he had more pressing questions to ask.

"I've answered two of your questions, it's my turn again to ask the questions. What is this black saber?" Han Li asked.

"You don't know what this is? I suppose that makes sense, considering you dared to place your spiritual sense in direct contact with it. That's further confirmation that you weren't sent by Yin Chengquan," Shi Qinghou replied as he nodded to himself, following which a contemplative look appeared on his face.

"You still haven't answered my question," Han Li reminded.

"This blade is called the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber, and the souls of all of the people that it kills are eternally trapped within it, unable to enter the cycle of reincarnation. It's claimed countless lives up to this point, and it's accumulated a tremendous amount of baleful qi and resentment as a result.

“You've already experienced that firsthand yourself, so I'm sure I don't need to tell you just how fearsome this blade is," Shi Qinghou explained.

It sounds like this is an extremely formidable treasure...

Han Li had many more questions that he wanted to ask, but he held off from doing so as it was Shi Qinghou's turn.

"I can make use of your time law powers. How about we make a deal?" Shi Qinghou suddenly proposed.

"What kind of deal?" Han Li asked as his eyes narrowed slightly.

"Rest assured, I bear no ill will toward you. The deal that I'm proposing will be beneficial for both of us," Shi Qinghou assured with a smile, then swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of white light that vanished into the ground near the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber in a flash.

The ground immediately began buzzing, and the earth in a radius of over a hundred feet around the saber was slowly elevated by about half a foot to form a round stone platform.

The mud on the platform was quickly shaken off to reveal the gray stone material underneath, and there were countless black patterns engraved onto the surface of the entire stone platform to form a complex array.

Bursts of inky black light were rising up from the array before rapidly flowing outward in all directions, accompanied by harrowing shrieks and screams.

The Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber was plunged into the center of the array, and it seemed to have been sealed there.

A hint of surprise appeared in Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

He had just scoured the area with his spiritual sense, yet he had completely failed to detect this array.

In complete contrast with the arrays of the Immortal Realm, this was a restriction that was unique to the Gray Realm. Han Li had read some books regarding the arrays of the Gray Realm, but his understanding of the subject was still quite rudimentary, so he was unable to fully comprehend this array.

Even so, he could still sense that the black array was extremely profound, and the restrictive powers within it were constantly intertwining and changing. It was clear to him that this restriction was not inferior to any that he had ever seen before.

"This is a sealing array. You're from the True Immortal Realm, so you may not be able to make sense of it, but the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber and I are currently being sealed here by this array. My request is very simple: pull the saber out of the array. Of course, I won't ask you to do this for no compensation.

“I am able to control this Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber, and if you can get me out of here, I can stay by your side to assist you in battle for the next one hundred thousand years," Shi Qinghou said with a serious expression.

"You want me to pull the saber out of this array? I'm afraid you think far too highly of me. This is an extremely powerful restriction, and I certainly have no chance of breaking it," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

"Of course it would be impossible solely through your own efforts, but I've been trapped in this saber for countless years, and through the saber, I've managed to refine much of the array, so I can disable most of its power for you," Shi Qinghou said with a smile.

"In that case, I can consider it, but I'm assuming there must be other obstacles to pulling the saber out of the array. Otherwise, surely you would've already freed yourself long ago," Han Li mused in a contemplative manner.

"Of course. I can disable most of the array's power, but at the very minimum, High Zenith Stage power will be required to pull out the saber. On top of that, while I'm suppressing the array, I won't be able to divert any attention to suppressing the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber, so you'll be struck by backlash from the boundless resentment within the saber as soon as you come into contact with it, and only the three paramount laws will be able to protect you.

“The only reason why I'm proposing this deal to you is because you've mastered the laws of time," Shi Qinghou replied with a nod.

Han Li lowered his head in contemplation upon hearing this, and he was silent for a long while.

"What do you think of my proposal?" Shi Qinghou asked, trying to prompt a response from Han Li.

"While it's true that this is a mutually beneficial deal, I'm afraid you'll have to find someone else. My apologies," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

Shi Qinghou's expression instantly darkened slightly upon seeing this, but Han Li paid no heed to this as he turned to depart.

"Hold on a second, do you know what the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber entails? With this saber, your powers will be elevated by at least tenfold! I can see that you're at the pinnacle of the Golden Immortal Stage. With my help, you'll be unmatched across the Great Encompassment Stage! Is that enough to change your mind?" Shi Qinghou asked.

"This is a very tantalizing offer, but the saber is ultimately under your control instead of mine. On top of that, how do I know if you're telling the truth or not? I've only recently arrived in the Gray Realm, and I don't wish to take any undue risks," Han Li replied in a stoic fashion.

Shi Qinghou's expression eased slightly upon hearing this, and he said, "So you're harboring doubts about my integrity. I suppose that's only normal. What do I have to do to make you believe me?"

Han Li considered the question for a moment, then replied, "If you want me to trust you, then you have to agree to two of my conditions."

"Go ahead," Shi Qinghou prompted.

"Firstly, I want to know your identity. I'm assuming that you're not the artifact spirit of this Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber. On top of that, I want to know who Yin Chengquan is and what vendetta exists between the two of you," Han Li said.

"Why do you want to know all of this?" Shi Qinghou asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"Truth be told, I can free you from this place, but I don't want to attract any trouble in the process. If you don't clarify these matters to me, then I won't agree to your proposal," Han Li replied.

A complex look appeared on Shi Qinghou's face upon hearing this, and he was silent for a moment before replying, "Alright, if you insist, I can answer your questions, but let me warn you that knowing too much isn't a good thing."

"That may be so, but I'd still like to hear your answer," Han Li said with a smile.

Chapter 714: Pulling Out the Saber

"Why do I feel like I've fallen for a ruse? So be it, I'll tell you what you want to know. It's true that I'm not the artifact spirit of this saber. Instead, I was previously but one of the souls trapped in the saber after I met my demise to it. However, thanks to my lofty cultivation base, my soul wasn't completely assimilated by the boundless resentful energy within the saber.

“Instead, I was able to glean some of the saber's secrets, and that allowed me to survive in this form up to this point," Shi Qinghou revealed.

"Who were you before you were killed, and what was your cultivation base?" Han Li asked as a hint of astonishment flashed through his eyes.

At the moment, his spiritual sense was no weaker than that of late-High Zenith cultivators like Su Liu and Bi She, but even he wasn't able to ward off the boundless resentment within the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber.

However, not only was Shi Qinghou able to do this, he was even able to gain control over the saber, and that was something that Han Li had to be wary of.

"Don't push your luck, you insolent brat! Do you want me to tell you my entire life story and all of the cultivation arts I've used up to this point? I require your help, but that doesn't mean that you can ask for whatever you want from me!" Shi Qinghou said in a cold voice.

Han Li hurriedly cupped his fist in an apologetic salute as he said, "My apologies, Senior. All you have to do is answer the three questions that I raised earlier."

Due to his cautious and inquisitive personality, he reflexively wanted to find out more about Shi Qinghou, but in his haste to do so, he had inadvertently overstepped some boundaries.

Shi Qinghou gave a cold harrumph before replying, "Before I was killed, I was the monarch of a certain region in the Gray Realm, and the person who killed me was Yin Chengquan, the monarch of the Infernal Region."

After revealing all of this, he closed his eyes, unwilling to divulge any more information.

A contemplative look appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing these three answers, and he was silent for a long while before continuing, "Alright, my first condition has been met. My second condition is that I want to set up some restrictions in your body to use as leverage."

"That's fine," Shi Qinghou agreed without any hesitation, not even bothering to ask what type of restrictions Han Li was going to plant in his body.

A hint of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes, but he then quickly composed himself as he cupped his fist toward Shi Qinghou in an apologetic salute.

"Please pardon my intrusion."

Shi Qinghou drifted out of the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber over to Han Li, who began to chant an incantation, then bit through the tip of his own tongue before spitting out a ball of blood essence.

The blood essence began to squirm like a living creature at his behest, quickly transforming into countless peculiar crimson runes.

At this moment, Han Li's glabella was flashing with translucent light, and several translucent threads shot out from within before fusing as one with the crimson runes, following which all of them vanished into Shi Qinghou's glabella.

A series of crimson patterns instantly emerged on Shi Qinghou's glabella, and they quickly spread over the rest of his body in the blink of an eye.

However, these crimson runes only flashed a few times before fading away, and it was as if nothing had ever happened.

"It's done," Han Li declared.

The restriction that he had just set up was a special secret technique that specifically targeted the soul. It was quite similar to the restriction that he had planted in Mo Guang's body, but on this occasion, he was using his own blood essence as a medium to tie himself and Shi Qinghou together to a certain extent.

With this restriction in place, he would immediately know if Shi Qinghou were plotting against him, but at the same time, he couldn't just harm Shi Qinghou for no reason, either.

This was quite a fair and equal restriction, and it was the ease with which Shi Qinghou had agreed to his conditions that convinced him to plant such a restriction.

"I've already satisfied both of your conditions, so our deal is in effect now, right?" Shi Qinghou asked.

"That's right," Han Li replied without any hesitation.

A faint smile appeared on Shi Qinghou's face upon hearing this, and he flew back into the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber as a streak of white light.

All of a sudden, incredibly bright white radiance erupted out of the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber, following which strands of fur-like white light shot forth through the air in all directions.

The surrounding black restriction seemed to have sensed the impending threat, and it also lit up before releasing plumes of black clouds that converged toward the strands of white light.

A fierce clash ensued between the two, and black and white light flashed erratically, with neither one able to get the better of the other.

Right at this moment, a quiet incantation rang out from within the saber, following which it shuddered as bursts of liquid-like white light surged forth before fusing into the stone platform down below along the blade of the saber.

The black patterns on the array quickly turned white, and the clouds of black light immediately began to dim, following which they were pierced through by the strands of white light before vanishing altogether.

The light emanating from the black restriction parted down either side to create an opening that was just wide enough to fit a person, but due to the fact that all of the white light was dedicated to counteracting the restriction, the white light emanating from the saber itself had become quite sparse, and plumes of black mist were beginning to rise up from the saber.

"Pull out the saber! Hurry! I won't be able to keep this up for long!" Shi Qinghou said in an urgent voice.

At this moment, Han Li's entire body was enveloped in radiant golden light, forming a suit of golden armor around him.

He immediately sprang into action without hesitation, shooting through the opening in the black restriction as a streak of golden light before arriving beside the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber and grabbing onto its hilt.

The black light radiating from the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber reared up while spreading outward in all directions to form a dense black halo.

Han Li's right arm and half of his entire body were swallowed up by the black halo, and a burst of incredibly formidable resentful power instantly flooded into his mind along his arm.

However, at this moment, his entire body was enveloped within time law powers, so as soon as the burst of resentful power entered his body, it was severely repressed, only able to advance at an extremely sluggish rate.

Even though the burst of resentful power hadn't yet infiltrated Han Li's mind, it was so immense that Han Li still felt his consciousness churning violently.

He gritted his teeth against the intense discomfort as he channeled all of his immortal spiritual power while hoisting his arm upward in a forceful motion.

A burst of tremendous force erupted out of his arms, causing the nearby space to ripple incessantly.

The entire stone platform shuddered violently, as did all of the black light radiating from the array, and the connective point between the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber and the stone platform was buzzing and trembling violently, but the saber remained firmly in place.

Han Li immediately made a hand seal upon seeing this, and a string of true spirit projections flew out of his body in rapid succession, then flew around him momentarily before vanishing back into his body.

A resounding boom rang out as radiant purplish-golden light erupted out of his body, and he instantly transformed into a purplish-golden devilish deity.

His aura instantly swelled drastically, causing the entire pond to tremble violently, and the devilish deity's eyes widened as it let loose a low roar and tugged on the saber with all its might.

An explosive boom rang out as the connective point between the saber and the stone platform shattered, leaving a huge hole in its wake.

The devilish deity flew back with the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber held firmly in its grasp before crashing into the side of the pond.

With the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber drawn, the black light emanating from the restriction on the stone platform quickly faded, following which the stone platform itself also disintegrated into a pile of loose rocks.

A ball of white light flew out of the stone platform before vanishing into the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber, and the black light emanating from the saber was instantly suppressed.

Shi Qinghou emerged from the saber amid a flash of white light, and his eyes were glowing with elation as he roared, "Finally, after being trapped in this godforsaken place for so many years, I'm finally free! Yin Chengquan, you'll get what's coming to you for what you've done to me!"

Meanwhile, the devilish deity rapidly reverted back to Han Li's human form, and it observed Shi Qinghou in silence without disrupting him.

Shi Qinghou threw his head back and let loose a thunderous roar, venting all of the fury and indignation that had been accumulating within him for countless years.

Some time later, the excitement on his face slowly faded, and he turned to Han Li with a smile as he said, "My apologies, I've been trapped here for so long that I was unable to suppress my excitement upon being freed."

"It's fine, I can empathize with how you must be feeling," Han Li replied.

"Now that I'm free, let's get out of here. We caused quite a commotion just now, so someone could be coming," Shi Qinghou said.

Han Li nodded in response, then turned his gaze to the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber in his hand. Even though Shi Qinghou had suppressed the resentful energy within the saber, it was still giving off a tremendous aura, and he was trying to think of a way to suppress its aura as well.

Shi Qinghou could see what Han Li was concerned about, and he said, "Those black crystals are Mythical Black Jade, and they're very effective at concealing baleful qi and resentful energy. Make a scabbard out of the material, and you'll be able to conceal most of the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber's aura."

Chapter 715: Scabbard

Han Li turned to the pile of rocks that he had kicked aside earlier upon hearing this.

He had read about Mythical Black Jade in some of the scriptures that he had collected. It was an extremely precious type of Gray Realm ore, and just as Shi Qinghou proclaimed, it was indeed able to conceal baleful auras.

However, there were no illustrations of physical descriptions of the material in any of the scriptures, so Han Li wasn't able to identify it.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of azure light, which forced back the surrounding water in the pond before also sweeping up the black crystals and carrying them back to him.

He then opened his mouth to release a ball of azure flames to refine the material.

The Essence Fire Raven was still in a state of slumber at the moment, so he could only use his nascent flame for this purpose.

"Hold on, that flame of yours is filled with immortal spiritual power, and it'll be very harmful to the Mythical Black Jade," Shi Qinghou hurriedly said as he raised a hand to stop Han Li, then flicked a finger through the air, and all of the nearby baleful qi instantly converged toward the azure nascent flame before fusing into it.

As a result, the azure flame quickly turned gray, and a hint of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

The baleful qi and the azure nascent flame didn't conflict with each other at all. Instead, they were perfectly fused together, and this degree of baleful qi manipulation was beyond what Han Li was currently capable of.

Han Li took a glance at Shi Qinghou, then made a hand seal, and the gray flame instantly enveloped the Mythical Black Jade to produce a sizzling and popping sound.

Close to an hour later, the Mythical Black Jade finally melted into a ball of black liquid, and the liquid slowly elongated to form a black scabbard of the same size as the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber at Han Li's behest.

Shi Qinghou pointed a finger at the scabbard, and all of the nearby baleful qi converged once again forming strands of gray light that fused into a scabbard.

A series of patterns instantly appeared on the scabbard's surface, and Han Li guided it onto the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber.

The resentful energy emanating from the saber was instantly significantly suppressed.

"Thank you for your guidance, Fellow Daoist Shi," Han Li said as he examined the scabbard.

"There's no need to thank me over such trivial matters. I've exerted myself quite severely from suppressing the array earlier, so I'll have to rest and recuperate for a while. You can contact me if you need my help in battle," Shi Qinghou said in a rather cold manner, then flew back into the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber as a streak of white light.

Han Li wasn't fazed by Shi Qinghou's cold demeanor. In fact, it instilled within him a sense of reassurance.

He swept a sleeve through the air to release a string of black and white talismans, then cast a series of incantation seals into the talismans.

The talismans instantly transformed into bursts of black and white light that enveloped the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber to form a black and white cocoon of light.

With this additional restriction in place, the baleful qi emanating from the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber was suppressed even further, to the point that it was barely even detectable anymore.

Han Li gave a pleased nod upon seeing this, and he stowed the black and white cocoon of light away, then flew out of the pond.

At this point, the suns had already well and truly risen, and Han Li took a moment to ascertain the louchuan's location, then set off as a streak of azure light.

Around half a day later, he caught up to the louchuan, then snuck into his own room without being detected.

"Welcome back, Fellow Daoist Han," Daoist Xie said as it rose to its feet.

"Has anything abnormal happened during my absence?" Han Li asked.

"No, but Shi Chuankong did come to visit once. He saw the restrictions around the room, so he left after leaving a voice transmission talisman," Daoist Xie said as it pulled out a black voice transmission talisman.

Han Li accepted the talisman, then injected his spiritual sense into it before quickly crushing it.

Shi Chuankong had come to ask him about the Baleful Quelling Pills.

It was clear that Shi Chuankong was struggling with the baleful-qi-rich environment of the Gray Realm, so he was going to refine a batch of Baleful Quelling Pills as soon as possible.

He flipped a hand over to produce a white voice transmission talisman, then spoke briefly into it before releasing it, sending it flying toward Shi Chuankong's room as a streak of white light.

After that, he conjured up an entrance to the Flower Branch domain, then turned to Daoist Xie as he said, "I have to go into seclusion for some time, Brother Xie. Please continue to keep a lookout."

"No problem," Daoist Xie replied with a nod, and Han Li entered the Flower Branch space.

He sat down in his secret chamber to meditate, priming himself into the best possible condition before commencing his pill refinement.

Over two hours later, his eyes sprang open, and he briefly ran over the Baleful Quelling Pill refinement method in his mind, then swept a sleeve through the air to release a silver cauldron.

After that, he released a burst of green nascent flames out of his mouth to envelop the cauldron.

His nascent flame was a little weaker than his Flame of Essence, but it was still more than enough for Baleful Quelling Pill refinement purposes.

The spirit patterns on the silver cauldron quickly lit up, and the entire cauldron gradually turned a red hot color.

Han Li made a hand seal to release a ball of azure light, which picked up a green spirit plant before transferring it into the cauldron.

The spirit plant quickly melted into a ball of light green spirit liquid, following which another ingredient was tossed into the cauldron.

......

Several years flew by in a flash.

Inside the secret chamber, the silver cauldron was still enveloped by azure flames, and its lid was trembling and rattling incessantly.

Han Li was staring intently at the cauldron, and a short while later, he suddenly thrust a palm forward, sending a burst of azure light flying into the cauldron.

The green flames around the cauldron instantly faded, while its lid sprang up before falling to the side.

A spicy aroma wafted through the air, and there were five Baleful Quelling Pills laying inside the cauldron.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he plucked the five pills out of the cauldron before storing them into a black jade vial, then stowed the silver cauldron away as well.

Over the past few years, he had refined a total of close to twenty Baleful Quelling Pills. Funnily enough, he still had some Profound Zoysia Crystals and Bitter Ornament Herbs leftover, but he had run out of all of the supplementary ingredients, something that he had never anticipated before.

However, this batch of pills would be enough for quite some time.

In the next instant, Han Li vanished from the spot before reappearing in his room on the ship, and Daoist Xie rose to its feet upon seeing this.

"Brother Xie, you've been out here this entire time, has your body been affected by the baleful qi here at all?" Han Li suddenly asked.

"My body is that of a puppet, so it's not easily infiltrated by external forces. On top of that, my body contains the power of lightning, so the baleful qi here has no effect on me," Daoist Xie replied in a calm manner.

"That's good to hear. Has anyone come to visit me during my seclusion?" Han Li asked.

Daoist Xie offered no response, merely pulling out a stack of voice transmission talismans.

Han Li accepted the talismans before examining their contents one by one, upon which he discovered that almost all of them were from Shi Chuankong, and there was also one from Mo Guang, asking Han Li about how he should proceed.

Han Li emerged from his room, then flipped a hand over to produce a voice transmission talisman, which he spoke into briefly before releasing.

The voice transmission talisman shot forth through the air before vanishing into Mo Guang's room in a flash, following which he strode over to Shi Chuankong's room, then made a hand seal to release a burst of white light, which vanished into the black restriction around the room.

The restriction around the room quickly began to ripple before fading away, following which the door swung open.

"You've finally come out of seclusion, Fellow Daoist Li. Please come in," Shi Chuankong said in a slightly hoarse voice.

Han Li raised an eyebrow as he entered the room, following which the door swung shut, and the black restriction was restored.

The room was rather dim, and at this moment, Shi Chuankong was seated in a corner of the room with the silver lute that he had secured from the True Mantra Sect ruins hovering above his head.

Hovering beside the lute was a silver badge that was riddled with silver star designs, and it was the other spatial-attribute immortal treasure that he had secured from the entrance of the True Mantra Sect ruins.

The two spatial immortal treasures were releasing bursts of silver light that formed a spherical light barrier around Shi Chuankong, and there were also numerous gray array flags hovering around him, forming a complex array that conjured up yet another silver light barrier outside of the spherical one.

Shi Chuankong was seated at the center of all of the restrictions, looking in horrible condition. His hair was disheveled, his eyes were gleaming red, and baleful qi was swirling around his body, giving him the appearance of someone on the verge of insanity.

"What happened to you, Fellow Daoist Shi?" Han Li asked with a startled expression.

"My baleful decay was triggered by the baleful qi here. I didn't anticipate the Gray Realm to be so abundant with baleful qi. I've tried everything to keep it at bay, but I'm still unable to completely shut it out," Shi Chuankong replied with a wry smile.

Chapter 716: Arriving at Black Teeth City

"You're enduring your baleful decay as well, Fellow Daoist Shi?" Han Li asked with a surprised expression.

"It actually began several hundred years ago, but I've been suppressing it up to this point using secret techniques. In any case, that's not important. Have you managed to refine any Baleful Quelling Pills, Fellow Daoist Li?" Shi Chuankong asked with a hopeful expression.

Han Li offered no response, merely flipping a hand over to produce a black pill.

Shi Chuankong's eyes instantly lit up as he rose to his feet, and a burst of silver light shot out of the restrictions around him, transforming to a silver hand that grabbed onto the pill.

Han Li made no effort to stop him, allowing the silver hand to close itself around the pill.

Shi Chuankong was just about to withdraw the silver hand when he suddenly stopped what he was doing.

The baleful qi around him was rippling violently due to his excitement, but he still turned to Han Li as he asked, "Fellow Daoist Li, what would you like in exchange for this Baleful Quelling Pill?"

"We can discuss that another time. Right now, the top priority is for you to take the pill and suppress the baleful qi in your body. Otherwise, at this rate, it won't be long before you land all of us in a world of trouble," Han Li replied with a faint smile.

Shi Chuankong cupped his fist in a grateful salute toward Han Li, following which the silver hand shot back into the silver restrictions.

At the same time, a series of spatial vortexes emerged around Shi Chuankong, while the silver restrictions also lit up significantly, and he was completely concealed within them.

Han Li raised an eyebrow upon seeing this, and instead of departing, he sat down in another corner of the room with his legs crossed.

Close to a year passed by in a flash.

All of a sudden, the radiant silver light in the corner of the room faded, and Shi Chuankong was revealed.

At this point, the unrest in his aura had already subsided, and it seemed that he had made a complete recovery.

"Thank you, Fellow Daoist Li. If it wasn't for your Baleful Quelling Pills, the Gray Realm would've most likely become my final resting place," Shi Chuakong said as he cupped his fist in a grateful salute.

"It's only right for me to help an ally when we're both in such an inhospitable place," Han Li replied with a smile as he rose to his feet.

Shi Chuankong took a glance at Han Li, then hesitated momentarily before flipping a hand over to produce a rectangular jade box, which he opened to reveal a black spirit plant.

The spirit plant was giving off a peculiar aroma that instantly struck one with a sense of alertness, and Han Li's eyes immediately lit up as he identified the spirit plant.

"If I'm not mistaken, it seems like you've also cultivated the Spirit Refinement Technique, so I'm sure you're in need of this Myriad Soul Herb, Fellow Daoist Li. This is the same one that I purchased from that auction all those years ago, and you can have it exchange for that Baleful Quelling Pill," Shi Chuankong said as he offered the jade box to Han Li.

Han Li took a long glance at Shi Chuankong, then accepted the jade box as he replied, "This is indeed something that I need, so I won't refuse it."

"Many people directly consume Myriad Soul Herbs for its spirit sense enhancement effect, but if you refine it into Myriad Soul Pills, the effect will actually be superior," Shi Chuankong said.

"Myriad Soul Pills?" Han Li asked with a surprised expression.

Even though Han Li had failed to secure the Myriad Soul Herb during the Jade Gathering City auction, he had conducted some research into the spirit plant after the event, but there were no records mentioning that the spirit plant could be refined into pills.

"The Myriad Soul Pill is something that a pill refinement master of our Devil Realm developed only several million years ago, and the recipe is yet to make it to the True Immortal Realm, so it's no surprise that you don't know about it," Shi Chuankong explained as he summoned a jade slip before also offering it to Han Li.

Han Li hesitated momentarily before accepting the jade slip, and after examining the recipe inside, a hint of elation quickly appeared on his face.

The ingredients required for the Myriad Soul Pill weren't particularly rare, and he should be able to easily collect the ingredients upon returning to the True Immortal Realm.

Furthermore, according to the pill recipe, the Myriad Soul Herb's medicinal effects could be significantly enhanced upon being refined into Myriad Soul Pills, and that was naturally great news for Han Li.

"Fellow Daoist Li, are you able to sell me any more Baleful Quelling Pills? I don't have any more Myriad Soul Herbs, but during the Jade Gathering City auction, the Myriad Soul Herb was sold for three thousand five hundred Immortal Origin Stones, and I'm willing to pay that price for each pill," Shi Chuankong said with a hopeful expression.

"I was only able to refine a small batch of Baleful Quelling Pills due to insufficient ingredients, and I need to save some for myself, so I can only sell you five," Han Li replied after some contemplation.

"Five is certainly better than nothing, I suppose," Shi Chuankong said with a hint of disappointment in his eyes as he swept a sleeve through the air to summon a small pile of Immortal Origin Stones.

Han Li briefly swept his spiritual sense over the Immortal Origin Stones, then summoned a black jade vial before tossing it at Shi Chuankong.

Shi Chuankong removed the stopper of the vial to discover that there were six Baleful Quelling Pills inside.

"You can have an extra Baleful Quelling Pill in exchange for the Myriad Soul Pill recipe," Han Li said.

"You're a good man, Fellow Daoist Li," Shi Chuankong said with a wide smile, and after the two of them chatted for a while longer, Han Li returned to his own room.

Even though he had a decent supply of Baleful Quelling Pills in his position, he didn't dare to stay in the outside world for long, and he immediately entered the Flower Branch domain to remove himself from direct contact with the pervasive baleful qi in the Gray Realm.

Several more years flew by in a flash, and the louchuan finally arrived at Black Teeth City, which was quite a large city, comparable to some medium-sized cities in the True Immortal Realm.

There were many residents and shops in the city, but still far fewer than in some of the cities of the True Immortal Realm.

The louchuan circled around in the sky for a while, then descended in front of a majestic manor, following which Han Li's group disembarked.

Han Li didn't want to leave the Flower Branch space, but at the moment, the three of them were supposed to be guest elders of the San Miao Tribe, so he would have to meet the Black Teeth Regional Monarch.

Having said that, all three of them had concealed their auras, so they didn't attract any attention.

A black-robed man with scales all over his face rushed out of the manor to greet Miao Gao.

"Welcome, Monarch San Miao. The regional monarch is waiting for you inside, and all of the other monarchs have already arrived."

"It sounds like everyone's here nice and early. Lead the way," Miao Gao instructed.

The black-robed man led the group into the manor, and they soon arrived in a large hall, at the center of which was a trapezoid stone platform.

The stone platform was around five feet tall, and at this moment, there was a man with a thick black beard sitting on it.

The man was extremely broad and imposing, and he was wearing a black and golden robe that was stretched taut in many areas, struggling to contain the man's huge and muscular physique.

Four stone chairs were placed on either side of the stone platform, and aside from the last chair on the left hand side, all of the other seven chairs had already been occupied, with four or five servants standing behind each chair as well.

"Subordinate Miao Gao pays his respects to the regional monarch," Miao Gao said as he extended a salute, and Han Li and the others followed suit.

The black-robed man gave a slight nod, following which his gaze swept over Han Li's trio, and in particular, a hint of befuddlement flashed through his eyes at the sight of Mo Guang, but he didn't immediately raise any questions.

Meanwhile, Han Li was also secretly observing everyone in the hall, and he discovered that the Black Teeth Regional Monarch possessed the highest cultivation base out of everyone here at the mid-High Zenith Stage, while all of the other monarchs were Golden Immortals.

In light of this, it appeared that the Black Teeth Region was a slightly weaker region in the Gray Realm.

"Why are you so late, Miao Gao? Everyone's been waiting for you for a long time!" a portly elderly man seated on the third chair to the left complained in a displeased manner.

"My apologies, everyone. During our Tamda Festival, we were suddenly attacked by the Nirarbuda Region, and I had to take care of some matters in the aftermath, so I was delayed quite a bit," Miao Gao replied in a calm manner.

All of the other seven monarchs were astonished to hear this, but the regional monarch seemed to be already aware of this, and he said, "I've already heard about this. You did a great job fighting off the Nirarbuda invasion, and I'll arrange a reward for you later. For now, take a seat."

Miao Gao expressed his gratitude to the regional monarch, then sat down on the only vacant stone chair, while Han Li and the others stood behind him.

"Regional Monarch, the Three Region Conference is fast approaching. Now that Monarch Miao Gao is here, should we set off right away?" another black-robed man asked.

"There's no hurry. I'll arrange the itinerary, so there's no need for any of you to worry about that. On top of that, I have some matters that I wish to discuss with all of you regarding this conference," the regional monarch said.

The eight monarchs immediately sat up straighter upon hearing this.

The regional monarch took a glance at all of the monarchs' entourages, then instructed, "You can all go for now."

All of the entourages immediately vacated the hall, and Han Li had no interest in this meeting anyway, so he was more than happy to leave.

After all of the entourages had departed, the portly elderly man remarked, "Monarch Miao Gao, I can sense that three of the people in your entourage have very unique auras. They don't seem to be from your San Miao Tribe."

Chapter 717: Traveling to the Infernal Region

"Indeed, Monarch Lu Hong. I was just about to report this matter to our regional monarch. Those three are Void Integration beings from the Young Dawn Tribe, and they played an important role in opposing the Nirarbuda invasion, so our San Miao Tribe is quite indebted to them. They wanted to accompany us to Asura City to see the Three Region Conference, and that's why I brought them here," Miao Gao explained.

"Void Integration beings?"

All of the other monarchs faltered slightly upon hearing this.

"This conference directly concerns the interests of our Black Teeth Region, and it's an extremely important occasion. How could you just bring outsiders with you in such an unprofessional manner?" the portly elderly man by the name of Lu Hong complained with furrowed brows.

Miao Gao's expression darkened slightly, and he was just about to respond when the regional monarch said, "It's fine. All of them are carrying San Miao Tribe guest elder badges, so there's no problem in having them attend the conference. On top of that, I can see that they're all quite powerful, so if we can win them over, that would definitely be beneficial to our Black Teeth Region."

An elated look appeared on Miao Gao's face, and he hurriedly cupped his fist in a salute.

Lu Hong was still rather displeased, but he didn't dare to rebuke the regional monarch, so he could only remain silent.

......

After Han Li and the others emerged from the hall, Miao Xiu informed them of some of the rules of Black Teeth City, following which everyone parted ways.

Shi Chuankong bade farewell to Han Li and Mo Guang, then went straight to the markets in the city to hunt for more money-making opportunities.

Mo Guang returned straight to the louchuan, while Han Li gathered some more scriptures pertaining to the Gray Realm before also returning to the louchuan and entering the Flower Branch domain.

He had only just sat down in the Flower Branch space when Shi Qinghou's voice rang out in his mind. "I hear that the Three Region Conference is about to be held, is that right?"

"That's right. It seems that the three regions are going to discuss whether the Gray Realm should invade the True Immortal Realm," Han Li replied.

"Oh? That's quite interesting, but why is a True Immortal Realm cultivator like you interested in attending the conference? Are you going to gather intelligence?" Shi Qinghou asked.

"I'm nowhere near important enough to have to worry about such matters. The only reason why I'm interested in attending the conference is because I've heard that there's a Baleful Cleansing Pond in Asura City that can cleanse one of baleful qi, and I'm hoping to find this pond and use it to overcome my baleful decay," Han Li revealed.

"You want to find the Baleful Cleansing Pond? I've heard that there is such a place in Asura, but don't expect me to be of any help. Yin Chengquan and I are sworn enemies, but I've never been to Asura City, so I don't know where this Baleful Cleansing Pond is. Also, don't go taking risks willy nilly just because you've mastered the laws of time.

“Let me make this clear in advance: I've agreed to help you, but if you insist on courting death, then don't blame me if I waive our agreement," Shi Qinghou harrumphed coldly before falling silent.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this.

He had informed Shi Qinghou of his intentions as he wanted to find out more information about the Baleful Cleansing Pond from him, but it seemed that he didn't know anything on the subject.

Having said that, the Baleful Cleansing Pond was a vastly renowned place, so he was confident that he would be able to track it down once he reached Asura City.

As for Shi Qinghou's threat, Han Li didn't pay it much heed. Right now, their fates were intertwined, and once he entered Asura City, Shi Qinghou would be forced to help him whether he liked it or not.

On top of that, while Shi Qinghou's help would naturally be very welcome, even if he didn't help, it didn't matter to Han Li. He had always relied on himself, and he didn't need anyone else.

With that in mind, Han Li closed his eyes.

The meeting between the monarchs lasted two days, and on the third morning, everyone gathered on the plaza in front of the regional monarch's manor before boarding a five-story louchuan that was entirely constructed out of some type of black jade material, and they resumed their journey from there.

......

Over thirty years flew by in the blink of an eye.

On the horizon was an enormous black city wall that was over a thousand feet tall and stretched for thousands of kilometers, casting a gargantuan black shadow under the dim light of the suns.

A massive louchuan slowly descended right where the light and the shadows met, and several dozen figures disembarked, but didn't immediately fly toward the city gate.

Only after the Black Teeth Regional Monarch had flown down and stowed the louchuan away did everyone make their way toward the city gates together.

Han Li's trio was dressed in San Miao Tribe clothing, and as they walked along, Shi Chuankong praised, "So this is Asura City. What a majestic city it is. I'm sure it must be one of the largest cities in the entire Gray Realm."

Han Li cast his gaze into the distance to find that all types of strange patterns had been engraved onto the city walls, and there were faint baleful qi fluctuations emanating from them.

At this moment, there was a huge line of people at the city gates, waiting to enter the city.

The convoy of carriages that Han Li and the others were in slowed down over a thousand feet away from the city gates as it joined the back of the line.

From there, Han Li could see three arch gates, stationed beside which were hundreds of guards.

All of them were dressed in gray robes that trailed all the way down onto the ground, while their feet hovered around a foot in mid-air so that they stood a little taller than everyone else, all of them wore cold expressions.

In terms of physical appearance, they were quite similar to humans, except their faces were covered in gray scales, presenting a rather disconcerting sight to behold.

"It looks like all of them are Infernal beings," Shi Chuankong remarked as he swept his gaze over the gray-robed figures, and Han Li was also rather perplexed to see this.

The Infernal Tribe was the ruling tribe of the Infernal Region, and its chief was the monarch of the Infernal Region, so it was a prestigious tribe that normally didn't stoop to such menial duties, yet on this day, all of the guards at the city gates were Infernal beings.

"Those aren't Infernal beings, they can only be categorized as Infernal Servants at the very most. Infernal Servants are a lowly branch eliminated from the Infernal Tribe that act as their servants. There are very few true Infernal beings, and almost every single one of them is a cultivation prodigy, so they're all extremely proud.

“You see that small group of people standing at the foot of the city gate? Those are true Infernal beings," Miao Gao explained as he turned to Han Li's trio.

Han Li cast his gaze in that direction to find a thin elderly man with sunken cheeks seated on a large black chair at the foot of the city gate. He was wearing a black robe, and he appeared to be no different from the Infernal Servants, except his face was devoid of scales.

The elderly man made no attempt to conceal his own aura, and he was a late-High Zenith cultivator.

There were two other black-robed figures hovering in mid-air beside him, and they were quite tall to begin with, so the fact that they were hovering about a foot above the ground placed them even higher above everyone else.

As the Black Teeth Region's tribe arrived at the city gate, the black-robed elderly man merely took a glance at them while remaining seated in his chair.

Out of the two figures hovering beside him, a slightly chubby man drifted over to Han Li's group, and he didn't even bother to extend a salute as he led them to the side gate to the left of the main gate and said, "Please come with me."

The Black Teeth Regional Monarch's brows furrowed slightly with displeasure upon seeing this, but he didn't say anything.

The other monarchs of the Black Teeth Region were also infuriated by this treatment, and many of them were cursing under their breaths, but none of them dared to protest beyond a whisper.

Upon being led to the gate on the left, they were greeted by the sight of another long line, this one seemingly consisting of some tribes from the Reincarnation Region.

Han Li's trio were slowly walking along with Miao Gao and the others when Shi Chuankong suddenly said through voice transmission, "Something's not right, Fellow Daoist Li. It looks like they're conducting identity checks over there."

As soon as his voice trailed off, Miao Gao spat under his breath, "These bastards! Not only are they making us take the side entrance, they're even checking our identities! What do they take us for?"

Han Li turned to discover that there was a person standing in front of the gate, holding an octagonal black mirror with a metal frame. The surface of the mirror was glistening like a black crystal, and whenever someone arrived at the gate, the person would examine their eyes through the mirror.

However, there was no one conducting these examinations at the other two gates.

"That mirror is called an Infernal Inspection Mirror, and it's an inspection treasure that's particularly effective at examining changes in baleful qi. The baleful qi in the eyes of those examined by the mirror will be fully revealed, and they can even determine which tribe someone is from based on the minute differences in their pupils," Mo Guang suddenly said through voice transmission.

"How do you know that?" Han Li asked with a surprised expression.

"The two of you have been reading through all types of Gray Realm scriptures recently, and I haven't been slacking off, either. I saw a description of this mirror in a book called the Wondrous Artifact Journal. Would you like to take a look?" Mo Guang asked with a smile.

"Do you think the mirror will be able to see through our disguises?" Han Li asked with tightly furrowed brows.

"My body belonged to a Void Integration being to begin with, so I'll be fine. As for you, your pupils have already changed due to your struggles with your baleful decay, and there's also baleful qi in your immortal acupoints, so you should be able to avoid detection as well. However, the same can't be said for Fellow Daoist Shi," Mo Guang replied.

A concerned look appeared on Shi Chuankong's face upon hearing this.

The line up ahead appeared to be quite long, but everyone was moving quite quickly, and it wasn't going to be long before it was the turn of Han Li's trio to undergo their examination.

The regional monarch naturally didn't have to be examined. All he had to do was flash his regional monarch badge to be granted entry into the city. However, everyone else from the Black Teeth Region tribes had to be examined with no exceptions.

Following their examinations, the people from the Black Teeth Region didn't immediately enter the city. Instead, all of them waited beside the gate with the regional monarch until everyone was ready.

Before long, it was time for Han Li's trio to step forward.

Chapter 718: Ripples

Miao Gao seemed to be in a rather foul mood, and he stepped forward to be examined by the Infernal Inspection Mirror, then strode forward without even taking a glance at the Infernal being.

Right after him came Miao Xiu, whose smile remained unchanged this entire time, making it impossible to tell what she was thinking.

"It'll be our turn soon, Fellow Daoist Li. What should we do?" Shi Chuankong asked through voice transmission.

"Don't do anything rash, just react as the situation unfolds. If one of us gets exposed, I'll buy us some time, while you use your spatial powers to get us our of here. If worse comes to worst, a battle will most likely be unavoidable, but hopefully it doesn't come to that," Han Li replied through voice transmission.

"I suppose that's all we can do. I must say, you're remarkably calm, given the situation," Shi Chuankong said.

"There's no point in worrying. If you have the time to worry, you may as well think about what you can do if things do go sour," Han Li replied.

Mo Guang remained silent with a faint smile on his face, seemingly completely unperturbed.

At this point, the people of the San Miao Tribe had already completed their identity examinations, and it was Mo Guang's turn.

The Infernal Servant operating the mirror turned slightly so that he could see Mo Guang through the mirror, and a perplexed look appeared on his face as he asked, "What is a Void Integration being like you doing with the San Miao Tribe?"

The elderly Infernal being seated on the black chair turned to Mo Guang upon hearing this.

"I'm serving as a guest elder in the San Miao Tribe. Is that a problem?" Mo Guang asked as he raised an eyebrow.

Before the Infernal Servant had a chance to reply, the elderly Infernal being replied in his stead, "It would certainly be normal for a San Miao being to serve as a guest elder in the Void Integration Tribe, but the opposite is far more uncommon."

Immediately thereafter, he appeared right in front of Mo Guang as if by instantaneous teleportation, and he began to blatantly examine Mo Guang without any modicum of respect.

This man has also mastered the laws of space!

Shi Chuankong's hands had already balled up into tight fists within his sleeves, and Han Li was also feeling a little apprehensive upon seeing this, but his expression remained unchanged.

"I can serve as a guest elder for any tribe that I want. Is your Infernal Tribe the master of the Void Integration Tribe?" Mo Guang asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"Don't forget that you're on the territory of our Infernal Tribe right now," the elderly man said in a cold voice.

"Is this where the Three Region Conference is being held?" Mo Guang asked.

"That's right," the elderly man replied.

"Are there rules stating that Void Integration Tribe guest elders of the San Miao Tribe can't accompany them to the conference?" Mo Guang asked.

The elderly man was silent for a moment, then returned to his chair as he instructed, "Let him through."

One of the Infernal beings beside him hurriedly said with a fawning smile, "There's no need to get mad at him, he's just a wretched Void Integration being who's willingly stooped down to the San Miao Tribe's level."

The elderly man harrumphed coldly in response, then closed his eyes.

The monarchs of the Black Teeth Region didn't feel this interaction to be inappropriate at all, and Miao Gao was even secretly giving Mo Guang a thumbs up, clearly very pleased that he had stood up for them.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong exchanged a glance with each other, following which Han Li stepped forward to the Infernal Servant.

The Infernal Servant peered into Han Li's eyes through his octagonal mirror, and on the outside, Han Li appeared calm and collected, but internally, he was extremely apprehensive, preparing to release his time spirit domain at a moment's notice.

A peculiar look appeared on the Infernal Servant's face as he suddenly said, "Your eyes..."

Han Li's heart immediately sank slightly upon hearing this, yet right as he was about to spring into action, the Infernal Servant continued, "They're a little light in color. Could it be that you're a mix-blood?"

Han Li's heart stirred slightly upon hearing this.

According to the scriptures that he had read, Gray Realm beings who didn't possess pure bloodlines often had abnormalities in their baleful qi, and that resulted in their pupils being lighter or impure in color.

Mix-bloods had always been regarded as lowly beings, and Han Li took advantage of this, adopting an enraged facade as he yelled, "What does that matter to you? If you're done, then hurry up and let me through!"

The Infernal Servant waved him through with a disdainful look on his face.

After being rebuked by Mo Guang, the Infernal Tribe elder was naturally reluctant to examine Han Li in person, particularly after hearing that he was a "mix-blood".

Shi Chuankong stepped up in Han Li's place, and the Infernal Servant turned to him through his octagonal mirror.

"Are you another mix-blood? No, that doesn't seem quite right..." the Infernal Servant murmured to himself.

"What's wrong?" the slightly chubby Infernal being asked as he approached the Infernal Servant.

"This man's eyes are a little strange, Elder Yin Shan," the infernal servant hurriedly replied.

"Let me take a look," Elder Yin Shan said.

His cultivation base was far superior to the Infernal Servant's, so if he were to conduct an examination in person, then Shi Chuankong's cover would most likely be blown.

"Get ready, Fellow Daoist Shi, Fellow Daoist Mo Guang," Han Li said through voice transmission, and he was already bracing himself for the imminent battle.

A serious look had also appeared on Mo Guang's face, and Shi Chuankong was also preparing himself to summon that silver lute at a moment's notice.

Miao Xiu was standing behind Han Li and Mo Guang, and a peculiar feeling suddenly welled up in her heart. It seemed to her like their demeanors had completely shifted.

Right at this moment, a disdainful voice rang out.

"I didn't know maggots from the Black Teeth Region were entitled to attend the Three Region Conference! This is not your little Tamda Festival, don't you feel embarrassed coming here?"

Everyone's attention was drawn in that direction, and Yin Shan also stopped what he was doing.

Shi Chuankong heaved an internal sigh of relief, and he turned to discover a giant azure ape that was over twenty feet tall, clad in a suit of black armor. He was holding a black spear as he swaggered along, and there were close to a hundred foreign beings behind him, all of whom were also walking along in an arrogant fashion.

All of the people from the Black Teeth Region immediately gathered before them.

"I thought I heard some barking, turns out it's the stray dogs from the Nirarbuda Region," Monarch Lu Hong chuckled.

The azure ape was furious to hear this, and he thrust his spear straight at Lu Hong without any warning.

His attack was extremely measured, and a beam of incredibly compact gray light shot out of the tip of his spear, affecting no one else in the area as it hurtled directly toward Lu Hong's glabella.

Only then did Han Li discover that the azure ape was a mid-High Zenith cultivator, and judging from the baleful qi erupting out his body, he seemed to be even more formidable than the Black Teeth Regional Monarch. He was striking with the intent to kill, and if his attack were to land, then Lu Hong would at least be severely wounded, if not killed on the spot.

Right at this moment, the Black Teeth Regional Monarch intervened, flying through the air before raising a hand to summon a circular black shield, which clashed against the beam of gray light.

A dull thump rang out as the beam of gray light exploded, and the force of the explosion forced the Black Teeth Regional Monarch back a step.

"What are you doing, Wu Chongshan? Do you want our two regions to battle it out here?" the Black Teeth Regional Monarch asked in a cold voice.

As he was speaking, he took a glance at the Infernal Tribe elder seated on the black chair out of his peripheral vision, only to discover that the elder was resting with his eyes closed, paying no heed to the unfolding conflict.

Yin Shan was also clearly not going to intervene, and the Black Teeth Regional Monarch's heart sank slightly upon seeing this.

"Mu Yi, who was the one that killed my nephew during the battle at Wave Edge Lake? Hand him over, and I won't pursue this matter any further," Wu Chongshan demanded.

Miao Gao reflexively took a glance at Mo Guang upon hearing this, only to find that he was standing off to the side as if he were watching a good show, displaying no fear, but also no intention to step forward.

"He deserved to die for attacking our Black Teeth Region," Mu Yi replied with a cold sneer.

At this point, all of the people gathered at the city gates had converged to watch the unfolding conflict, and the situation had become very chaotic.

With the attention diverted away from him, Shi Chuankong took the opportunity to sneak over to Han Li's side.

Wu Chongshan's expression darkened even further upon hearing this, and it seemed that a battle was inevitable.

"Fellow Daoist Mo Guang, if things continue to escalate, more powerful figures could arrive on the scene, and that could prove to be very troublesome for us," Han Li said through voice transmission.

Thus, Mo Guang stepped forward as he declared, "I killed him. What are you going to do about it?"

At the same time, a mid-High Zenith Stage aura erupted out of his body, and Wu Chongshan's expression changed drastically upon seeing this.

He had thought that Mu Yi was the only High Zenith cultivator in the entire Black Teeth Region, but another had suddenly popped up out of nowhere, and his aura wasn't any less formidable than Wu Chongshan's own.

However, with so many people watching, he couldn't just back down, so he strode forward as he prepared to attack Mo Guang, and all of the other beings from the Nirarbuda Region were also gearing up for battle.

A faint smile appeared on Mo Guang's face, and his lower body was already beginning to transform into black mist.

A battle was on the verge of erupting.

Chapter 719: Parting Ways

"Stop."

Right at this moment, the Infernal Tribe elder finally spoke up.

His voice rang out like the sound of a massive gong being struck, reverberating incessantly within the minds of everyone present.

"Asura City is not the place for your senseless battles. Settle down, or you'll be evicted from the Infernal Region right away."

Wu Chongshan was looking for an opportunity to de-escalate the conflict, so he immediately extended a respectful salute toward the Infernal Tribe elder before backing down, while all of the people from the Black Teeth Region also did the same.

In the wake of that farce, Elder Yin Shan forgot to examine Shi Chuankong, and he was granted entry into the city.

......

That night, the people from the Black Teeth Region were arranged to stay in a residential palace by the Infernal Tribe.

As night arrived, Han Li's trio arrived at a branch of the residential palace before announcing their arrival.

Before long, Miao Gao and Miao Xiu emerged to greet them, and the five of them entered Miao Gao's residential quarters together.

After sitting down around an ornate black stone table, Mo Guang said, "My apologies for coming to disturb you at such a late hour."

Miao Gao faltered slightly upon hearing this, then replied, "There's no need to apologize, Fellow Daoist Jiang Gu. Can I help you with something?"

"We will be leaving tomorrow morning, and I've come here to bid you farewell," Mo Guang said with a smile.

"Why are you leaving all of a sudden?" Miao Gao asked with a puzzled expression, and Miao Xiu's brows also furrowed slightly upon hearing this.

"I was initially planning to stay for the Three Region Conference, but it feels like there's a lot of animosity here, and I don't wish to be swept up in any conflicts, so I think the best course of action would be for me to leave. I much prefer more amicable and festive settings like the one at the Tamda Festival, although that also ultimately devolved into a battle.

“On top of that, I heard that the inverted street in Asura City is quite renowned, so I want to pay it a visit to see if I can find some good treasures there," Mo Guang explained.

A peculiar look flashed through Miao Gao's eyes upon hearing this, and he replied, "That's a shame, but if you've already made up your mind, then I won't try to dissuade you. However, do keep in mind that outsiders like us are only allowed to move around in certain areas of Asura City, while the rest of the city is off-limits for us."

"Please pardon my interjection, Senior Jiang Gu, but the three of you have entered Asura City as guest elders of our San Miao Tribe. If you won't be accompanying us to the Three Region Conference, then you'll have to adopt a different identity as you travel through the city," Miao Xiu suddenly said.

Han Li took a glance at her upon hearing this.

What she was implying was that once they left the San Miao Tribe, all ties would be severed between them, and their actions would have nothing to do with the San Miao Tribe, clearly indicating that she didn't believe Mo Guang's excuse for leaving.

Mo Guang was also aware of this, but his smile remained unchanged as he said, "Rest assured, Monarch Miao, I'm an avid traveler, and I won't cause any trouble."

"Forgive me for perhaps rambling a little, but the Infernal Region has harbored a great deal of enmity toward the tribes of the Reincarnation Region, and in the wake of what just happened, there's a chance that you could already be under some scrutiny. Hence, please make sure to be extra careful in case you're attacked," Miao Gao cautioned.

"Thank you for the cautionary words, Monarch Miao Gao, I'll be sure to keep that in mind," Mo Guang replied with a warm smile, and Han Li's trio departed shortly thereafter.

Following their departure, Miao Xiu turned to her father and said, "Father, they..."

"I know what you want to say, Xiuxiu," Miao Gao interjected. "It's fine. There's no way we can go to the Young Dawn Region to verify Jiang Gu's identity, but his aura is most definitely genuine, and his two servants also seem to be quite powerful. It's clear that they've come to Asura City for some type of ulterior motive, but seeing as we've already decided to vote for the Reincarnation Region, it's best for us to remain on good terms with them."

"But Father, are you not worried that their true objective for coming to Asura City could cause trouble for our San Miao Tribe? I can't shake the feeling that there's something strange about them, and I feel like even their initial contact with our tribe was orchestrated by them in advance," Miao Xiu said.

"What trouble could they possibly cause? It's fine as long as they don't harbor any ill will toward us. It's not like they'll go around telling everyone that they came here with our San Miao Tribe, and we're certainly not going to tell anyone, either. Besides, do you not want to see someone stir things up a little in Asura City?

“We still haven't fully exacted revenge on the Nirarbuda Region yet, so it would be quite welcome if they could stir up a little trouble in the Infernal Region. Having said that, I will have to think of a good explanation to provide to the regional monarch," Miao Gao said with a nonchalant smile.

Miao Xiu was still a little unconvinced, but there wasn't too much else that she could say on this matter.

......

The next morning, Han Li's trio left the residential palace and set off northward.

Earlier, Han Li had already heard from Miao Gao that Asura City was split up into nine major areas, with each area taking up hundreds of thousands of kilometers. As opposed to a city, it really was more like a nation.

The residential palace that they had been staying on was situated on the border of Asura City, and they had to pass through three entire areas in order to reach their destination.

There were many people on the streets, but in contrast with Han Li's trio, who were walking along, most of them were hovering roughly a foot above the ground.

Their appearances were quite similar to humans, but all of them wore cold expressions, and whenever they gazed upon Han Li's trio of outsiders, they did so with a great deal of enmity in their eyes.

At this point, Mo Guang had already changed into a loose-fitting black cloak, and there was a disdainful look on his face as he remarked, "These Infernal Servants really are a pain to look at."

Han Li adjusted the hood of his cloak slightly as he said, "The Infernal Tribe is just as xenophobic as Fellow Daoist Baili claimed they would be. They're not even making any effort to hide their animosity."

"Fellow Daoist Li, we know far too little about the Infernal Tribe. Are we really just going to venture into a sacred area of theirs like this? It seems far too risky no matter how I look at it," Shi Chuankong said with a concerned expression.

Han Li hadn't kept his meeting with Baili Yan a secret from Shi Chuankong. He had informed him of the two options, namely to return to the Immortal Realm through the Reincarnation Palace or to travel to the Baleful Cleansing Pond, and he had presented Shi Chuankong with two choices, the first of which was that Shi Chuankong could travel on his own to the Reincarnation Region, then wait for Han Li to return from the Infernal Region before taking him to the Reincarnation Palace, while the second was to accompany Han Li to the Infernal Region before traveling to the Reincarnation Region together.

Unsurprisingly, Shi Chuankong chose the latter option, both out of concern for his own safety and on the basis of his Baleful Quelling Pill requirements.

"If it isn't for this Three Region Conference, we wouldn't even be able to enter Asura City. If we don't go this time, the option will be forever lost to us," Han Li replied with slightly furrowed brows.

"It seems like the Infernal Tribe holds the Baleful Cleansing Pond in very high regard. Up to this point, we've barely been able to find out any information about it, how are we supposed to find it?" Shi Chuankong sighed.

"It's fine, let's just go to the inverted street first. There are supposed to be a lot of shops there, so I'm sure we can find out more about the Baleful Cleansing Pond there, and perhaps we could even secure a copy of the map of Asura City," Han Li replied.

"I suppose that's all we can do for now," Shi Chuankong replied with a nod.

Meanwhile, Mo Guang was walking along with his hands clasped behind his back while observing the people around him, looking very casual and relaxed.

......

Asura City, Passive Mountain Area.

On the summit of a giant mountain was an artificial plateau that was a result of the original summit being shaved off, and on the plateau was a majestic palace.

In front of the palace was a spacious black stone plaza that was constructed on a cliff, and beyond the railing was the sheer cliff face, at the foot of which was a vast expanse of black mist that was rippling incessantly in the wind.

At this moment, there were two figures, one black and one white, standing within the railing, looking out in the direction of the Fallen Lake Area.

The black figure was dressed in an enormous black cloak that was riddled with black dragon patterns, and the long tail of the cloak was trailing along on the ground, enshrouded in faint baleful qi.

Beneath the cloak was a tall and imposing man who was hovering roughly a foot above the ground. He had a head of long hair, and he was clad in a suit of antiquated azure armor, the breastplate of which was riddled with specks of rust and had been fashioned into the form of a beastly head.

The man's complexion was quite pale, and he had a set of clear-cut and angular features. There was a very cold look on his face, and he was looking directly forward in a completely expressionless manner.

The white figure beside him was an elderly man whose hair and beard were as white as snow, and he was dressed in a Dao robe of a very high caliber. There were waves of light constantly flowing down the robe from his shoulders before splashing down onto the ground beneath his feet.

The waves of light were giving off water law power fluctuations that weren't all that formidable, but were perpetual and unrelenting.

There was a cloud of water vapor around the elderly man, acting as a wall to completely keep out all of the baleful qi in the surrounding air, and he turned to the tall figure beside him as he asked, "What do you think are our chances of coming out on top in the vote during the conference?"

"Less than 30%," the black-robed man replied in a cold voice.

"Are there already that many tribes of the Black Rope Region that have thrown their support behind the Reincarnation Region?" the white-robed elderly man asked as he raised an eyebrow.

Chapter 720: Inverted

"Those fence-sitters are constantly swaying from one side to another, and the Reincarnation Region has been very active over the past thousand years, so this is no surprise. Having said that, the foundation of our collaboration hinges on the failure of this negotiation, so none of this really matters," the black-robed man harrumphed coldly.

"That may be true, but wouldn't it be better if we could secure victory by unveiling our trump cards? After that, we'll be able to exert pressure and slowly chip away at the Reincarnation Region," the white-robed elderly man said.

"You want to sow internal conflict within our Gray Realm so that we can whittle away at the Reincarnation Region without any effort on your part? Isn't your Heavenly Court being a little too greedy? Feng Qingshui, I suggest you stop trying to play these tricks because you're not fooling anyone," the black-robed man said with a cold sneer.

Veins immediately began to bulge on the white-robed elderly man's forehead upon hearing this.

Ever since he became a Dao Ancestor, he couldn't recall the last time someone had dared to refer to him directly by name to his face.

However, his anger was only a flash in the pan, and it quickly subsided as he replied, "Yin Chengquan, our Heavenly Court will be sure to do our part, but this is your Infernal Tribe's territory, so you better make sure that nothing goes wrong on your end."

"You don't have to worry about that. Even if the measures that you've prepared fail, I still have backup measures that I can employ," Yin Chengquan replied.

"Good. In that case, our collaboration should be a smooth and mutually beneficial one," Feng Qingshui replied.

"Let me make this clear in advance: your Heavenly Court better not do anything extra outside the terms of our agreement. Otherwise, there will be consequences to bear," Yin Chengquan said as a cold tone crept into his voice.

Feng Qingshui merely harrumphed coldly in response.

......

The Tarmin Area was the area in Asura City filled with the most shops and merchants, and it was also the most densely populated area in the city. Cultivators from all tribes in the Infernal Region converged there, so Han Li's trio didn't look too out of place.

There were many renowned merchant streets and markets in the Tarmin Area, and the most renowned one of all of them was the inverted street.

After passing through a multitude of streets, Han Li's trio finally arrived at a massive plaza.

There were several times more beings from different tribes than they had seen on the way here, and many of them had a black wooden crate hanging in front of them, within which were placed all types of different wares that they were trying to sell.

Right at this moment, a short Gray Realm being with dark green skin and a shock of green hair on his head approached Han Li's trio, then began enthusiastically advertising his wares.

"Can I interest you in a premium Baleful Snout Smoke Kettle? No? Then how about a few Baleful Inkstones? They're an absolute must for setting up arrays."

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he paid no heed to the salesman, while Mo Guang was staring at a giant black tree in the distance, and Shi Chuankong was the only one who was actually browsing through the wares in the black wooden crate with keen interest.

Shi Chuankong casually tossed an intricate little kettle back into the wooden crate, then remarked, "It doesn't look like you have anything good to sell. You could probably sell these things to some low-tier beings, but do we look like the type who would be interested in things like this?"

"I beg to differ. These little trinkets of mine aren't exactly high-grade tresures, but they're very versatile and useful for a wide variety of purposes," the green-haired being replied with a sheepish smile.

"I suppose you're not wrong there. How much for these Baleful Inkstones?" Shi Chuankong asked.

He continued to walk forward as he spoke, and the green-haired being was backpedaling in order to keep up with him.

"At the very least, seven of them will be required to set up an array, and I'll only charge three gray crystals. If you take a large set of twenty-one, then that'll only be eight gray crystals," the green-haired being hurriedly replied.

"Eight for twenty-one is a fair price. How about if I buy forty-nine? How much of a discount can you give me then?" Shi Chuankong asked.

The green-haired being's eyes instantly lit up upon hearing this, following which he replied in a slightly embarrassed manner, "I'm afraid I don't have that much stock left. I only have thirty-five left on hand, and I can sell them to you for twelve gray crystals. Is that alright?"

"You don't have enough stock? Forget about it then," Shi Chuankong replied with a dismissive wave.

"Don't pass me up so quickly, esteemed customer. Is there anything else I have here that catches your eye? Perhaps I can throw in something else to sweeten the deal," the green-haired being hurriedly said, frantically trying to retain Shi Chuankong's interest.

Shi Chuankong examined the wares in the crate momentarily with a disdainful expression, then said, "Nothing else here catches my eye. Do you have a map of Asura City? I want as detailed a map as possible."

The green-haired being was horrified by this request, and he hurriedly looked around momentarily, then gently tugged on Shi Chuankong's sleeve as he said in a quiet voice, "Please be careful with what you say here, esteemed customer. The Infernal Tribe is very stingy and never allows private sales of maps of Asura City, nor do they ever sell their maps to outside tribes.

“It's a good thing that you're talking to me. If you asked to buy a map from someone else, they could easily report the matter to the Infernal Tribe, and you'll be in a lot of trouble."

Han Li had been eavesdropping on their conversation this entire time, and his brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this.

"Is that so? Thank you for informing me of that," Shi Chuankong mused.

"You're very much welcome, esteemed customer," the green-haired being hurriedly replied.

"Alright, how about this? I'll take all thirty-five of your Baleful Inkstones, and there's no need to give me any discount. Throw in that black walnut, and I'll give you fifteen gray crystals as thanks for your cautionary words," Shi Chuankong said with a smile.

The green-haired being took a glance at the black walnut that Shi Chuankong was referring to, and a hint of elation flashed through his eyes as he said, "This is a Baleful Gathering Stone that's yet to reach full maturity, and it's not all that valuable. If you like it, then you can have it. It's not every day that I meet someone as generous as yourself, so I'd like to offer you another piece of advice.

“If you're looking for a map, don't go to the shops run by the major tribes of the Infernal Region, and don't go to walking salesmen like myself, either. The former wouldn't sell any maps to you, and the latter wouldn't have any, so they'd only be able to sell counterfeits."

"Alright, thanks again then," Shi Chuankong said with a smile, then handed over the gray crystals in exchange for the Baleful Inkstones and the Baleful Gathering Stone.

After the walking salesman departed, Han Li asked through voice transmission, "What bargain have you picked up this time, Fellow Daoist Shi?"

"That idiot mistook the core of a Baleful Bone Demon as a Baleful Gathering Stone!" Shi Chuankong replied with a smile.

"What's a Baleful Bone Demon?" Han Li asked.

"That's what those things are called in the Immortal Realm, and their cores are very valuable in our Devil Realm. This one seems to have been scorched by some type of fire, causing the baleful qi inside to become extremely subdued, and that's probably why it was mistaken for something else," Shi Chuankong explained with a smug expression.

Right at this moment, Mo Guang suddenly exclaimed, "So this is why it's called the inverted street..."

Han Li and Shi Chuankong cast their eyes forward upon hearing this, and they were greeted by the sight of hundreds of branches extending out of the giant black tree at the center of the plaza, with different types of buildings constructed on those branches like hanging fruits.

Due to the irregular shapes of the branches, the buildings constructed upon them were also built in different forms and on different angles.

Han Li's trio arrived at the foot of the giant tree, where they saw a massive entrance on its trunk, above which was hanging a huge plaque that read "Inverted Street".

After stepping in through the entrance, they were greeted by the sight of two spiral staircases that led up the trunk of the tree, one on each side. At set intervals up the staircase, there were openings that led to the shops on the branches.

There were currently many people walking up and down the staircases, as well as many people who were more familiar with the layout of the inverted street and were flying straight to the levels that they wanted to visit. The situation was a little chaotic, but it was quite efficient.

Han Li's trio made their way up the staircase on the left, then emerged from the first opening to arrive in front of a majestic black hall.

Even before entering the hall, Han Li could see that all of the shopkeepers and employees were either Infernal beings or Infernal Servants, and he immediately stopped in his tracks before making his way toward another branch.

After exploring around a dozen main branches, they discovered that all of the shops were either run by Infernal beings or by several of the Infernal Region's other major tribes, with very few exceptions.

In the end, instead of continuing their search level by level, they decided to fly straight to the top.

Up here, the branches were already extremely thin, so most of the shops were very small and hanging from the branches like bells.

Han Li's trio arrived at one of the shops before flying into it, and inside was a tall and thin shopkeeper with ashy gray skin.

He was sitting in front of a row of shelves in a drowsy fashion, and there was an ornate Baleful Snout Smoke Kettle in his hand.

Upon spotting Han Li's trio, the shopkeeper immediately inhaled some of the smoke coming out of the snout of the kettle to reinvigorate himself, then greeted, "Welcome! What can I help you with today? Here at my shop, you'll find great quality products for cheapt prices, and most importantly, all prices are negotiable."

This was clearly a very well-rehearsed spiel, but he spoke with a sense of laziness in his voice.

"You're from the Dark Mulberry Tribe, right? Why have you opened your shop in Asura City?" Shi Chuankong asked with a smile.

Through the scriptures that he had collected, Han Li knew that the Dark Mulberry Tribe was one of the tribes under the Black Rope Region, as opposed to the Infernal Region, so this was indeed quite a rare sight.

Chapter 721: Secret Journey

The shopkeeper was rather taken aback to hear this, and he replied, "You have a keen eye, esteemed customer. I am indeed from the Dark Mulberry Tribe, but I left a long time ago."

"I see. It's a pleasure to make your acquaintance," Shi Chuankong said with a smile.

"What can I help you with today?" the shopkeeper asked.

Shi Chuankong took a glance at his surroundings, then replied, "We need a map of Asura City. Do you have one?"

The shopkeeper's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he took a glance outside before replying in a hushed voice, "That's a prohibited item that's not to be sold to or by any outside tribes."

"Who's going to know if none of us say anything? I give you the money, you give me the map, and that'll be that," Shi Chuankong chuckled.

The shopkeeper seemed to be quite hesitant, and he offered no response for a long while. Shi Chuankong made no attempt to rush him, and he began browsing through the wares of the shop in a casual fashion.

Shi Chuankong was more adept when it came to business matters, so Han Li decided to remain silent and uninvolved.

Mo Guang had no interest in the shop's wares, so he stood at the entrance, looking down below.

The shopkeeper was intentionally putting on a hesitant display, but with no one taking the bait, he had no choice but to break the silence himself.

"I have what you're looking for, but I'm sure you're aware of how risky this is for me. Hence, the price is going to be a little steep."

"That's fine, just state your price, shopkeeper," Shi Chuankong replied with a smile.

"I want fifty gray crystals," the shopkeeper said.

Instead of immediately giving a response, Shi Chuankong merely smiled and said, "While it's true that this is quite a high-risk item, but it's also extremely niche, so I'm assuming it's very rare that you get customers looking for it."

"That's true, but like I said, everything that I sell in my shop is open to negotiation," the shopkeeper replied.

"I'll give you ten gray crystals at most," Shi Chuankong said.

"That's too large a discount to ask for. My map is different from all the counterfeits going around. It's a little old, but it's definitely genuine and accurate," the shopkeeper said as his brows furrowed slightly.

"How can you be sure that the map is genuine?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"The access restrictions on the nine areas of Asura City only came into effect around two thousand to three thousand years ago. Prior to that, all areas were accessible with the exception of the Soul Cleansing Area, so the regulations on maps weren't very tight, either.

“The map that I have is one of the few official maps left after the restrictions were implemented, and it can't even be compared with all of the replicas on the black market," the shopkeeper replied.

"What's so special about this Soul Cleansing Area?" Han Li asked.

"It's the area where the Infernal Region's sacred landmark is situated, and it's always been shrouded in mystery. Even the average Infernal being isn't granted access to that area," the shopkeeper replied.

"In that case, I can raise the price to fifteen gray crystals," Shi Chuankong said.

"I won't sell it for any less than forty," the shopkeeper countered.

Shi Chuankong remained unfazed, and after some negotiation, the price was finally decided at twenty-eight gray crystals.

The shopkeeper brought out a black stone plate in a slightly reluctant manner, but Shi Chuankong's hands remained clasped behind his back, displaying no intention to pay.

Right as the shopkeeper was beginning to grow confused, Shi Chuankong turned to Han Li and said, "What are you standing there for? Pay up!"

A wry smile appeared on Han Li's face as he handed over the gray crystals in exchange for the black stone plate.

Mo Guang refined the stone plate, and after verifying that the map inside was genuine, the three of them left the shop.

Upon emerging onto the street outside, Han Li turned to Shi Chuankong and asked, "Why did you barter so much just to save a few dozen gray crystals? It's not like we'll have any use for them after we get back to the Immortal Realm."

"It's not about the gray crystals, Fellow Daoist Li, it's about business," Shi Chuankong replied with a smile.

As soon as his voice trailed off, Mo Guang suddenly said through voice transmission, "According to the map, the location of the Soul Cleansing Area is very special. From here, we need to venture through the Hundred Treasure Area and the Rashom Area before we can get there.

“Both areas are separated by tall walls and restrictions, but the types of restrictions in place aren't specified. On top of that, the Soul Cleansing Area on the map is also completely blank."

"Given how secretive the area is, it seems like that should be where the Baleful Cleansing Pond is. Let's go to the Hundred Treasure Area first," Han Li decided.

Mo Guang nodded in response, then led the way toward the Hundred Treasure Area.

Right at this moment, the sound of a massive gong being struck rang out in the distance, and it was clearly audible across the entire city.

At the same time, four pillars of white light rose up from afar, rising up straight into the heavens.

Each pillar of white light was over a thousand feet thick, and they resembled four enormous pillars that connected heaven and earth.

Everyone on the street immediately stopped what they were doing to turn their attention to the spectacle, and some of the people who were familiar with one another had even gathered together to observe the pillars of white light with excited expressions.

Han Li's trio also stopped in their tracks and turned to the pillars of white light.

After listening to the conversations taking place for a moment, Shi Chuankong concluded, "Looks like the Three Region Conference has begun."

"That's good. Now that most of Asura City's attention is focused on the conference, we'll be able to depart without being detected," Han Li said.

With that, the three of them quickly set off again.

......

The four pillars of white light were situated around a giant plaza in the Fallen Lake Area, one that was close to a hundred kilometers in size.

The plaza was paved with white bricks crafted from an unknown material, and they were giving off wisps of white mist, causing the entire plaza to be enshrouded in a white cloud. This mist was rather interesting in that it didn't rise up any further beyond around a foot in height, making it resemble a flat sea of clouds.

At this moment, there were countless people standing outside the plaza, most of which were residents of Asura City, including both Infernal Servants and the entourages of all of the tribes that had come to attend the conference.

There were close to a thousand guards clad in suits of gray armor standing around the plaza, keeping the crowd at bay.

On each corner of the plaza was a stone pillar, and they were the sources of the pillars of white light, which were becoming brighter and brighter.

Countless white runes were surging out of the surfaces of the pillars of white light in a frenzy, releasing an incredibly tremendous aura.

Bursts of thunderous rumbling were ringing out incessantly high up in the sky, while the baleful qi was churning violently, forming bursts of swirling gray light in the sky.

All of a sudden, a resounding boom rang out as a white stone platform abruptly appeared in the sky, then slowly descended onto the ground.

The stone platform was several thousand feet tall, and it cast a shadow that encompassed all of the bystanders down below.

On top of the platform was an open area, upon which was placed an enormous circular white table.

It was unclear what material this table was crafted from, and it was very antiquated in appearance. Despite the apparent lack of restrictions on its surface, it still gave off a sense of prestige and gravitas.

There were over a hundred chairs placed around the table, and it appeared that was where the conference was going to be taking place.

All of the bystanders immediately erupted into conversation upon seeing this.

They had heard that the regional monarch was going to be holding the conference here, but they didn't think it would be on such an open platform for everyone to see.

Right at this moment, a streak of black light descended out of the sky before landing on the platform to reveal a tall and imposing man clad in a suit of azure armor.

His features were quite handsome, but also extremely cold, and in particular, his gray eyes were completely devoid of emotion.

He was none other than Yin Chengquan, and even though his aura was completely restrained, the surrounding space was warping slightly around him, as if heaven and earth were bending to his will.

In this instant, he was the center of the world.

All of the bystanders present were struck by a sense of awe and veneration that arose from the bottom of their hearts, and all of the residents of Asura City fell to their knees as they chanted in a collective voice, "We pay our respects to our esteemed regional monarch!"

All of the outsiders present also paid their respects.

"Welcome to the Three Region Conference. I'm sure all of you are already aware of the objective for this conference. In order to ensure a fair, just, and open process, the conference will be held here for everyone to see, so all of you can bear witness to this momentous occasion," Yin Chengquan declared, and even though his voice wasn't very loud, it was clearly audible to everyone, as if he were speaking directly next to them.

Right at this moment, three black-robed figures emerged on the elevated platform amid a flash of black light.

They were led by a middle-aged man with a square face and bushy eyebrows, and his skin was as black as the bottom of a well-used saucepan.

"Your willingness to display such an important conference for all to see is very admirable, Regional Monarch Yin."

The middle-aged man wasn't giving off any aura, but he was somehow in perfect harmony with heaven and earth, and it seemed that he could stand toe to toe against Yin Chengquan.

The other two black-robed figures consisted of an extremely imposing young man who almost resembled a bipedal bear, while the other was a hunch-backed elderly man leaning on a wooden cane, looking as if even a stiff breeze would be sufficient to blow him over.

Both of them also had pitch-black skin.

"Those are the envoys of the Black Rope Region! The rumors are true, their skin really is completely black due to the climate in the Black Rope Region!"

"That man is the Deputy Regional Monarch of the Black Rope Region, Xiao Buye, Dao Ancestor Xiao!"

"The other two seem to be the Bright King Holy Envoy and the Heavenly Baleful Holy Envoy of the Black Rope Region's Thirteen Holy Envoys, both of whom are Great Encompassment cultivators!"

The spectators were abuzz with excited chatter.

A slightly stiff smile appeared on Yin Chengquan's cold face as he replied, "You're far too kind, Deputy Regional Monarch Xiao. Everyone has shown sufficient trust in me to set my Asura City as the conference venue, so I naturally have to live up to that trust."

Right at this moment, three more figures appeared on the elevated platform.

"I hope you won't forget what you said just now, Regional Monarch Yin."

The one who had spoken was a white-haired young man who was extremely handsome, but there was a hint of melancholy in his eyes, as if he had become completely jaded with the world after enduring countless heartbreaks.

As for the two people standing behind him, one was a middle-aged man with an extremely imposing physique. He was clad in a suit of black armor, and he was standing like an immovable iron pagoda.

The second person was an extremely beautiful woman in a white dress, and if Han Li were present, he would be stunned to discover that it was none other than Wyrm 3.

Chapter 722: Reunion

"Those people are from the Reincarnation Region! The man with the white hair is Huang Fuyu!"

"So that's Huang Fuyu. Wasn't he once the Southern Brocade Regional Monarch?"

"I heard that he was once lovers with Palace Master Xin Yu of the Reincarnation Region, but she perished during a battle against the Heavenly Court. Somehow, in his heartbreak, Huang Fuyu's cultivation base advanced drastically to become a Dao Ancestor, and he later joined the Reincarnation Region."

"The other man looks like Palace Master Wu Yang of the Reincarnation Region, but I've never seen that woman in the white dress before. On top of that, she seems to have only just reached the High Zenith Stage."

With the emergence of Wyrm 3's trio, the crowd was abuzz with conversation once again, and most of bystanders' attention was drawn to Huang Fuyu, particularly the female bystanders.

"Rest assured, Palace Master Huang, you have my word," Yin Chengquan said as he turned to the trio.

Right at this moment, numerous streaks of light shot forth from afar before landing on the elevated platform, revealing a series of peculiar figures.

"Young Dawn Regional Master Mo Zan has arrived!"

"Heavenly Map Regional Master Xi Rensong has arrived!"

"Hundred Battle Regional Master Yue Yang has arrived!"

......

These were the regional masters who were subservient to the Infernal, Black Rope, and Reincarnation Regions, but of course, in the wake of the Three Region Conference, their affiliations were going to change drastically.

All of the people on the platform were giving off formidable auras, with even the weakest ones at the Golden Immortal Stage.

The Black Teeth Regional Monarch had also arrived, and he was accompanied by Monarch Miao Gao and Monarch Lu Hong.

"Please take a seat, everyone," Yin Chengquan invited, and all of the regional monarchs sat down, while their subordinates stood behind them.

Yin Chengquan took a seat alongside everyone else, then declared, "Let the Three Region Conference begin!"

The sound of the giant gong rang out one final time, and the four pillars of white light rapidly shrank down before fading away altogether.

......

Far away from the renowned inverted street, the buildings became sparser and sparser, and even the Infernal Servants on the streets were showing up with decreased regularity.

After leaving the inverted street, Han Li's trio had concealed their own auras as they made their way toward the Hundred Treasure Area.

Even though there were fewer pedestrians on the street, they encountered more groups of patrolling Infernal Servants.

In contrast with normal Infernal Servants, these ones were all clad in suits of black armor that only protected the chest and midsection while leaving the arms and legs exposed, appearing quite light and nimble.

The baleful qi emanating from their bodies was remarkably formidable, and they were led by a Grand Ascension cultivator, while the rest were mostly at the Body Integration and Spatial Tempering Stages.

All of them were conducting patrols along set routes, so it wasn't that difficult to avoid them.

Before long, Han Li's trio had snuck past several patrol groups and arrived on the border of the Tarmin and the Hundred Treasure Areas.

Just like on the border of Asura City, a massive black wall stood between the two areas. There were all types of strange runes engraved onto the wall, and it was enshrouded in a layer of murky gray mist, making it impossible to see clearly.

Constructed above the city gates was a three-story-tall black palace, several thousand feet to the left and right of which was a pair of turrets, and an armorclad Infernal Servant was stationed every ten steps between the palace and the turrets.

The city gates were tightly shut, and there were two armored giants that were over a hundred feet tall stationed outside. They were very similar to humans in appearance, except they were all bald with square faces and large mouths, as well as protruding tusks, presenting hideous sight to behold.

At this moment, Han Li was hiding under a gray rock several thousand feet away from the city gates, and Mo Guang and Shi Chuankong were also concealed under rocks of their own not far away.

Thanks to the spatial secret technique unleashed by Shi Chuankong, they were able to avoid detection even though they were already quite close to the city gates.

Shi Chuankong took a glance at a lifeless body of an armorclad Infernal Servant laying on the ground nearby, then communicated to Han Li and Mo Guang through voice transmission, "It looks like the information we obtained from the soul search is largely correct. There are special restrictions placed on the city walls, and the two giants at the city gates appear to be Copper Spine beings, presumably at or above the True Immortal Stage."

"They're not a cause for concern, the main problem is that there seems to be a Great Encompassment Stage Infernal being stationed in that palace. It won't be easy for us to get past him," Han Li said with slightly furrowed brows.

"I can get us through the city wall quite easily with my spatial powers, but what's difficult is doing so while ensuring that we don't alert that Infernal being," Shi Chuankong said with tightly furrowed brows.

"It's fine, just focus on getting us through, and I'll help you conceal the resulting aura fluctuations," Mo Guang assured with a casual smile.

"You have a way to fool that Great Encompassment Stage Infernal being?" Han Li asked in a skeptical manner.

"Do you not trust me?" Mo Guang asked with a smile.

"A Great Encompassment cultivator is far beyond what we can handle. If he's alerted to our presence, we won't even be able to get away, so if we're going to act, then we have to ensure that there's no chance of us being caught," Shi Chuankong said in a concerned manner.

"Fellow Daoist Han, there are some secrets concealed in this body of mine that you're not yet aware of. I wouldn't raise such a proposal if I wasn't confident in my abilities, so trust me on this one," Mo Guang said.

Han Li hesitated momentarily upon hearing this, then acquiesced, "I trust you."

Shi Chuankong's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he seemed to want to say something, but ultimately suppressed the urge to do so.

"Let's go somewhere else. We have to avoid the palace and the turrets and find a weaker point in the city wall to breach," Mo Guang said.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong nodded in response, and the three of them moved toward the east in a stealthy fashion.

After traveling eastward for close to a hundred kilometers, Han Li suddenly declared through voice transmission, "Stop for a second, someone's onto us..."

Shi Chuankong instantly stopped cold in his tracks upon hearing this. He hadn't detected anything amiss, nor had Mo Guang.

Right at this moment, a familiar voice rang out.

"Don't be alarmed, Brother Shi, Fellow Daoist Li, it's us."

Han Li and Shi Chuankong exchanged a glance with each other, and both of them could see their own surprise mirrored in one another's eyes.

Immediately thereafter, the nearby space warped slightly, following which two figures emerged, one of whom was none other than Fox 3.

He was accompanied by yet another familiar figure to Han Li, namely Baili Yan.

An elated look appeared on Shi Chuankong's face upon seeing this, and he asked, "Fox 3, what are you doing here? And who's this?"

"Long time no see, Brother Shi, Fellow Daoist Li. This is Fellow Daoist Baili Yan, and he's also from our Reincarnation Palace," Fox 3 introduced with a smile, following which he turned to Mo Guang with a slightly bewildered look in his eyes.

Baili Yan had already met Mo Guang back in the San Miao Tribe, and he had heard about Mo Guang from Han Li, so he wasn't all that surprised.

After briefly introducing Mo Guang to Fox 3, Han Li asked, "What are you two doing together?"

"That's a long story. Back when the True Mantra Sect ruins collapsed, I was sucked into this realm by a spatial vortex, and I almost perished to a Baleful Bone Demon. Thankfully, I had enough pills and Immortal Origin Stones on me to scrape by, and later ran into Fellow Daoist Baili," Fox 3 explained with a slightly awkward expression.

This was quite different from Fox 3's normal lackadaisical demeanor, so Han Li knew that he had to have been hiding something, and he turned to Baili Yan with an inquisitive look.

"After I left the San Miao Tribe, I went to the East Lake Region and the Square Hill Region, and I encountered Fox 3 in the Ring Shark Tribe. At the time, he was locked up in prison awaiting his execution for attempting to steal the Ring Shark Tribe's secret treasure.

“Thankfully, the Ring Shark Tribe had already decided to join the Reincarnation Region, so they handed him over to me as a gift, and we came here together after that," Baili Yan explained with a wry smile.

Han Li turned to Fox 3 with a speechless expression upon hearing this, while Shi Chuankong jibed, "Well, well, well, I thought you had a near-spotless record."

"I was feeling a little under the weather in a new realm, but that's all in the past, let's discuss the matter at hand," Fox 3 replied in a slightly bashful manner.

"How did you find us?" Han Li asked.

"I knew you came here with the San Miao Tribe, but I didn't see you there, so I assumed you must've set off for the Baleful Cleansing Pond," Baili Yan explained.

"We are indeed planning to travel to the Baleful Cleansing Pond," Han Li replied with a nod.

"That's perfect! We can all go together, and with our combined powers, our chances of success should be a little higher," Fox 3 said.

"Sounds good to me," Han Li agreed as he took a glance at Baili Yan.

Even though Mo Guang possessed the highest cultivation base of the three, it was clear that Han Li was the leader of the group, and neither Mo Guang nor Shi Chuankong raised any objections.

With that, the five of them set off once again, traveling eastward for close to another hundred kilometers before stopping again.

"This is a good place to stop. If we keep going, there will be another watchtower, and that one could also have a high-grade Infernal being stationed in it, so let's make our move here," Mo Guang said.

Atop the city wall was a row of armorclad Infernal Servants standing in a uniform formation, looking directly up ahead.

"The restrictions on these city walls are primarily for fortification and alert purposes, so we'll have to get a little closer if we want to pass through without being detected," Shi Chuankong said.

"Leave that to me," Fox 3 said as he flipped a hand over to produce a round crystal ball.

Chapter 723: Fortresses

As Fox 3 chanted an incantation, a layer of rainbow light appeared over the surface of the crystal ball, then swept up everyone in a flash.

All of a sudden, Han Li's group had completely disappeared, and even their auras had been entirely concealed.

"Is this an illusion, Fellow Daoist Fox 3?" Han Li asked.

"You can say that. This layer of light can't come into contact with any sensory restrictions. Otherwise, we'll be exposed right away. Time is of the essence, so let's get moving," Fox 3 replied with a nod, and the group made its way to the foot of the balck city wall under the concealment of the layer of rainbow light.

Sure enough, they attracted no attention at all the entire time, and the armorclad Infernal Servants continued to stand still on the spot, looking out into the distance.

"Are we close enough now?" Fox 3 asked.

"Hold on, I have to prepare some things."

Shi Chuankong began to summon a series of array tools and Baleful Inkstone as he spoke, then arranged them onto the ground.

"You can use those things to set up arrays? I thought you only purcahsed them for that demon core," Han Li said with a slightly surprised expression.

"When it comes to setting up spatial arrays, it's best to use native materials. We have Fellow Daoist Mo Guang with us anyway, and I can teach him how to activate the array," Shi Chuankong replied with a smile, then returned to his work.

Han Li carefully observed the process, and he discovered that the array that Shi Chuankong was setting up was extremely complex. It was similar to a teleportation array, but also clearly different, and he wasn't able to glean much from it.

Some time later, Fox 3 urged, "Is it ready yet, Brother Shi? My Shadow Illusion Crystal won't be able to last much longer."

Shi Chuankong embedded one final array plate into the ground, then wiped the sweat from his forehead as he stood up straight and replied, "It's ready. Everyone, stand in the array."

Everyone immediately stepped into the array upon hearing this. The array wasn't very large, just enough to fit the five of them.

After learning the activation method from Shi Chuankong, Mo Guang nodded and replied, "The array isn't difficult to activate. Just do your best to restrain your auras, and I'll conceal the aura fluctuations from the array's activation."

He then raised a finger, and a plume of baleful qi instantly began to surge out of the tip of the finger, enveloping everyone like a cloud of black mist.

Immediately thereafter, he began to chant an incantation, and bursts of spatial fluctuations emerged from the array down below, but they were completely contained within the surrounding wall of baleful qi.

"Let's go!" Mo Guang declared, and in the same instant, Fox 3's Shadow Illusion Crystal shattered.

Everyone within the array vanished in a flash, and one of the Infernal Servants on the city wall seemed to have detected something as he looked down at the foot of the city wall, where he saw a gust of wind stir up a cloud of dust.

He hurriedly swept his spiritual sense over the area, but discovered nothing amiss, and there was no reaction from the restrictions placed on the city wall, either, so he shook his head and began to look out into the distance again.

Meanwhile, Han Li's group emerged on a small brick path, then began to rush deeper into the city in a stealthy fashion.

Perhaps it was due to the ongoing Three Region Conference, but the Hundred Treasure Area seemed very quiet and bleak. The buildings in the city were primarily quite short, with the exception of some fortress-like pagodas, stationed atop which were more armorclad Infernal Servants.

Some Infernal Servant patrol groups could be seen traversing through the streets in the city, and the occasional group even had True Immortal Stage leaders.

"Security is clearly tighter here in the Hundred Treasure Area, so we have to be more careful," Shi Chuankong said.

"It seems like the map that we have is rather inaccurate. On the way here, I noticed many watchtowers that weren't marked out on the map," Mo Guang said.

"That's not a surprise. Our map came from before the access restrictions in Asura City came into effect, and any changes that took place after that naturally won't appear on the map. As long as the general layout is correct, we should be fine," Han Li replied.

"It seems like the general layout is quite accurate. There are three routes that we can take to the border of the Rashom Area, two of which lead to the city gate, while the other leads to a turrret in the northwest," Mo Guang said.

"Let's go take a look at the turret. If we go to the city gate, there will most likely be a Great Encompassment cultivator stationed there," Han Li proposed.

No one raised any objections to this, and thus, they began to traverse carefully through the Hundred Treasure Area, making sure to avoid the watchtowers and patrol groups.

As they progressed deeper into the city, they encountered more and more patrol groups, and even with their lofty cultivation bases, they had to be on high alert at all times and proceed with a great deal of caution.

Close to two hours flew by in a flash, and the five of them finally arrived in the central region of the Hundred Treasure Area, where they hid behind a tall building to rest.

Han Li inspected his surroundings with slightly furrowed brows, and he could sense that a bone-chilling sensation had suddenly arisen in the air, while layers of frost had emerged on the nearby ground and walls.

At this point in the city, there were no longer any normal buildings. Instead, the streets were lined with massive black fortresses that stretched as far as the eyes could see.

Several giant chimneys were protruding out of the clusters of fortresses, releasing plumes of thick smoke up into the sky, looking much like some type of large factory.

There was a marked increase in the number of patrol groups in this area, and occasionally, streaks of light would fly across the sky, inspecting everything down below.

Fox 3's eyes lit up slightly at the sight of the clusters of fortresses up ahead, and he said through voice transmission, "The fact that there are so many guards indicates that this is no ordinary area. Perhaps some secret of the Infernal Tribe is being concealed here."

"That has nothing to do with us, our top priority is to find the Baleful Cleansing Pond. This is a very seriuos situation, so don't go causing any trouble, Fox 3," Shi Chuankong warned with a stern exrpession.

"I know, I know, I'll behave," Fox 3 replied with a faint smile, but Shi Chuankong remained unconvinced and continued to keep a close eye on Fox 3.

Han Li took a glance at the two of them, then also cast his gaze toward the black fortresses while also releasing a wisp of spiritual sense in that direction.

His spiritual sense had only seeped slightly into the wall of the fortress before it was repelled, and a hint of surprise flashed through his eyes as he hurriedly withdrew his spiritual sense.

Right at this moment, Shi Qinghou's voice rang out in his mind.

"Do you want to know what they're doing in there?"

"Can you tell me?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"These walls contain the Infernal Great Concealment Restriction. It's a secret restriction of the Infernal Tribe, but it's not that difficult to bypass. I'll pass the method onto you, and you can see for yourself," Shi Qinghou replied, following which a profound restriction breaking method was transmitted into Han Li's mind.

Instead of being elated by this development, Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he asked, "Why do you want me to see what's happening in there?"

However, Shi Qinghou had fallen silent again, displaying no intention of answering Han Li's question.

Han Li's expression darkened slightly, but after a brief hesitation, he released a wisp of his spiritual sense toward the wall up ahead once again.

A burst of invisible force instantly emerged within the wall to stop his spiritual sense in its tracks, but as soon as Han Li began to implement the restriction breaking method taught to him by Shi Qinghou, the restriction quickly softened before fusing as one with his spiritual sense.

Immediately thereafter, his spiritual sense was able to seep through with ease, allowing him to see what was on the other side.

Inside the fortress was a massive basin that was around two hundred to three hundred feet in size, and it was filled with bubbling gray liquid that looked as if it were boiling.

Submerged in the basin were four black metal cages, held captive within which were two Gray Realm beasts and a pair of Gray Realm beings with cow horns on their heads.

The two gray beasts were shrieking in agony while struggling with all their might, attempting to break free from the cage, but to no avail.

As for the two Gray Realm beings, they weren't struggling or screaming. Instead, they were laying in their cages as stiff as a pair of boards with extremely wooden expressions, and only the occasional movement of their eyes indicated that they were still alive.

These two Gray Realm beings seemed to have been submerged in the basin for too long, to the point that their skin had turned gray in color, presenting an unsettling sight to behold.

Additionally, there were also two Infernal Servants in the fortress, closely observing the scene that was unfolding within the basin.

Han Li was quite surprised to see this, but he didn't linger for long in this fortress. Instead, he quickly moved on to the next fortress.

This one had no basin in it, but in its place was a huge furnace, beneath which was a raging gray flame, but strangely enough, it was giving off an intense chill rather than any heat.

Hanging within the furnace were several Gray Realm beings and gray beasts, and bursts of gray light were surging out of the furnace before quickly fusing into their bodies, which rapidly swelled in size like balloons, while a series of peculiar patterns emerged over their skin.

Han Li's spiritual sense lingered here briefly before venturing onward, and in the blink of an eye, he had examined around a dozen black fortresses, each of which housed a different body refinement method, including boiling, burning, or exposure to lethal poison.

The Gray Realm beings went through their refinement stations in a set sequence, and their bodies took on all types of different forms.

In the end, these monstrous creations were far more powerful than before, but they had lost all sentience and been reduced to puppets with wooden expressions, all of which were locked up in huge metal cages in the final fortress.

Chapter 724: Splitting Up

Han Li was quite surprised by what he was seeing in these fortresses.

It seemed that these unremarkable-looking fortresses were some type of puppet refinement facility for the Infernal Tribe. This was an extremely inhumane refinement process, so it was no wonder that it had to be kept hidden from the general public.

On top of that, the Infernal Tribe had already become so proficient in this strange puppet refinement process that they were able to produce these puppets in large batches.

Infernal beings were quite rare, but not only were they very powerful, they were also able to control Infernal Servants and mass-produce these puppets, so it was no wonder that they had become the ruling tribe of the Infernal Region.

After some further observation, Han Li withdrew his spiritual sense back to the fortress that housed the basin, then released it in another direction, quickly arriving in another giant fortress.

This fortress contained a series of prisons of different sizes that were tightly packed together like a beehive.

Some of these prisons contained different types of gray beasts, while the rest housed different types of Gray Realm beings. All of them were completely nude with soulless looks in their eyes, and these prisons were intentionally designed to be very short, so these people were forced onto all fours, just like the gray beasts.

These were the "raw materials" used for the puppet refinement process, and there were thousands of them, some of which were even at the True Immortal and Golden Immortal Stages.

However, the prisons for these powerful beings were also specially designed to ensure that they wouldn't be able to escape.

Han Li had already spent quite some time inspecting these fortresses, and he quickly withdrew his spiritual sense.

Shi Chuankong and the others were naturally oblivious to what he had just seen, and having taken a brief rest, the group continued onward.

The five of them carefully advanced through the Hundred Treasure Area according to their map, and they quickly arrived at the area's northwestern border.

There was a massive turret hanging above the city wall not far away, and it was identical to the one drawn on the map.

The turret was enshrouded within a glowing black restriction, and there were many armorclad Infernal Servants standing on guard duty nearby.

Han Li's group was observing the city wall from a hidden location, and at this moment, all of them were feeling a little more relaxed.

They had already completed the most difficult segment of the journey, and all they had to do now was employ the same method as before to pass through this city wall.

"Fellow Daoist Shi, we'll have to count on you to get us through again," Han Li said as he turned to Shi Chuankong.

"Not a problem. However, I'll need Brother Fox to get us close to the city wall," Shi Chuankong replied with a nod.

"Leave it to me," Fox 3 declared, then flipped a hand over to produce another one of the round crystal balls from before.

A layer of rainbow light emerged over the crystal ball at his behest, then encompassed everyone in a flash, following which the entire group vanished on the spot.

Under the cover of the rainbow light, the group quickly arrived at the foot of the city wall, where Shi Chuankong began setting up another teleportation array.

With a sweep of his sleeve, a streak of silver light fell upon the teleportation array, while Mo Guang was also releasing plumes of baleful qi out of his sleeve, enshrouding the entire array within a cloud of black mist to conceal all of its aura fluctuations.

However, after the teleportation array lit up, Han Li and the others merely swayed slightly on the spot, but didn't disappear like last time.

Han Li and others all turned to Shi Chuankong with surprised expressions upon seeing this.

At this moment, Shi Chuankong was looking a little pale, and he turned to the city wall with a grim expression.

"What's wrong, Brother Shi?" Fox 3 asked.

"Let's go back first."

Instead of immediately elaborating on why the teleportation had failed, Shi Chuankong swept a sleeve through the air to stow away all of his array tools, then returned to their hiding spot.

Everyone hurriedly followed along, and once they were concealed again, Baili Yan asked, "What happened back there, Fellow Daoist Shi? Why did the teleportation fail?"

"Could it be that there's an additional spatial restriction in the city wall?" Han Li asked.

"Are you familiar with spatial teleportation secret techniques as well, Fellow Daoist Li? That's exactly what's happened. With that spatial restriction in place, my teleportation secret technique has been rendered ineffective," Shi Chuankong replied.

Everyone's expressions darkened slightly upon hearing this.

The Hundred Treasure Area was enshrouded in layers upon layers of restrictions, and aside from Shi Chuankong's teleportation secret technique, there was no other way for them to reach the Rashom Area.

"Are we going to have to give up after coming all this way?" Baili Yan asked with an indignant expression.

"Not necessarily, all we have to do is deactivate the spatial restriction in the city wall," Shi Chuankong said.

"Deactivate the spatial restriction? Surely that's far easier said than done. We don't even know where the core of the spatial restriction is," Baili Yan said with tightly furrowed brows.

"I presume you only raised this option because you already have a rough idea of how to accomplish it, right, Fellow Daoist Shi?" Han Li asked, and everyone immediately turned to Shi Chuankong.

"I did indeed notice something just now. Given how powerful the restrictions within the city wall are, the core of the array must be nearby. I think it's either in that turret or the city gates there," Shi Chuankong replied.

"In that case, let's split up. Brother Shi, Fellow Daoist Li, and I will go one way, while Fellow Daoist Mo and Fellow Daoist Baili go the other way, and we'll search for the core of the array at the entrance of the city gates and in this turret," Fox 3 proposed.

In terms of concealment abilities, Fox 3 and Mo Guang were the most proficient of the group, so this was a sound plan, and no one raised any objections.

"Fellow Daoist Baili and I should be able to sneak into this turret with no problems, but if you're going to the city gates, you could encounter the Great Encompassment cultivator stationed here, so make sure to be careful," Mo Guang cautioned.

"Rest assured, I've already made some preparations. Just because you're going to the turret doesn't mean you can let your guard down. Also, take this teleportation array plate, it can facilitate teleportation over short distances. Once we've found the spatial restriction, we'll meet back up using these array plates," Shi Chuankong replied with a confident smile, then summoned an octagonal silver jade plate that he handed to Mo Guang.

"The Vast Origin House is certainly never short on resources," Mo Guang remarked with a smile as he accepted the jade plate.

"Hold on a second, even if we manage to find the core of the array, we'll inevitably attract some attention if we try to destroy it. If we draw the attention of the Great Encompassment cultivator here, we'll be in a world of trouble," Han Li suddenly said.

Everyone's expressions darkened slightly as this problem also dawned on them.

"It's fine. As long as we can find the core of the array, I'll have a way to take care of it," Shi Chuankong assured with a faint smile.

Han Li took a surprised glance at Shi Chuankong upon hearing this, but didn't say anything.

"In that case, we'll be counting on you, Fellow Daoist Shi."

After some further discussion, everyone split up and went their separate ways.

Han Li's trio made its way toward the city gates. There weren't many patrolling Infernal Servants near the city walls, so it didn't take them long to arrive at the city gates, which were tightly shut.

Constructed above the city gates was a three-story-tall black palace, on either side of which was a smaller turret, and the three buildings were connected by a stone path that was crawling with armorclad Infernal Servants.

There were also many armorclad Infernal Servants standing on either side of the city gates down below, and a grim look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

They were about to sneak into a palace that was likely to be holding a Great Encompassment cultivator, and he couldn't help but feel a little anxious.

Even Fox 3 had adopted a serious expression as he turned to Shi Chuankong and asked, "Brother Shi, do you really have a way to avoid a Great Encompassment cultivator's detection?"

He had been captured by a Great Encompassment Stage being back at the Ring Shark Tribe, so he had firsthand experience of just how formidable such beings were.

"I can't say for sure, but at the very least, I have a great deal of confidence that it'll work," Shi Chuankong replied with a smile, then pulled three white talismans out of his sleeve.

The talismans were each three inches in length and around an inch wide, and they were riddled with thin black patterns to form an extremely complex design.

The talismans were flashing with black and white light, but they weren't giving off even the faintest of auras, and Han Li and Fox 3 were stunned to discover that they were completely unable to detect the talismans with their spiritual sense.

"These are concealment talismans refined by a Great Encompassment cultivator of our Vast Origin House. As long as there's no Great Encompassment cultivator directly scrutinizing us, these talismans should be sufficient for us to sneak through," Shi Chuankong said as he handed a talisman each to Han Li and Fox 3.

Both Fox 3 and Han Li were stunned to hear this.

"These talismans are far too precious, Fellow Daoist Shi. What would you like in exchange for them?" Han Li asked.

"There's no need to compensate me, Fellow Daoist Li. If it wasn't for you, I would already be dead and buried in the Gray Realm by now, so how can I ask for anything in exchange for a mere talisman? Right now, our top priority is to bypass this spatial restriction and enter the Soul Cleansing Area so we can find the Baleful Cleansing Pond," Shi Chuankong replied with a smile.

"Don't worry about him, Fellow Daoist Li. I've known him for a very long time, and he's ridiculously wealthy, so there's no need to feel guilty at all for taking things from him," Fox 3 said to Han Li as he grabbed a talisman without any hesitation.

"Fellow Daoist Li is a true gentleman. Not everyone is a shameless thief like you," Shi Chuankong scoffed as he glared at Fox 3, who remained completely unfazed.

"In that case, you have my thanks, Fellow Daoist Shi," Han Li said as he also took one of the talismans.

Chapter 725: Diversion

"By the way, these talismans can only last an hour, so we have to complete our search of this place within that span of time," Shi Chuankong said, then opened his mouth to swallow his talisman.

Immediately thereafter, black and white light began to ripple over his body, following which he slowly faded into the surrounding space.

Han Li and Fox 3 followed suit, and both of them quickly vanished as well.

Due to the fact that they were using the same talisman, they were able to sense one another, so they weren't completely in the dark.

"Let's go. The core of the spatial restriction could be in this palace or either of the two turrets, so let's search through them one by one," Shi Chuankong said as he flew toward the turret on the left.

There were many armorclad Infernal Servants stationed near the turret, but their cultivation bases were all quite lackluster, so there was no way that they would be able to detect Han Li's trio.

The three of them flew into the turret, and it wasn't very large, so it didn't take them long to complete their inspection.

Inside were several residential rooms that were all empty at the moment, but judging from the items within them, they seemed to be occupied by the leaders of the guards.

Han Li's trio quickly emerged from the turret, and Shi Chuankong said through voice transmission, "It's probably a similar story in the other turret, so let's not waste any time and head straight to the palace."

Han Li and Fox 3 were of the same opinion, and thus, the three of them quickly flew over to the entrance of the black palace.

Looking at the palace up ahead, Han Li's pupils contracted ever so slightly.

The interior of the palace was dimly lit, and it resembled a terrifying devilish mouth threatening to devour everything that ventured into it.

However, it then occurred to him that this was most likely an illusion that had arisen from the pressure of potentially having to face a Great Encompassment Stage Infernal being, and he took a deep breath to stifle his apprehension.

Shi Chuankong seemed to have also entered a brief daze, and after returning to his senses, he led the way toward the palace.

"Let's go."

The three of them flew into the palace, and they entered a huge cylindrical hall that was around forty to fifty feet tall with a diameter of around four hundred to five hundred feet. The walls and ground were all pitch black, and there were several black crystals the size of human heads embedded into the walls, giving off a faint black glow.

There were three paths deep in the hall, with the left and right ones each leading to a side hall, while the one in the middle extended up toward the second floor.

Instead of immediately making their way up to the second floor, the group split up to examine the two side halls.

However, they quickly came together again and arrived on the path leading to the second floor.

Both of the side halls were warehouses that were laden with things like armor and weapons, and they clearly didn't contain what Han Li's trio was searching for.

"It looks like it must be up there. Great Encompassment Stage beings are far more sensitive than we can imagine, so proceed with the utmost caution," Shi Chuankong cautioned in a solemn voice.

Both Han Li and Fox 3 nodded in response, and the trio quickly arrived on the second floor.

Just like the first floor, the second floor was also a cylindrical hall, but there were several thick stone pillars on this floor, all of which were engraved with demonic dragons that were roaring to the heavens.

There were also three passageways deep within the hall, leading to a pair of side halls and the third floor, respectively.

As soon as they arrived on the second floor, Shi Chuankong immediately turned to the side hall on the left with an elated expression.

"I can sense spatial fluctuation there!"

Han Li and Fox 3 were also ecstatic to hear this.

However, right at this moment a white blur suddenly shot out of the passageway leading to the third floor, and it was a furry little white beast.

The beast was only around a foot in length, and its entire body was covered in soft white fur. It resembled a civet cat in appearance, but its eyes were enormous, taking up virtually half of its face, presenting a rather peculiar sight to behold.

The little white beast was flying around the second floor in a playful manner, seemingly entertaining itself.

Han Li's trio was given quite a fright by the little beast, but they were relieved to see that it was merely playing on its own.

"It's alright, just ignore it," Shi Chuankong said through voice transmission, yet right as he was about to make his way toward the side hall on the left, the little beast suddenly stopped in its tracks, then turned to Han Li before releasing a burst of white ripples toward Han Li's trio out of its eyes.

"Get back!"

Shi Chuankong's expression changed drastically as he grabbed onto Fox 3 before retreating back toward the second-floor passageway, and Han Li reacted even faster, darting back in retreat as soon as he saw the little beast turning to look at them.

Thankfully, the three of them were standing right next to the passageway, so they were able to instantly flee into it.

However, the white ripples continued to pursue them into the passageway, and the three of them didn't dare to use any immortal spiritual power, so their speed was limited.

The white ripples were quickly gaining on them, and an urgent look appeared on Shi Chuankong's face upon seeing this. He gritted his teeth as he grabbed onto Han Li with his other hand, then began to chant a rapid incantation.

A burst of law powers surged out of his body before entering the pair of concealment talismans that Han Li and Fox 3 had just swallowed.

The three talismans shuddered violently before shattering altogether, transforming into a burst of peculiar power that spread through their bodies.

In an instant, they were able to vanish into the wall of the passageway without a trace.

In the same instant, the white ripples spread through the entire passageway and the walls on either side of it, but at this point, Han Li's trio was already completely undetectable.

The little white beast cocked its head to the side with a hint of befuddlement in its eyes.

"What's wrong, Cloudball?"

A figure emerged from the third-floor passageway, and it was a tall and thin middle-aged man.

The man had a pair of long and narrow eyes, and his skin was deathly pale, giving him the harrowing appearance of a drowned body that had just been fished out of the water.

A burst of forbidding baleful qi was emanating from his body, striking one with the urge to get as far away from him as possible.

Right at this moment, a black figure flew up from the first floor, and it was a black-robed Infernal Servant.

There were plumes of black qi surging out of his black robe to encompass his entire body, giving him a rather indistinct, ghostly appearance.

The black-robed Infernal Servant faltered slightly at the sight of the pale middle-aged man, following which he fell to his knees and offered up a black voice transmission talisman with both hands as he said in a respectful voice, "Master Gui Mu, I bring a message from the esteemed regional monarch."

The little white beast observed the Infernal Servant for a moment, following which the white ripples surging out of its eyes faded, and it flew into Gui Mu's arms.

Gui Mu held the little beast in his arms, gently stroking its soft fur with one hand while accepting the talisman with the other before injecting his spiritual sense into it.

Shortly thereafter, he crushed the talisman in his hand, then said in a coarse and grating voice, "Tell the regional monarch that the preparations in the puppet fortresses are already complete."

The Infernal Servant gave an affirmative response, then flew away as a black shadow, vanishing in the blink of an eye.

Gui Mu paced back and forth in the hall with the little beast in his arms for a while, seemingly contemplating something, then returned to the third floor.

A short while later, Han Li's trio re-emerged from the wall of the passageway.

Instead of making their way up to the second floor again, they snuck back down to the first floor and hid themselves in one of the side halls.

Only then did they allow themselves a sigh of relief.

"That was way too close! What was that thing just now? It detected us right away!" Fox 3 said with a hint of lingering fear in his eyes.

"I'm assuming it must be some type of special gray beast. Looks like we were too complacent," Han Li said, then quickly swallowed a pill.

"As expected, Great Encompassment cultivators are not to be underestimated. Just a spirit pet of his was almost enough to blow our cover," Shi Chuankong sighed.

The three of them were all looking rather grim. They had thought that the concealment talismans would've been enough for them to get to the core of the array without too much trouble, but it seemed that they had been overly optimistic.

"By the way, what happened to the talismans in our bodies, Fellow Daoist Shi? Mine seems to have shattered," Han Li suddenly asked.

"The situation was quite urgent, so I completely unleashed the power of the talismans to enhance its concealment effect. However, now that I've done that, the amount of time that the talismans will be able to last has been reduced by half, so they'll probably fail after around fifteen more minutes," Shi Chuankong replied in a grim voice.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, while Fox 3 said in an urgent voice, "In that case, we have to hurry! That little beast was carried away by Gui Mu just now, should we give it another crack?"

If they were to lose the cover of the concealment talismans, there would be no chance for them to make any further progress.

"We can't do that, it's too dangerous," Shi Chuankong immediately said.

"Indeed. It seems like our only option is to divert Gui Mu away," Han Li mused.

"Divert him away? Do you have a plan to do that, Fellow Daoist Li?" Shi Chuankong hurriedly asked, and Fox 3 also turned to him.

"The plan is very simple. The black fortresses that we passed by on the way here are actually the Infernal Tribe's puppet refinement facility, and they contain some secrets that can't be displayed to the general public. All we have to do is think of a way to cause a disturbance there, and Gui Mu will most likely leave right away," Han Li explained.

"You were able to see into those fortresses?" Fox 3 asked with a surprised expression. "I was really curious about what was inside, but my spiritual sense wasn't able to breach their walls."

"That sounds like a plan, but right now, we're a little far away from that area, and I don't think we'll have enough time to go there and back," Shi Chuankong said with slightly furrowed brows.

"Get Fellow Daoist Mo Guang and Fellow Daoist Baili to go. They're closer to that area, and once they're done, just get them back to us using that teleportation array plate of yours," Han Li said.

Chapter 726: Every Second Counts

"That's a good idea, I'll contact them right away," Shi Chuankong said, and he was just about to make a hand seal when Han Li interrupted him.

"Allow me, Fellow Daoist Shi. There are some things that I have to tell them about what's happening inside the puppet refinement fortresses. We have to make sure that they can create a sufficient disturbance while ensuring that Gui Mu doesn't detect any signs of foul play."

Shi Chuankong nodded in response, and Han Li contacted Mo Guang through their spiritual connection, then informed him of their current situation and the plan that they had devised.

"A puppet refinement facility? No wonder the area was tightly guarded. It won't be difficult to stir up some unrest there, and I can definitely do so without leaving any traceable signs behind, but the restrictions there are quite advanced, and it'll be quite difficult to sneak into the facility," Mo Guang replied.

"That's not a problem, I have a secret technique to bypass the restrictions," Han Li said, then relayed Shi Qinghou's secret technique to Mo Guang.

"Alright, in that case, there shouldn't be any problems," Mo Guang replied.

"As soon as Gui Mu leaves, I'll get Shi Chuankong to teleport the two of you to us. Make sure to be extra careful and don't leave behind any aura fluctuations for Gui Mu to detect," Han Li cautioned in a serious voice.

Mo Guang gave an affirmative response before cutting off the voice transmission, and Han Li opened his eyes before giving Shi Chuankong and Fox 3 a brief recount of his conversation with Mo Guang.

"Alright, let's make some preparations here as well to ensure that the plan is successful," Shi Chuankong said, then made a hand seal, and four black talismans flew out of his sleeves, carrying the words East, West, South, and North in ancient text.

The four talismans adhered themselves to the walls of the side hall at his behest, following which he strode over to the entrance of the side hall to observe what was happening outside.

Han Li and Fox 3 were also waiting anxiously, and several minutes passed by without anything happening.

"What's going on? Has something gone wrong on Mo Guang's end?" Fox 3 asked in an urgent voice.

The concealment effect of their talismans was about to wear off.

After some contemplation, Han Li decided not to contact Mo Guang through voice transmission for fear of distracting him, and he said, "It'll take some time for the two of them to get to the puppet refinement facility, so let's wait a little longer."

As soon as his voice trailed off, a faint thump rang out in the distance, as if something had exploded, and this was immediately followed by another dull thump.

Han Li's trio faltered slightly upon hearing this, following which ecstatic looks appeared on their faces.

A thick column of black smoke was rising up from the puppet refinement fortresses, accompanied by the sound of rumbling explosions, and the Infernal Servants near the city gates immediately erupted into a panicked frenzy upon seeing this.

"Something's happening at the puppet refinement fortresses! We have to report to Master Gui Mu!" one of the Infernal Servants yelled.

Right at this moment, Gui Mu appeared out of thin air outside of the palace, and he was holding the same white beast as before with an alarmed look on his face.

Immediately thereafter, he stomped a foot down onto the ground and began flying toward the puppet refinement fortresses as a streak of black light.

Shi Chuankong was ecstatic to see this, and he immediately made a hand seal, upon which the four talismans adhered to the walls of the side hall began to radiate dazzling black light, forming a black light barrier in the blink of an eye.

Immediately thereafter, he flipped a hand over to produce an octagonal silver jade plate identical to the one that he had given to Mo Guang, then opened his mouth to release a burst of silver light into it.

The jade plate instantly began to glow brightly while revolving rapidly and releasing countless silver runes to form a silver array that was around ten feet in size.

In the next instant, Mo Guang and Baili Yan appeared within the array with elated looks on their faces, but their elation quickly turned to befuddlement as they were unable to see Han Li's trio at all.

"We've concealed ourselves using a secret technique," Shi Chuankong explained in a concise fashion as he cast a pair of incantation seals into their bodies, thereby allowing them to just barely make out the outlines of Han Li's trio.

"How did it go?" Han Li asked.

"It went very smoothly. I used my heavenly devil secret technique to drive a Golden Immortal Stage gray beast wild, and it went on a rampage, destroying several of the arrays in the facility. I left no traces behind, and I can guarantee that even a Great Encompassment cultivator wouldn't be able to detect anything," Mo Guang replied.

"Good. We don't have much time left, let's go to the core of the spatial restriction!"

Shi Chuankong stowed the pair of jade plates away as he spoke, then peeled the four talismans off the walls before flying up toward the second floor.

In the blink of an eye, the entire group arrived on the second floor before rushing over to the entrance of the side hall on the left.

The doors of the side hall were tightly shut, and not only was Fox 3 unable to push them open, a layer of black light appeared over their surface as soon as an attempt to open them was made.

"There's another restriction here!" Fox 3 exclaimed, and everyone's expressions darkened slightly upon seeing this.

"I'll take care of it," Han Li stepped forward as he activated his Infernal Devilish Eyes while also releasing his spiritual sense toward the black restriction.

The restriction was quite similar to the Infernal Great Concealment Restriction placed upon the puppet refinement facility, so Han Li had a rough idea of how to bypass it.

Mo Guang raised a hand to conjure up a black light barrier that encompassed both Han Li and the entrance of the side hall, ensuring that no aura fluctuations escaped.

At the same time, Han Li made a rapid string of hand seals, casting a stream of incantation seals into the black restriction, which began to flash erratically as countless black runes emerged onto its surface.

Han Li carefully scrutinized all of the changes in the restriction with his Infernal Devilish Eyes, and all of a sudden, his eyes lit up as he thrust the palms of both of his hands into the restriction.

The black restriction flashed one final time before its light quickly faded, and the doors swung open.

Shi Chuankong and the others were ecstatic, and they immediately flew into the side hall.

Han Li gently closed the doors, and much to his relief, the black restriction on them immediately began to make a rapid recovery.

The side hall was quite large, more so than the two side halls on the first floor, and there were eight stone platforms arranged in a certain formation within it. Each platform was laden with array tools, and they formed the cores of different restrictions.

Thick pillars of light were rising up out of the stone platforms into the ceiling of the side hall, where a series of extremely complex array patterns had been engraved, all of which were flashing incessantly.

At this moment, Shi Chuankong and the others were standing beside the stone platform that was at the very back of the room. All of the array tools on this platform were silver in color, and rising up from it was a thick pillar of silver light that was giving off formidable spatial fluctuations.

All of a sudden, Shi Qinghou's voice rang out in Han Li's mind.

"So there are now as many as eight restrictions in these city walls. That's quite an improvement."

"Why have you suddenly popped up now? Where were you when I had those questions for you?" Han Li asked through voice transmission as he flew over to Shi Chuankong's side.

Shi Qinghou offered no response to this.

"Did you teach me the method to bypass the Infernal Great Concealment Restriction because you already predicted that I was going to cause trouble there to lure Gui Mu away?" Han Li asked.

Once again, there was no response.

"I don't know what your intentions are, but you better not try any funny business here. If we're discovered, all of us will have to die here, and that includes you," Han Li warned in a cold voice.

"There's no need to be so wary of me. Right now, our fates are tightly intertwined, and the last thing I want to do is put you in harm's way," Shi Qinghou sighed.

"How am I supposed to trust you when you don't tell me anything?" Han Li harrumphed coldly.

"You'll understand in the future," Shi Qinghou replied in an ambiguous fashion before falling silent again.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, but he had no time to dwell on this frustrating interaction as he turned his attention to the stone platform.

There were countless silver patterns on the stone platform, forming an extremely complex array that was littered with silver array flags and around forty to fifty fist-sized silver crystals.

These silver crystals were rather similar to spirit stones, but they had strange corkscrew patterns on them and were releasing bright silver light and spatial fluctuations.

"These are Silver Embryo Stones," Han Li remarked with a surprised expression.

This was a type of spirit material that contained spatial power, and even in the True Immortal Realm, it was quite rare, so he wasn't expecting to see it in the Gray Realm.

Shi Chuankong was standing beside the stone platform, and he flipped a hand over to summon a silver jade vial, then chanted an incantation while making a hand seal.

The jade vial shuddered slightly, following which a fist-sized ball of silver liquid flew out of it before splitting up into dozens of drops at Shi Chuankong's behest, each of fused into one of the Silver Embryo Stones.

A layer of silver light instantly appeared over the Silver Embryo Stones, following which all of them became dull and devoid of luster, as if the spatial power within them had been frozen, and the pillar of silver light also instantly vanished.

"It's done! Gather around, everyone, we don't have much time!" Shi Chuankong urged as he made a rapid string of hands seals, releasing bursts of silver light that fell onto the surrounding ground to form a silver array.

Han Li the others immediately stepped into the array, and Mo Guang released plumes of baleful qi out of his sleeves to inundate the entire array.

With a flash of silver light, everyone instantly vanished from within the array, and the residual baleful qi in the side hall quickly faded away.

Immediately thereafter, the Silver Embryo Stones began to function again, and in just a few moments, the entire array was back up and running, looking as if nothing had ever happened.

Chapter 727: Rumor

Mere moments after the spatial restriction was restored, Gui Mu suddenly appeared on the second floor of the palace.

Right as he was about to fly up to the third floor, he suddenly turned to the side hall to the left with slightly furrowed brows, but then shook his head and withdrew his gaze before continuing up to the third floor.

At the same time, Han Li and the others appeared in a secluded alley amid a flash of light, and as soon as they emerged, Han Li's brows immediately furrowed slightly with discomfort.

"How can conditions be so different on the other side of the wall? Not only is the air here much more murky, even the baleful qi has become far denser than before," Fox 3 complained with a disgruntled expression.

"Not only that, but the air temperature here seems to be quite a bit higher as well," Shi Chuankong remarked.

"Fellow Daoist Baili, does the Reincarnation Region have any information about Asura City?" Han Li asked.

"I'm afraid not. The regions of the Gray Realm are all quite wary of one another, and information isn't readily shared. To make matters worse, the Infernal Region is extremely xenophobic, so there's even less information to come out of here," Baili Yan replied with a shake of his head.

"In any case, let's head to the border first. As long as we can bypass that hurdle, we'll be able to enter the Soul Cleansing Region," Han Li said.

"The layout of this area is a little strange. There are many ring-shaped buildings that haven't been marked out in the map, and their purpose is unclear. If we're going to the border, then we'll have to pass by these buildings," Mo Guang said.

"We'll just have to do our best to avoid them and pass by them as quickly as possible," Han Li said.

With that, everyone set off toward the border.

The Infernal Servant patrol groups were popping up with greater and greater regularity, and there were even some mid-True Immortal cultivators in many of the buildings. Security here was even tighter than it was in the Hundred Treasure Area, and it took the group a great deal of effort to finally arrive at the border of the Soul Cleansing Area.

Right as Fox 3 was about to employ his usual concealment method for everyone, Mo Guang suddenly said, "Stop! We can't go any further than this."

Han Li and the others hurriedly stopped in their tracks upon hearing this.

"Why not?"

"Take a look over there," Mo Guang said as he pointed in a certain direction.

Han Li turned to that direction, and his brows instantly furrowed slightly.

On the ground near the city wall up ahead was embedded a red watermelon-sized eyeball, and identical eyeballs were embedded into the ground at set intervals along the wall.

What was even more disturbing was that the black city wall up ahead was also riddled with these harrowing eyeballs.

"Those are Asura Ghost Eyes," Baili Yan sighed.

"Asura Ghost Eyes? Are they going to be a problem?" Fox 3 asked.

"These things are the eyes of Great Asura Demons, each of which has three thousand six hundred such eyes that can see through all types of illusions, so your illusions most likely won't work here," Baili Yan explained with a shake of his head.

"How are we supposed to get close to the city wall then?" Shi Chuankong asked with tightly furrowed brows.

As soon as his voice trailed off, the Asura Ghost Eye that was closest to them suddenly turned in their direction, and Han Li and the others immediately restrained their auras before retreating to a safe distance away.

After finding a new hiding place, Han Li was just about to say something when a resounding boom abruptly rang out nearby.

Everyone was quite startled by this, thinking that they had been discovered, and they hurriedly began inspecting their surroundings.

"Over there!" Baili Yan said with a peculiar expression as he pointed in a certain direction.

Han Li turned to that direction to find that a black mushroom cloud was rising up into the sky above one of the mysterious ring-shaped buildings that Mo Guang had mentioned earlier.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li decided, "Fellow Daoist Mo Guang and I will go take a look, all of you remain hidden and wait for us here."

"I'll go with you. There seems to be something rather out of the ordinary there," Baili Yan said in a low voice.

"Alright," Han Li replied with a nod.

"Be careful," Shi Chuankong cautioned.

With that, Han Li's trio emerged onto the street outside as three blurry shadows, and they quickly made their way over to that ring-shaped building while taking care to avoid the nearby watchtowers.

Up close, Han Li discovered that these buildings were even taller than he had thought they were from afar, and the walls were riddled with complex runes, but thankfully, all of them were merely for fortification purposes.

The three of them snuck into the building to find that it was quite empty, with the only noteworthy feature being a large black plaza, littered across which were some black rocks that were several dozen feet tall.

At this moment, the plaza was looking severely ravaged, and Han Li's trio was hiding behind a relatively intact rock. However, this rock also had a hole that was roughly the size of a human head blown through it, and wisps of white smoke were rising up from the hole.

All of a sudden, a burst of rumbling rang out from the other side of the plaza, following which the ground split open to reveal an underground passageway.

Immediately thereafter, several figures made their way onto the plaza from the passageway.

They were quite short, only around half the height of the average grown man, and their upper bodies were bared to reveal their dark green skin. Their facial features were quite hideous, with thin, tapered ears, protruding sharp teeth, and bald heads with only a tuft of black fur in the middle.

Despite how short and stubby they were, their muscles were extremely well-developed, and their arms were particularly thick and strong with a series of copper rings around them, giving them a very fearsome appearance.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly at the sight of these beings, and he was struck by a sense of familiarity, as if he had seen records of such beings in the scriptures that he had read, but he was unable to recall exactly what they were.

"There's a really strong karmic fire aura here," Baili Yan suddenly remarked in a low voice as he examined the rift on the ground.

Han Li's attention was focused on the green-skinned beings at the moment, so he failed to hear Baili Yan clearly.

The leader of the green-skinned beings had the most copper rings on his arms at five each, and he was scouring his gaze over the plaza with a furious expression as he roared, "This is pathetic! This amount of power isn't enough to do anything! How can we possibly catch the interest of the Infernal beings with this? Go and test out the largest one!

As soon as his voice trailed off, another green-skinned being immediately approached him in a shaky manner, holding a black ball in his hands.

"Please return to the underground shelter, esteemed elder," the green-skinned being said to the leader of the group.

The elder turned around and made his way back down the underground passageway with a dark expression, while the rest of the group hurriedly followed along.

Meanwhile, Han Li's trio turned to the green-skinned being holding the black ball with perplexed expressions.

After chanting an incantation, the green-skinned being pressed a palm down onto the black ball in his hand, then tossed it toward the center of the plaza.

The patterns on the surface of the black ball began to light up, and a sense of foreboding instantly welled up in Han Li's heart as he hurriedly raised a hand to summon a dark green turtle-shell-shaped shield.

Immediately thereafter, an explosive boom rang out, and an enormous ball of black flames erupted out of the black ball, forming a sea of black flames that spread rapidly in all directions.

The green-skinned being that had detonated the black ball attempted to scurry back into the underground passageway, but he was swallowed up by the waves of black fire before he could reach the entrance, and his body melted away into a puddle of goo.

The large rocks on the plaza also rapidly melted away in the face of the scorching black flames, quickly reduced to lava-like black liquid.

The rock in front of Han Li's trio was also rapidly melting away, and while the shield that Han Li had summoned was keeping the black flames at bay, it was also sizzling and crackling incessantly.

"Let's get out of here," Han Li said, and the three of them immediately flew out of the ring-shaped building.

At this point, all of the black rocks on the plaza had already been wiped out, and the black flames were ravaging the surrounding walls, while a black mushroom cloud that was several times larger than before rose up into the sky.

At the same time, all of the patterns engraved onto the plaza and the walls began to release black light alongside peculiar energy fluctuations, counteracting the black flames and containing them within the building.

Han Li's trio returned to the spot where Shi Chuankong and Fox 3 were hiding, and the latter asked with a puzzled expression, "What happened? We thought you'd been exposed, and we were just about to go after you."

"That building seems to be a test site of some sort for Gray Realm weapons," Han Li explained.

"What was that just now then?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"If I'm not mistaken, that appeared to be an explosive treasure forged using karmic fire, and it's powerful enough to pose quite a threat even to the average True Immortal," Mo Guang said.

"It looks like those green-skinned beings that we saw are from the Dwarf Tribe, a tribe that's very adept in tool refinement," Han Li mused.

"The Dwarf Tribe? Weren't they supposed to have been completely wiped out several thousand years ago?" Shi Chuankong asked with a surprised expression.

"It seems like that was only a ruse. The reality is that they were abducted to craft treasure for the Infernal Tribe," Han Li said.

"In that case, that rumor must be true," Baili Yan suddenly said.

"What rumor?" Fox 3 asked.

Chapter 728: Confounding the Enemy

"Prior to coming here, I conducted some research into the Infernal Tribe, and I saw an interesting rumor. Apparently, there's a naturally forming karmic fire crater in Asura City, and all Infernal beings are thrown into the crater at birth to be baptized in a process that they refer to as soul cleansing," Baili Yan said.

"They're throwing newborns into karmic fire? How is that possible?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"Baleful qi is essential for all cultivators of the Gray Realm, so their tolerance of karmic fire far exceeds ours. On top of that, they're not actually throwing infants into karmic flames. Instead, they're only making the newborns live near the karmic flames. Only upon reaching twelve years of age are they truly baptized using karmic flames, and only those that survive have the right to become true Infernal beings," Baili Yan explained.

"No wonder there are so few Infernal beings," Fox 3 mused.

"Earlier in the courtyard, I already sensed a very formidable karmic fire aura. I presume the karmic fire crater must be right under that courtyard," Baili Yan remarked.

"If the rumor is true, then the karmic fire crater should be in the Soul Cleansing Area, why is it in the Rashom Area?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"That's nothing to be surprised about. We don't know the shape and size of the karmic fire crater, perhaps it runs through both areas," Mo Guang said with a smile.

"It's also a possibility that the Infernal Tribe carved out an underground passageway to guide the karmic fire into the Rashom Area for tool refinement purposes. In any case, it looks like we'll have to make a trip underground," Han Li said.

"Are you suggesting that we sneak into the Soul Cleansing Area through the karmic fire crater?" Baili Yan asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"That's right. There's a very good chance that we'll be caught by Great Encompassment cultivators if we try and go there through conventional means, so we may as well try our luck underground," Han Li replied with a nod.

"But how are we supposed to traverse through the karmic fire? It's not like we're Infernal beings," Shi Chuankong said in a concerned manner.

He was already quite worried about baleful qi infiltrating his body, so he was naturally even more fearful of these karmic flames.

"I'm sure Fellow Daoist Baili knows more about karma flames than all of us. Do you have a solution to that problem?" Han Li asked as he turned to Baili Yan.

"As I'm sure all of you are aware, baleful qi and karmic fire are essentially one and the same, except they're manifested in different forms. Even among karmic flames, there are differences between naturally occurring ones and ones derived from a cultivator's body.

“These underground karmic flames can scorch both the body and the soul. The body can be protected using treasures, but not much can be done to protect the soul," Baili Yan explained.

"So what you're saying is that there's nothing we can do but endure the karmic fire," Fox 3 sighed.

"Not necessarily. If any of us has a graded immortal treasure that can protect the soul, we can all use it together, and that could perhaps ensure that our souls remain unaffected," Baili Yan said.

"I have a treasure of that description," Han Li said, then pointed a finger at his own glabella, and a white rune emerged, accompanied by a burst of formidable spiritual sense.

This was none other than the Imperial Peak Spirit Restriction Talisman in his consciousness, and everyone's expression changed slightly upon sensing Han Li's spiritual sense.

"Your spiritual sense is immense, Fellow Daoist Li! Could it be that you've already cultivated the Spirit Refinement Technique up to the fifth level?" Baili Yan asked with a stunned expression.

"That's right," Han Li replied with a nod. "What do you think, Fellow Daoist Baili? Will this Imperial Peak Spirit Restriction Talisman suffice?"

Everyone was so stunned by Han Li's spiritual sense that they forgot to examine the talisman, and only now did they begin to assess the talisman.

"This is a treasure of a very high caliber to begin with, and with your immense spiritual sense and everyone's help, it should suffice for our needs. The only problem is that we don't know what it's like underground," Baili Yan said with a concerned expression.

"How about we disguise ourselves as Infernal beings and sneak underground?" Fox 3 suggested.

"That's too risky. The aura of Infernal beings is quite unique and difficult to replicate. If we're exposed on the spot, we'll be in a world of trouble," Shi Chuankong said with slightly furrowed brows.

"How about if I use this?" Fox 3 asked with a smile, and he summoned several slender fox tails as he spoke.

The fur on the fox tails were all standing up on end and giving off a translucent gleam, but they were also giving off a strong foxy stench that made everyone involuntarily recoil slightly.

"Are these Heavenly Jade Fox Tails?" Shi Chuankong exclaimed.

"You have a good eye, Brother Shi. Indeed, these are Heavenly Jade Fox Tails, and they were shed by a High Zenith Stage senior of mine. Let me make this clear in advance: I'm only borrowing these tails to everyone, and you have to return them to me after the event, Fox 3 said.

"Heavenly Jade Fox Tails are not just illusory treasures, but also have a confounding effect. With these tails at our disposal, we could definitely attempt to pose as Infernal beings," Baili Yan said with a smile.

"In that case, let's get moving," Han Li said.

Thus, Fox 3 handed out the Heavenly Jade Fox Tails to everyone, then disclosed the usage method, and everyone employed the method to complete their transformations, following which the foxy stench instantly faded.

Mo Guang and Baili Yan were both at the High Zenith Stage, so they had transformed into true Infernal beings, while Han Li's trio transformed into three Infernal Servants that trailed along behind them in a subservient fashion.

With their disguises adopted, they rose up into the sky and flew toward the ring-shaped building.

Inside the courtyard, several Dwarf beings were examining the aftermath of the explosion, and their leader was nodding with a pleased expression.

Han Li's group descended out of the sky before drawing to a halt in front of them while hovering a foot above the ground, and the Dwarf beings were forced to look up at them as they extended a respectful salute, in response to which Baili Yan and Mo Guang merely nodded in silence.

The Dwarf beings immediately began to sweat profusely, and none of them dared to say anything.

Right as Baili Yan was about to break the silence, the leader of the Dwarf beings said, "Please forgive our incompetence. Those two scoundrels from the True Immortal Realm have refused to cooperate with us, and as a result, we were only able to conclude our experiments on the Karmic Fire Baleful Lightning today, so we haven't had a chance to go into mass production yet.

“However, rest assured, we'll be able to produce a batch in three more days at most, and they'll definitely hold sufficient power to match your requirements."

"Take me down there," Baili Yan instructed in a cold voice.

The leader of the Dwarf beings hurriedly led the way, while the other Dwarf beings trailed along behind Han Li's group.

The ground began to rumble as a passageway that led downward slowly emerged, and an intense karmic fire aura instantly erupted upward.

After traveling down the passageway for several thousand feet, everyone arrived in a massive underground hall.

Upon entering the underground hall, everyone was struck by bursts of scorching heat alongside dense baleful qi, and with the exceptions of Mo Guang and Baili Yan, everyone else was feeling quite uncomfortable.

The fact that there was so much discomfort even before entering the karmic fire had Han Li wondering if he had really made the right decision.

Even after taking some to acclimate to these new conditions, the discomfort still remained, but it had abated somewhat.

The hall was lined with several dozen armorclad Infernal Servants that were hovering above the ground, and their expressions remained unchanged at the sight of Mo Guang and Baili Yan, but they did extend respectful bows.

"Lead the way," Mo Guang instructed without even sparing a glance at the Infernal Servants.

The Dwarf being immediately led them deeper into the hall, and the deeper they went, the louder the sound of pounding metal became.

After passing through a short passageway, a series of giant underground halls began to appear on either side. These halls were bustling with flames and activity, and there were many Dwarf beings in all of them, vigorously refining all types of treasures and weapons.

Han Li snuck a few glances into the underground halls along the way, and he discovered that each of them had a giant furnace that was filled with scorching karmic flames.

The group made its way to the entrance of a certain hall, following which the Dwarf being stopped in his tracks and said, "This is where the Karmic Fire Baleful Lightning is being refined."

Mo Guang and Baili Yan stepped into the hall first, followed by Han Li's trio.

This hall was significantly larger than the ones before it, and it was split up into many sections, with close to a hundred Dwarf beings busy at work inside.

They seemed to be completely oblivious to the arrival of Han Li's group, and they continued to toil away, while a True Immortal Stage Infernal Servant approached the group before extending a respectful bow toward Mo Guang and Baili Yan.

Balls of black flames were dancing incessantly within a giant furnace at the center of the hall, and beside the furnace was a group of Dwarf beings that were clad in full suits of protective equipment, including even visors that covered their faces, and they were carefully fishing out balls of black karmic fire out of the furnace using containers with extremely long handles.

Right at this moment, one of the Dwarf beings accidentally bumped their container against the edge of the furnace, and the karmic fire inside instantly spilled out before flowing toward Han Li's group.

The Dwarf being was horrified to see this, and he hurriedly bent down to recover the karmic fire, but he was struck by a whiplash to the face from the Infernal Servant.

A loud crack rang out as the visor on his face was instantly shattered, and a charred gash appeared on his face.

Smoke was rising up from the gash, but he didn't even dare to groan in pain as he continued to chase after the spilled karmic fire.

Chapter 729: Springing Into Action

At this point, the karmic fire had already reached Mo Guang, and he casually bent down before making a grabbing motion, drawing the karmic fire into his hand as if it were a ball of putty.

After playing with it for a moment, he tossed it back into the giant furnace.

The Infernal Servant faltered slightly upon seeing this, then extended an apologetic salute toward Mo Guang before lashing out with his whip again, winding it around the Dwarf being's neck this time.

The Dwarf being's complexion had already turned extremely pale, and a pained look appeared on his face as he struggled against the whip around his neck.

The Dwarf being that had led Han Li's group here was also looking on with a pained and sorrowful expression, but he didn't dare to say anything.

"That's enough. Bring me the finished product," Baili Yan instructed.

The Infernal Servant's cold expression remained unchanged, but he retracted his whip from around the Dwarf being's neck, and the spared Dwarf being immediately fell to his knees and began kowtowing in gratitude.

The Dwarf being that had led Han Li's group here hurriedly brought over the dozen or so balls of Karmic Fire Baleful Lightning that had already been refined, and Baili Yan picked one up for a brief inspection, following which a perplexed look appeared on his face as he said to Han Li through voice transmission, "There appears to be some fire law powers intermingled with the baleful lightning."

"Perhaps that has something to do with the two people from the Immortal Realm that he spoke of earlier. Perhaps this baleful lightning is only as powerful as it is thanks to the infusion of fire law powers. In any case, you should take these," Han Li replied.

"Should we go and see those two Immortal Realm cultivators?" Baili Yan asked.

"Let's go to the karmic fire crater first and see if we can get to the Soul Cleansing Area through it. I don't think a detour would be wise," Han Li replied.

Baili Yan stowed the dozen or so balls of Karmic Fire Baleful Lightning away, then turned to Mo Guang as he said, "We're already here anyway, so we may as well take a look at the karmic fire crater, right?"

"I suppose," Mo Guang replied with a nod.

"Please come this way," the Infernal Servant said as he drifted over to Han Li's group.

After that, he led the group out of the hall, and as they were leaving, Han Li turned back to take a glance at the toiling Dwarf beings, just in time to see the Dwarf being that had led them here glowering at him with a resentful look in his eyes.

As soon as their eyes met, the resentment on the Dwarf being's face instantly turned to horror, but Han Li merely departed without doing anything.

The Dwarf being heaved a long sigh of relief, but was also rather perplexed about why he had been spared.

The passageway stretched on for close to ten kilometers before finally reaching an enormous underground cave.

There was a giant black fiery pit up ahead the size of an average lake, and inside it were churning black flames and baleful qi, making it difficult just to draw breath.

The path beneath everyone's feet gradually narrowed above the fiery crater, tapering to a bridge that was several dozen feet wide before coming to an abrupt end at the center of the crater.

On the other side of the fiery crater was a black rock wall with a giant hole that was several hundred feet tall on it, and the karmic fire was pouring out of the hole before flowing into the fiery crater down below.

"It's just as you speculated, Fellow Daoist Li, the Rashom Area's karmic fire comes from the Soul Cleansing Area!" Shi Chuankong said through voice transmission.

"Don't celebrate just yet, we have to hurry up. The more abundant the baleful qi in a place is, the faster the spiritual qi in a Heavenly Jade Fox Tail will be worn down, so we'll revert back to our true forms soon," Fox 3 suddenly cautioned.

Han Li was just about to respond when something suddenly caught his attention.

Standing on the bridge up ahead were around a dozen armorclad Infernal Servants, all of whom were holding weapons with cold looks on their faces, and they were displaying no reaction to Han Li's group.

Dangling down from the end of the bridge was a square black cage that was swaying incessantly above the karmic fire, constantly being eroded by the flames and baleful qi.

There were two figures in the cage, each leaning against a corner with disheveled hair, looking very frail and defeated.

The one on the left was the larger of the two figures, and his face was concealed by his head of messy red hair, but there was a nose resembling a rhinoceros horn protruding out from his tangled locks.

On the other side of the cage was a man with a head of white hair and many gashes on his face, making him barely recognizable, but Han Li was immediately able to identify him as none other than Immortal Lord Hot Flame.

His heart stirred slightly upon seeing this, but he didn't do anything.

At this point, Fox 3 had also identified them, and he exclaimed through voice transmission, "Those two seem to be Chi Rong and Fellow Daoist Hot Flame!"

"It looks like they were far less fortunate than us," Shi Chuankong remarked.

Baili Yan didn't know them, and he asked, "Are they acquaintances of yours? Should we save them?"

Han Li's brows were tightly furrowed, and after a brief moment of hesitation, he said, "Restrictions have been planted in their bodies, so it'll most likely be very difficult to free them in a short time. Let's find the Baleful Cleansing Pond first, then save them later."

"Should we make our move now?" Mo Guang asked.

"Yes," Han Li replied.

A cold smirk instantly appeared on Mo Guang's face upon hearing this, and he raised a hand to make a grabbing motion, releasing bursts of black mist out of his sleeve that hurtled toward the Infernal Servant who was acting as their guide like five ferocious black dragons.

Before the Infernal Servant had a chance to say anything, he was already inundated by dense baleful qi, and at the same time, a vast expanse of black mist surged forth to encompass the entire bridge, as well as the dozen or so Infernal Servants on it.

Baili Yan had already vanished into the baleful qi, and a string of dull thumps rang out, while Mo Guang lifted up the Infernal Servant who was acting as their guide with one hand.

No more than a few seconds later, all of the baleful qi had returned to Mo Guang's body, while the Infernal Servant fell like a sack of skin and bones, having been completely sucked dry of all blood and vitality.

The karmic fire down below churned momentarily and swallowed up the Infernal Servant’s body in the blink of an eye, while Baili Yan was kicking the rest of the lifeless Infernal Servants into the fiery crater.

After that, everyone descended back down onto the ground instead of continuing to hover above it, then removed their Heavenly Jade Fox Tails before returning them to Fox 3.

"Let's go," Han Li said, and the group hurriedly made their way to the end of the bridge.

While passing by the metal cage, Han Li hesitated momentarily, but then quickly made his way past it.

Inside the cage, Immortal Lord Hot Flame seemed to be completely oblivious to what had happened up above. He displayed no reaction to the commotion, and his eyes were gray and dull.

"Aren't you supposed to be allies of my senior martial brother? Are you not going to save him?" Chi Rong chuckled in a gravelly voice.

Fox 3's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he stopped in his tracks.

"We don't have time, we'll save them when we come back," Shi Chuankong said in a low voice as he passed him by, and Fox 3 quickly continued onward.

At the end of the bridge, the environment had become extremely hostile from the scorching heat of the karmic fire and the vast abundance of baleful qi, to the point that even Han Li was struggling to suppress his discomfort. Shi Chuankong and Fox 3 were beginning to feel a little lightheaded, and violent impulses were welling up in their hearts.

Han Li immediately channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique while pointing a finger at his own glabella, upon which the Imperial Peak Spirit Restriction Talisman in his consciousness instantly released a burst of formidable spiritual sense.

"Protect your physical bodies and inject your spiritual sense into the talisman, we're setting off right away," Han Li said.

Everyone did as they were told, with Baili Yan summoning a suit of black armor that looked as if it had been refined from dragon scales, and it was clear at a glance that it was a graded immortal treasure.

Fox 3 opened his mouth to release a green jewel that embedded itself into the crown on his head, and the two treasures instantly released a burst of dazzling green light that encompassed his entire body, turning his skin a bright green color.

Meanwhile, Shi Chuankong had summoned his silver lute and was strumming its strings to release bursts of invisible ripples that formed a spatial barrier around him.

As for Mo Guang, he took a glance down at the karmic fire below, then decided that he didn't even need to do anything to protect himself.

At the same time, a layer of golden scales appeared over Han Li's body alongside a suit of dark green turtle shell armor, and everyone began to inject their spiritual sense into the Imperial Peak Spirit Restriction Talisman.

With their injections of spiritual sense, the rune on Han Li's glabella became clearer and clearer, releasing a snowy mountain projection that was over a hundred feet tall, encompassing the entire group within it.

Fox 3 and Shi Chuankong's expressions instantly eased slightly, and their discomfort instantly faded away.

Han Li could sense that the two of them had relaxed a little, and he immediately cautioned, "Don't let your guards down. Karmic fire is a lot more invasive than baleful qi, so even the slightest lapse in concentration could have catastrophic circumstances."

Shi Chuankong and Fox 3 hurriedly nodded in response as they retightened their focus.

"Let's go," Han Li declared, and the group leaped down from the bridge toward the giant hole up ahead where the karmic flames were flowing out of.

However, they had only just flown down from the bridge when the karmic fire up ahead suddenly began to flicker and rumble incessantly.

"There's a restriction in the fire crater!" Han Li exclaimed.

As soon as his voice trailed off, the karmic fire down below instantly began to churn violently, following which millstone-sized balls of black flames shot up toward them in a frenzy, filling the air with a noxious miasma.

Chapter 730: Sudden Turn

"Fellow Daoist Mo Guang!" Han Li yelled, and Mo Guang immediately swept a sleeve through the air to release a plume of black mist, which split up into eight tentacle-like appendages before lashing out at the oncoming karmic fireballs.

A string of loud thumps rang out as specks of black flames were sent flying in all directions, but some of them made their way up the tentacles of black mist toward Mo Guang.

Mo Guang's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and a burst of aura fluctuations erupted out of his body to scatter the oncoming karmic flames.

Some specks of karmic fire fell onto Fox 3's body, but they were instantly repelled by the green light emanating from his body.

He felt a burst of baleful qi infiltrate his body, and his consciousness was dealt a heavy blow, but thankfully, under the protection of the Imperial Peak Spirit Restriction Talisman, he only experienced a brief rush of dizziness that quickly wore off.

However, that was far from the end of their troubles.

As the karmic fireballs continued to shoot up from down below, the fiery crater became more and more restless, and the karmic flames inside began to rise up as a black wall of fire.

Shi Chuankong strummed his fingers over the strings of his lute upon seeing this, releasing a burst of formidable soundwaves and spatial power that clashed against the wall of karmic fire, tearing an opening that was several dozen feet wide through it.

Shi Chuankong continued to strum the strings of his lute urgently, releasing a steady stream of soundwaves to keep the opening intact as he yelled through tightly gritted teeth, "Hurry! I can't keep this up for long!"

Han Li immediately released his time spirit domain without any hesitation, forming a golden light barrier around him as he shot forward at an incredible speed.

However, as soon as the karmic flames made contact with his spirit domain, bursts of baleful qi instantly seeped straight into his body through the spirit domain from all directions.

Han Li gave a muffled groan as his consciousness began to churn violently, and he was almost overcome by a intense wave of aggressive intent, but thankfully, he was already channeling his Spirit Refinement Technique with all his might, so he was able to suppress the adverse effects of the baleful qi.

Immediately thereafter, the white snowy mountain rune on his glabella brightened significantly, releasing bursts of invisible ripples that quelled the unrest in his consciousness.

However, at the same time, his spirit domain was constantly being whittled down by the surrounding karmic flames.

With his brows tightly furrowed, he let loose a low roar as he swept a sleeve through the air to release several chains of azure light, which wound themselves around Baili Yan and the others. At the same time, he channeled his Reversal True Axis and instantly accelerated significantly as he flew through the opening in the wall of fire.

As soon as they passed through the wall of fire, Shi Chuankong retracted his fingers with cold sweat pouring down his face, and the tips of his fingers were torn and bleeding profusely.

Without the resistance of the soundwaves, the black wall of fire quickly mended itself, but at this point, it was already past them, and Han Li's group was no more than a hundred feet away from the karmic fire passageway that led to the Soul Cleansing Area.

Everyone heaved a collective sigh of relief, yet right as they were about to venture into the karmic fire passageway, an array suddenly lit up within it, following which the black karmic fire inside surged forth like floodwaters through a broken dam.

At such close quarters, there was no time for Han Li and the others to react, and they were instantly scattered by the torrent of karmic fire before plunging down toward the fiery crater below, and the karmic fire down below also reared up to devour them in an instant.

As soon as Han Li plunged into the karmic fire, the spiritual connections that he had formed with everyone through the Imperial Peak Spirit Restriction Talisman were severed. Before he had a chance to think about anything else, he was inundated by karmic fire from all directions, setting his suit of dark green armor alight.

Bursts of incredibly formidable baleful qi surged into his body alongside the waves of heat, and even his suit of armor wasn't able to keep them at bay. In the blink of an eye, Han Li felt as if he were being bound by layers of chains, and the baleful qi in his immortal acupoints also began to riot.

Thankfully, he was still keeping a tight leash on his own consciousness, so he wasn't driven to the point of insanity.

All of a sudden, his Mantra Treasured Axis appeared behind him at his behest, and all of the black karmic flames encompassed within the golden light that it was releasing were instantly frozen, but the heat and baleful qi that they were giving off hadn't abated in the at all.

Han Li's brows were tightly furrowed as he flew out of the fiery crater, yet before he even had a chance to steady himself, a vast expanse of black light suddenly descended upon him like a crushing black cloud.

He looked up to discover a millstone-sized black seal that was somehow completely unaffected by his time law powers, and it was crashing down with tremendous force while releasing a burst of suction power that held him firmly into place.

Han Li had no time to think in this dire situation, and he threw a punch up toward the black seal, unleashing a giant azure sword projection the size of a house, which struck the black seal with immense power.

The azure fist projection shattered almost instantly upon contact, sending waves of azure energy erupting in all directions, while the black seal continued to crash down from above.

Han Li let loose a thunderous roar as the muscles on his body bulged, and he took on his Giant Mountain Ape form before pushing against the black seal with both hands.

The black seal abruptly swelled to several times its original size before crashing down onto the palms of Han Li's hands, and he felt as if he were being crushed under a thousand mountains.

Even with his current physical prowess, the seal was impossible to keep at bay, and he found himself being forced back into the fiery crater.

Only then did he realize that the seal wasn't affected by his time law powers purely because the power that it contained was too immense, to the point that it was able to affect the space around it to a certain extent.

Without his time law powers slowing it down, the black seal would've only crashed down onto him with even greater speed and power.

Right at this moment, a raspy voice rang out nearby.

"Time law powers and a true spirit bloodline? Impressive! No wonder you dared to sneak into the Rashom Area. Who are you? Are you from the Reincarnation Region or the Heavenly Court?"

Han Li was struggling to keep the giant black seal and the surrounding karmic flames at bay as he looked up to find a figure hovering a foot in the air above the bridge overhead.

The figure was dressed in a black robe that was giving off a faint sheet, and there was a strange tall hat on his head. His face was deathly pale, but his pupils were an extremely dark gray color, even darker than Mo Yu's.

His appearance was rather effeminate, and unlike the cold expressions commonly seen on the faces of other Infernal beings, there was a faint smile on his face, striking Han Li with a sense of disgust.

What was most alarming to him was that this Infernal being was a Great Encompassment cultivator.

Standing behind him were a pair of strange beings with bull horns on their heads, and both were completely devoid of expression.

The two beings were from the same tribe as the beings that Han Li had seen in the puppet refinement fortresses, except these two were clearly finished products. There were shaped white bones protruding out of their arms and shoulders, and black chains were wound around their hands.

On the other end of the chains was another figure that had been completely tied up, and it was none other than Fox 3.

At this moment, his eyes were tightly shut, and it was unclear whether he was dead or alive.

There were seven or eight armorclad Infernal Servants nearby holding the same black chains, and they had formed an encirclement around Shi Chuankong.

These Infernal Servants were different from the ones that Han Li had seen up to this point in that the scales on their faces were black instead of gray, and there was a huge hole in each of their chests, within which were balls of scorching karmic flames.

The Infernal Servants released the chains in their hands, and karmic flames emerged over them as they converged from all directions to form a spherical cage around Shi Chuankong, who was strumming the strings of his silver lute to release a spatial barrier that kept the black chains at bay.

Two of the armorclad Infernal Servants drifted forward upon seeing this, approaching the spherical cage as a series of strange runes emerged around the karmic flames in their chests, following which the flames exploded violently.

A burst of tremendous shockwaves erupted forth, instantly shattering the spatial barrier around Shi Chuankong.

Not far away from him, Baili Yan's arms had already turned completely black, while his hands had transformed into a pair of huge dragon claws that also had black flames burning over them. Clearly, he had been forced to release his karmic fire once again after suppressing it for so long.

In contrast with Shi Chuankong, he only had a single opponent, but Han Li was astonished by the sight of this opponent as it was none other than Su Liu!

At this moment, Su Liu's aura didn't resemble that of a True Immortal at all, and his suit of armor had also vanished, leaving his upper body bare. There was a series of harrowing gashes on his body, and a hole had also been dug into his chest, embedded into which was a metal ball that was riddled with runes and burning with karmic flames.

There were also two black chains that completely ran through both of his arms before protruding out of the palms of his hands, and connected to the ends of the chains was a black double-edged ax and a chain mace.

Han Li noticed that Su Liu's eyes were completely dull and devoid of luster, and that his pupils had turned gray, just like the pupils of a gray immortal.

Chapter 731: Dire Straits

"It looks like you recognize this puppet of mine," the Great Encompassment Stage Infernal being remarked as he observed the changes in Han Li's expression.

"What did you do to him?" Han Li asked with tightly furrowed brows.

"So you really do know him. He wasn't as fortunate as those two in the cage. By the time he got here, he had already been torn apart by spatial power, so I took the liberty of modifying his body a little. Right now, he's feeling quite lonely, and I just so happen to be looking for a buddy for him. There's no need to feel depressed, you'll become just like him soon! How about it? Isn't that an exciting thought?" the Infernal being chortled with glee.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a resounding boom suddenly rang out from underground, and all of the black karmic fire in the crater down below began to churn violently before rising up as an enormous wave that swallowed up most of Han Li's body.

The baleful qi around Han Li instantly became a hundred times more potent, and even though he was forcibly stabilizing his own consciousness with his Spirit Refinement Technique, he was struck by an irrepressible violent urge that instantly set his blood alight.

Even though he was able to just barely cling onto a shred of lucidity by desperately channeling his Spirit Refinement Technique, he was still stunned by this turn of events.

"How interesting! I've never seen a Golden Immortal with spiritual sense as powerful as yours. Let's see how long you can last," the Infernal being mused with an intrigued expression as he clasped his hands behind his back.

Han Li was frantically channeling his Spirit Refinement Technique while simultaneously resisting the giant black seal up above, and his face had turned deathly pale, while cracks and pops were ringing out incessantly within his body.

Right at this moment, he spotted two more figures rushing at him from another direction in the fiery crater, and one of them was none other than Mo Guang.

However, he was also looking rather worse for wear, and there was a young woman that was less than half his height with a hand locked around his throat.

Despite this, there was a faint smile on his face, and it was unclear whether his calmness was genuine or just a facade.

The young woman was dressed in a bright red cloak that presented a stark contrast compared with the bleak and drab color tones adopted by most other beings of the Gray Realm.

Right at this moment, a burst of black light suddenly flashed over Mo Guang's body, and he began to transform into a cloud of black mist. However, at the same time, a burst of dark red light emerged over the palm of the hand of the young woman that was clasped around his throat, and it was releasing a burst of peculiar energy fluctuations that prevented his body from disintegrating.

After that, the young woman swiveled around in mid-air before flying toward the end of the bridge, still dragging Mo Guang by the throat.

Despite this, Mo Guang still wasn't displaying any fear, and the nonchalant smile on his face remained unchanged. The young woman seemed to be very displeased by this, and she gave him a vicious slap to the face, sending his head swinging to the side, and even his cheekbone seemed to have been broken.

The young woman then tossed him onto the ground before making a hand seal and pressing the palm of her hand against his forehead.

Immediately thereafter, a bright red rune instantly appeared on his glabella.

The bull horn puppets standing behind the Great Encompassment Stage Infernal being immediately stepped forward before releasing their chains, which bound Mo Guang in a flash.

"Thank you for your help, Ms. You Luo," the Infernal being said.

"Aren't you supposed to be overseeing the Rashom Area, Yin Gua? How did you only detect these people after they had gotten so far?" the young woman asked in a cold voice.

Yin Gua could only give a sheepish smile in response.

"Do I need to take care of the rest of them as well?" You Luo asked with a mocking sneer.

Her appearance was very similar to that of a human, with fair skin and beautiful features, but ther was a black scale that resembled a vertical eye on her glabella, as well as several bright red markings on her cheeks.

Han Li noticed that her pupils were black instead of gray, and he immediately began to wonder if perhaps she wasn't a Gray Realm being.

Upon catching sight of Han Li in his Giant Mountain Ape form, a hint of surprise appeared on You Luo's face as she asked, "Why is there a true spirit from the Immortal Realm here?"

"Don't be fooled, Ms. You Luo, he's just a human with a true spirit bloodline, and I'm perfectly capable of taking care of him on my own," Yin Gua replied.

You Luo fell silent upon hearing this, and Yin Gua turned back to Han Li with an eager expression as he said, "These humans are very interesting, I'll have a lot of fun playing with them."

As soon as his voice trailed off, he swept a sleeve through the air, and the black seal above Han Li instantly came crashing down with even greater force.

Han Li gave a muffled groan as he withdrew his Mantra Treasured Axis, following which it began revolving in reverse, and he slipped out from under the black seal with great difficulty.

Instead of retreating toward the severed bridge, he rushed toward the karmic fire passageway with all his might.

"You're not getting away!" Yin Gua harrumphed coldly as he swept a sleeve through the air, and a series of black stone pillars erupted out of the karmic fire crater, forming a cage in front of Han Li.

A grim look appeared in his eyes upon seeing this, and he summoned nine Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords at once before combining them into one, then lashed out with the joint sword as he released the Divine Devilbane Lightning stored inside without any reservation.

Countless arcs of golden lightning came together to form a giant golden lightning net that tore through the karmic flames before striking the black stone pillars, shattering them in rapid succession.

Meanwhile, Han Li continued onward without pause, hurtling directly toward the karmic fire passageway, yet right as he was about to rush into it, Yin Gua appeared in his path in a flash.

He reached out with one hand to grab onto Han Li's shoulder, while his other hand grabbed onto the black seal from earlier before pressing it toward Han Li's forehead.

There was no time for Han Li to summon his Mantra Treasured Axis, and he had already severely overexerted himself up to this point, so he was powerless to resist as the seal was pressed firmly into his forehead.

He felt as if a jolt of electricity were running through his body, followed by a numb sensation, and all of his immortal spiritual power was sealed away, while all of the strength was also drained from his body, leaving him completely immobilized.

At this point, Shi Chuankong had also already been captured, leaving only Baili Yan, who was still battling against Su Liu.

You Luo chose an opportunity to enter the fray, and Baili Yan was quickly overwhelmed and also captured.

Han Li's heart instantly sank upon seeing this.

He was already mentally prepared for a worst case scenario, but the combination of Mo Guang, Fox 3, Baili Yan, Shi Chuankong, and he weren't even able to last fifteen minutes against Yin Gua.

At the same time, he was wondering how Yin Gua had managed to get here so quickly. Even if they had triggered the restriction in the fire crater, he shouldn't have been able to get here so fast, unless he had already detected the intrusion.

Could it be that their disguises had been seen through?

That was quite implausible as well. Setting aside the fact that they had genuine Heavenly Jade Fox Tails at their disposal, Mo Guang possessed a gray immortal body, and due to the ravages of his karmic fire, Baili Yan was essentially half a gray immortal as well, and just their auras alone would've been enough to fool anyone. Otherwise, they wouldn't have been assigned the task of posing as Infernal beings.

With his entire body numbed, Han Li's tongue wasn't working that well, so he could only ask in a slurred manner, "How did you... discover us?"

"I'm in a good mood today, so I'll tell you. One of the Infernal Servants on duty here is actually a puppet of mine," Yin Gua explained.

Han Li heaved an internal sigh upon hearing this.

Right at this moment, Yin Gua raised his left hand before thrusting it toward Han Li's group, and a bolt of black lightning shot out of the palm of his hand, then exploded into countless black runes that instantly burrowed their way into the bodies of Han Li and the others.

Han Li felt a burst of sharp pain in his dantian, and he hurriedly inspected his own internal condition in an alarmed manner.

In doing so, he discovered that arcs of black lightning had appeared in his dantian, enveloping his nascent soul.

These arcs of black lightning were giving off a type of unknown law power fluctuations, after his nascent soul was ensnared within them, all of the immortal spiritual power in his body instantly became completely frozen and stagnant.

On top of that, these law powers were continuing to rapidly spread through the rest of his body, and he was completely powerless to resist.

Judging from the expressions on the faces of Mo Guang and the others, they were clearly experiencing the same thing.

Chapter 732: Infernal Prison

Yin Gua seemed to be quite pleased with the changes in the expressions of Han Li's group, and he casually withdrew his hand, while You Luo praised, "Your baleful lightning law powers are becoming more and more profound, Yin Gua."

A subtle hint of envy flashed through Yin Gua's eyes upon hearing this, but he maintained an amicable smile as he replied, "There are no fewer than ten people in the Gray Realm who've mastered the laws of baleful lightning, so I can't even begin to compare with your law powers."

You Luo burst into laughter upon hearing this, and Yin Gua's brows furrowed slightly as a cold gleam flashed through his eyes, but his amicable facade remained intact.

"You're far too kind, Yin Gua. What do you plan to do with these people?" You Luo asked after her laughter subsided.

"These clowns must have some objective for sneaking into Asura City, so I plan to interrogate them to find out their intentions," Yin Gua replied.

"This appears to be a very diverse group. There are humans, a devilish being, and a Void Integration being. With that in mind, it is rather difficult to guess their intentions, so an interrogation is indeed in order. Speaking of that, I'm quite good at interrogations, so how about I interrogate him in your stead?" You Luo proposed as she pointed a finger at Han Li, who was rather surprised to see this.

The smile on Yin Gua's face slowly faded upon hearing this, and he watched You Luo in silence without saying anything.

"I'll take that as a yes," You Luo said as she swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of dark red light that swept directly toward Han Li, but right at this moment, a bolt of black lightning appeared above Han Li before striking the burst of red light, instantly scattering it.

Yin Gua slowly withdrew his arm, and there was a glimmer of black lightning flickering on the tip of his finger.

"What's the meaning of this?" You Luo asked with a surprised expression.

"Don't think that you can do whatever you please just because you've caught the fancy of the regional monarch! These people were captured in the Rashom Area, so I'll interrogate them, and you have no right to step in and tell me how to do my job!" Yin Gua said in a cold voice.

"I wouldn't dare to tell you how to do your job, Yin Gua. If you don't need my help, then forget about it. Having said that, a foreign invasion of the Rashom Area is a major issue that must be reported to the regional monarch right away," You Luo replied with a calm expression, seemingly completely unbothered.

Yin Gua's expression changed slightly upon hearing this, and he said, "The regional monarch is currently hosting the Three Region Conference, so I'll take care of this matter, and I'll report to him in person once my interrogation has yielded an outcome."

"That's fine, but seeing as I was here to see this, I think I should inform the regional monarch, just in case you forget," You Luo said with a faint smile.

Yin Gua was silent for a moment as he glowered intently at You Luo, then asked, "What exactly is it that you want, You Luo?"

"These people are all quite powerful, and their law powers are also very special. I played a role in capturing these people just now, so I think I should be entitled to some benefits," You Luo replied with a smile.

"So what do you want?" Yin Gua asked again.

"You can take them, but I want all of their treasures," You Luo replied.

"Fine. Most of these people come from the True Immortal Realm, so their treasures won't be any use to me anyway," Yin Gua replied after a brief moment of contemplation.

With that, You Luo swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of dark red light, which swept over the bodies of Han Li's group, taking all of their storage tools and immortal treasures.

With his immortal spiritual power sealed, Han Li's Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords had fallen to the ground, and they were also taken by You Luo.

"These are some fine treasures," You Luo remarked as she examined Shi Chuankong's silver lute and the nine Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords momentarily, then quickly stowed everything away.

"Alright, I'll be taking my leave now," You Luo said to Yin Gua, then flew away into the distance.

"Greedy whore!" Yin Gua spat through gritted teeth as he watched You Luo leave with a look of unadulterated hatred in his eyes.

After taking a deep breath, the resentment in his eyes faded a little, and he instructed, "Put them all in the infernal prison."

The two bull horn puppets beside him immediately lifted Han Li and the others up from the ground, then unwound the chains from around their bodies, but replaced them with sets of shackles that locked onto their upper bodies, leaving their legs free to move.

However, at the moment, Han Li and the others were so feeble that they could barely even walk, so there was no danger of them getting away, and they were quickly escorted out of the ring-shaped building by the two puppets.

A beast-drawn carriage was parked in front of the building, at the back of which was a cage that was several dozen feet in size.

Han Li's group was thrown into the cage, following which the carriage departed, and Han Li and the others were left to look at one another in silence.

Close to half a day later, the carriage arrived in front of a black building in the Rashom Area.

This was quite a large building that was square in shape, and there were countless glowing black jewels embedded into its walls, presenting a slightly chaotic sight to behold.

One of the bull horn puppets dragged Han Li's group out of the cage before throwing them heavily onto the ground.

Yin Gua had sealed away their immortal spiritual power and physical strength, so their bodies had become very frail.

Thanks to Han Li's incredible physical constitution, he was still quite sturdy even in this severely compromised state, but Fox 3 and the others couldn't help but groan in pain from the rough treatment.

Right at this moment, a burly man emerged from the black building.

He was very tall and imposing, and there were three huge fleshy growths on his forehead, giving him a rather fearsome and hideous appearance.

He was a High Zenith Stage Infernal being, and he was accompanied by a pair of armorclad Infernal Servants who were holding whips that were lined with hooked spikes.

"These are True Immortal Realm cultivators! Where did you capture them from?" the burly man asked with a surprised expression.

"They were personally captured by Master Yin Gua, and they're to be locked in the bottom level of the infernal prison," one of the bull horn puppets replied.

"Master Yin Gua personally captured them?" the burly man asked with a surprised expression.

"That's right, and Master Yin Gua will also be personally interrogating them, so be sure to keep a close eye on them," the bull horn puppet replied.

"Leave it to me," the burly man said with a serious expression.

With that, the two bull horn puppets promptly departed, flying away into the distance.

"Come with me," the burly man instructed with a sinister grin as he made his way toward the black building, and Han Li's group could only follow along, while the two armorclad Infernal Servants brought up the rear.

Everyone made their way into the black building, and the interior was quite spacious, with a stone platform that was around half a foot tall at the very center.

There were eight white stone pillars around the platform, all of which were riddled with countless squiggly runes, and there was also a black teleportation array that had been engraved onto the stone platform.

The burly man stepped onto the stone platform, then ordered, "Get on here."

Han Li and the others did as they were told, and Baili Yan, who was at the back of the group, was a little too slow, and he immediately received a whiplash from one of the Infernal Servants.

"Hurry up!"

The skin and flesh on Baili Yan's back was instantly torn open, and he was sent flying before falling heavily onto the stone platform.

The burly man paid no heed to this as he made a hand seal, and the teleportation array on the stone platform instantly began to buzz and flash incessantly.

Shortly thereafter, everyone vanished from within the array.

......

Countless scenes flashed past Han Li's eyes, and only after a long while did his vision return to normal, upon which he discovered that he was in a dimly lit hall.

There was a great abundance of baleful qi here, filling the air with a bone-chilling sensation, and even Han Li couldn't help but shudder slightly.

The burly man was very pleased by the discomfort being displayed by Han Li's group, and he began to make his way out of the hall, while Han Li and the others trailed along.

After emerging from the hall, they stepped into a long corridor, on either side of which was a series of prison cells, most of which were currently empty.

There was no end in sight to the corridor, and it was impossible to tell how many cells there were.

Blood-curdling howls could be heard occasionally ringing out up ahead, and Han Li glanced at the cells on either side of the corridor before suddenly asking, "So this is the infernal prison?"

The burly man stopped in his tracks, then turned around before approaching Han Li with a menacing look in his eyes.

The burly man then flipped a hand over to summon a spiked whip that was several times larger and more menacing in appearance than the ones used by the two Infernal Servants from earlier, and he said in a cold voice, "Where do you think you are right now? Don't talk unless you're being spoken to!"

"I'm just asking a question. Is there a rule against speaking in the infernal prison?" Han Li asked with a calm expression.

Chapter 733: No Escape

"You can speak if you want, as long as you can handle my whip!" the burly man said with a cold grin as he lashed out with his whip, sending it hurtling toward Han Li's face.

Han Li remained still on the spot displaying no intention to take evasive action, and the black whip drew to an abrupt halt right in front of his face, with its sharp spike mere inches away from his eyes.

Han Li continued to look at the whip with a calm expression, not even blinking or flinching at all.

"You've got guts, I'll give you that. No wonder Master Yin Gua went to the trouble of capturing you in person. I'll spare you this time considering it's your first offense, but don't test my patience again," the burly man warned as he withdrew his whip, then continued onward, and this time, Han Li didn't say anything.

"Fellow Daoist Li, we're not in a good position right now, so let's not start any conflicts," Shi Chuankong said in a barely audible voice.

Han Li nodded in response.

He had spoken just now not out of a moment of recklessness, but instead because he wanted to see how the burly man would react.

The attitudes displayed by Yin Gua and You Luo had struck him with a sense of unease that he couldn't quite put his finger on, but after what had just transpired, he was now feeling a bit more reassured.

After walking for a while longer, the group arrived in a huge space, where the air temperature suddenly spiked.

This was an underground plaza similar to the one in the ring-shaped building from before, and there were lit furnaces here that were releasing scorching heat that threatened to incinerate one's lungs upon inhalation.

There was a series of stone pillars on the plaza, tied to each of which was a prisoner, all of whom howling in agony from the burning heat.

Standing off to the side were some gray-robed wardens that were holding kettles, out of which they were occasionally pouring some type of white liquid into the mouths of the prisoners who were on the brink of death.

This white liquid would bring the prisoner back from the verge of death, and they would keep being tormented by the scorching flames.

"This is the first level of our nine-level infernal prison. Take a good look," the gray-robed man said to Han Li's group with a sinister grin.

"Chief Warden!"

Some of the nearby wardens hurriedly extended respectful bows upon catching sight of the gray-robed man.

The gray-robed man waved a dismissive hand in response, then Han Li and the others further onward. Before long, they had descended down a flight of stairs to the next floor.

This floor also had a massive plaza, but this one consisted of a series of black ponds that were giving off a bone-chilling aura.

There were prisoners currently submerged within the ponds, all of whom were deathly pale and trembling uncontrollably while letting loose gut-wrenching cries.

The gray-robed man continued onward, leading Han Li's group down another staircase to the third floor.

There were also some ponds on the plaza on the third floor, but they were filled with creatures like snakes and scorpions as opposed to any liquid.

All of the prisoners on this floor were forced to endure the agony of being ravaged by these venomous creatures.

After that came the fourth floor, then the fifth floor, then the sixth...

The gray-robed man seemed to want Han Li and the others to witness the horrors on every single floor, and he led the group through the infernal prison at a leisurely pace.

All of the prisoners on all of the floors were being subjected to horrific agony, and Han Li hadn't even heard of some of the torture methods on display.

Fox 3 and the others were looking a little pale at this point, and only after walking for a full hour did they finally arrive on the ninth floor of the infernal prison.

To their surprise, there were no torture methods being implemented on the ninth floor. Instead, there was only a series of prison cells, all of which appeared to be quite tidy.

However, the baleful qi was several times more abundant here than it was on the previous floors, to the extent that it was being manifested as visible gray mist.

Furthermore, the baleful qi here was also more ferocious than normal baleful qi, and muffled ghostly howls could be heard ringing out from within it.

As soon as Han Li and the others stepped onto this level, they felt as if their entire bodies were being pierced through by countless steel needles.

A cold grin appeared on the gray-robed man at the sight of their pained expressions, and he continued to lead them deeper into the area.

There were only around twenty to thirty cells on this floor, most of which were empty, and only a small portion of them were occupied.

There wasn't a single warden to be seen on the entire ninth floor, and all of the prisoners were also completely silent.

The gray-robed man opened five cells one after another, then pushed Han Li and the others into the cells.

"This is the ninth floor of our infernal prison. I hope you enjoy your time here," the gray-robed man cackled in a sinister manner, then immediately turned to depart, seemingly not wanting to stay here for any longer than he had to.

Han Li watched as he departed, then began to inspect his surroundings with slightly furrowed brows.

The pain of the baleful qi on this level infiltrating his body was still bearable, and all of a sudden, his expression changed slightly as he noticed something.

The cells here weren't remarkable in any way, they were just normal prison cells with some normal restrictions placed upon them.

At the moment, Han Li and the others had no strength in their bodies, so these cells were more than enough to contain them.

Through the bars of the cells, Han Li could easily see the other prisoners being held captive on this level, and that was what had caught his attention.

Even though his immortal spiritual power had been sealed away, his eyesight was still particularly sharp thanks to the spirit eye abilities that he had cultivated, and he noticed that all of the prisoners here were at least at the Golden Immortal Stage, while close to half of them were at the High Zenith Stage.

Furthermore, in addition to Gray Realm beings, there were two other people from the True Immortal Realm being held captive here.

Shi Chuankong was locked up in the cell right next to Han Li's, and upon seeing the surprised look on Han Li's face, he asked in a quiet voice, "Have you noticed something, Fellow Daoist Li?"

Han Li revealed his observations to Shi Chuankong.

Shi Chuankong took a glance at the two people from the True Immortal Realm before looking away again, clearly uninterested, then asked, "How do we get out of here, Fellow Daoist Li? You always have a bunch of tricks up your sleeve, can you think of a way out?"

"What could we possibly do in this situation? We're locked up in the bottom level of this infernal prison, and our immortal spiritual power has been sealed away, so we're no different from mortals at the moment," Han Li replied with a wry smile.

Right at this moment, a cold voice rang out from nearby.

"You're a fool if you think you can escape from the infernal prison."

Han Li and Shi Chuankong turned to discover that the voice had come from one of the nearby prison cells, which housed a thin man with a head of long and disheveled hair.

Black scales could be seen on the exposed skin of his arms and ankles, and it seemed that he was some type of Gray Realm being.

It was impossible to see the man's appearance, but his ears were extremely long, almost trailing all the way down to his shoulders, and his hearing seemed to be very sharp.

With their spiritual sense sealed away, Han Li and Shi Chuankong were unable to communicate through voice transmission, but they had spoken in barely audible voices, so it had come as quite a surprise that they had been overheard.

However, the sight of the Gray Realm being's long ears provided ample explanation for how they had been overheard.

"Who are you, and why do you say that?" Han Li asked with slightly furrowed brows.

The long-eared man ignored Han Li's questions as he chuckled coldly, "What kind of place do you think this infernal prison is?"

Fox 3, Mo Guang, and Baili Yan's attention had also been drawn to the long-eared man at this point, and Shi Chuankong asked with a puzzled expression, "Isn't this just a prison of the Infernal Tribe?"

"Ha! Where did you idiots come from? You don't even know what kind of place you're in!" the long-eared man chortled with mirth.

"What's that supposed to mean?" Shi Chuankong asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"Let me tell you what kind of situation you're in right now. This infernal prison is where the Infernal Tribe refines high-grade puppets, and we are to be used as the materials!" the long-eared man revealed with a mocking sneer.

Shi Chuankong's expression changed slightly upon hearing this, but Han Li wasn't overly surprised by this revelation.

Having witnessed the puppet refinement fortresses from earlier, he already had a feeling that this was the fate that awaited them.

"You saw all of the other levels on your way down here, right? Those prisoners are undergoing the initial bodily refinement process so that it'll be easier to refine them into puppets. From the instant that you stepped into this prison, your fate has been sealed! You will become the slaves of the Infernal Tribe for all of eternity!" the long-eared man guffawed in a deranged manner.

The expressions of Shi Chuankong and the others darkened significantly upon hearing this.

After his laughter subsided, the long-eared man seemed to have been drained of all strength, and he leaned back against the wall behind him in a defeated manner as he sighed, "All of us will be reduced to mere puppets on strings for the Infernal Tribe..."

"What else do you know? Tell me!" Shi Chuankong demanded in a cold voice.

As the young master of the Vast Origin House, he was extremely proud, and he would rather die than to be reduced to a puppet.

However, the long-eared man seemed to have completely lost interest in their conversation, and he refused to answer any more questions.

"It seems like you're quite familiar with the puppet refinement methods of the Infernal Tribe. Back in the Hundred Treasure Area, I came across some puppet refinement fortresses, and the things going on inside are similar to what's happening on the other levels of this infernal prison," Han Li said.

The long-eared man took a glance at Han Li upon hearing this, but still displayed no intention of saying anything.

"The Infernal Tribe's puppet refinement skills rank at the very top in the Gray Realm. What you saw in the Hundred Treasure Area are only their most crude and puppets that have no Infernal Soul Bugs planted into their bodies, so their consciousness will fade after they're refined into puppets.

“In contrast, we'll have Infernal Soul Bugs planted into our bodies, and we'll be eternally enslaved by the Infernal Tribe without even being able to put an end to our own lives."

This time, it was an elderly man with a head of white hair in another prison cell that had spoken.

He was also a Gray Realm being whose facial features weren't all that different from those of a normal human, and there was a resentful look on his face.

However, there was also a long black serpentine tail dragging along behind him, and it was unclear which tribe he was from.

"What are these Infernal Soul Bugs that you speak of?" Han Li asked as he turned to the elderly man, as did Shi Chuankong and the others.

Chapter 734: Doomed?

"I suppose it can't hurt to tell you about Infernal Soul Bugs. It's a type of ability that's unique to the Infernal Tribe, allowing Infernal beings to suck out the power of other people's souls before using their abilities to convert such power into bugs," the elderly man explained.

"And those Infernal Soul Bugs are then planted into the body?" Han Li asked.

"That's right. These bugs can infiltrate one's soul and take over the host, controlling their actions and even thoughts. Puppets refined using Infernal Soul Bugs are ones of the highest caliber as these puppets retain their consciousness and all of their abilities, including even their law powers," the elderly man replied with a nod.

The expressions of Han Li and the others darkened significantly upon hearing this, and Shi Chuankong spat through gritted teeth, "If that's the case, then I'd rather detonate my own nascent soul and die than be reduced to a living puppet!"

"Detonate your own nascent soul? The situation still isn't completely hopeless yet, would you really be willing to put an end to your own life?" Mo Guang asked in a cold voice.

"I wouldn't do that unless there was absolutely no hope left," Fox 3 sighed with a wry smile.

Baili Yan also heaved a heavy sigh and remarked, "No wonder the Infernal Tribe was able to rule over this region for so many years. They do have some tricks up their sleeve."

Meanwhile, Han Li remained silent with a contemplative look in his eyes.

The elderly man seemed to have gleaned Han Li's thoughts, and he warned, "I can sense that your soul is extremely powerful, but even for you, it would be impossible to resist an Infernal Soul Bug."

"Have Infernal Soul Bugs been planted into all of your bodies?" Han Li asked.

"That's right. Everyone on this ninth level has already had Infernal Soul Bugs planted into their bodies with the exception of the five of you," the elderly man sighed as a resentful look flashed through his eyes.

"Does that mean we have no choice but to be reduced to puppets?" Han Li asked.

"There's no longer any hope for any of us, but if the five of you don't want to follow in our footsteps, then I advise you to put an end to your own lives now. Otherwise, once the Infernal Soul Bugs are planted, suicide won't even be an option anymore," the elderly man replied.

"Thank you for your words of advice," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a grateful salute toward the elderly man, then fell silent again, as did Shi Chuankong and the others.

A short while later, Han Li shook his head to rid himself of his current train of thought, then sat down with his legs crossed, steeling himself against the pain of the baleful qi infiltrating his body while also inspecting his own internal condition.

He discovered that there were currently a series of black ripples in his mind, giving off immense restrictive force that sealed away both his soul and spiritual sense.

Furthermore, his dantian was completely filled by arcs of black lightning, with no space left unoccupied.

His nascent soul was trapped within the countless arcs of black lightning in a completely immobilized state, and its connection to Han Li had also been completely severed.

Not only had these arcs of black lightning sealed away his nascent soul, they were also constantly releasing wisps of black mist that slowly spread toward his nascent soul and his internal organs.

Thankfully, his internal organs had become extremely resilient due to the body refinement arts that he had cultivated, so they were able to ward off the black mist without too much trouble.

However, the situation was completely different for his nascent soul, which was already displaying signs of contamination, much to Han Li's dismay and agitation.

With his connection to his nascent soul severed, he couldn't examine how much damage this process was causing to it, but one could imagine that the damage would only become more and more untenable over time.

Han Li took a deep breath to suppress his agitation, then took a glance at his own fingers.

The only silver lining here was that You Luo had only taken his storage tools, but hadn't detected the existence of the Flower Branch domain.

At the moment, close to half of all of his wealth was in the Flower Branch domain, including the Heaven Controlling Vial, and if the vial were to be discovered, he didn't even dare to imagine what that would entail for him.

Unfortunately, the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber was also in his storage tools, so it was currently in You Luo's possession. Otherwise, with Shi Qinghou on his side, perhaps there could be a twist in the tale.

Han Li took a subtle glance at his surroundings, and after verifying that there were no surveillance restrictions nearby, he leaned back against the wall of his cell, then pressed a hand against his own forehead, seemingly struggling to withstand the pain of the baleful qi infiltrating his body.

At the same time, he was drawing upon all of the spiritual sense in his mind to attack the black ripples there.

The black ripples were only able to restrict his spiritual sense within his mind, but weren't able to completely seal away his spiritual sense.

At the moment, he was unable to advance any further beyond the pinnacle of the Golden Immortal Stage, so during his time in the Gray Realm, he had prioritized the cultivation of the Spirit Refinement Technique, thereby significantly enhancing his own spiritual sense.

Even though the black ripples were extremely formidable, they were still trembling slightly in the face of Han Li's immense spiritual sense.

Han Li was ecstatic to see this, and he immediately redoubled his efforts, sending one wave of spiritual sense after another surging against the black ripples.

Two hours flew by in a flash, and the black ripples were trembling more and more violently, but they still remained intact.

At this point, Han Li's complexion had grown a little pale. With his immortal spiritual power sealed away, channeling his spiritual sense for extended periods of time was extremely taxing on his body.

However, he couldn't afford to stop. He didn't know when Yin Gua would be returning, and once Infernal Soul Bugs were forcibly planted into their bodies, it would be impossible to escape.

Hence, he had to free himself from the restrictions in his body at all costs, then flee the infernal prison before Yin Gua's return.

With that in mind, Han Li took a deep breath and continued to toil away.

Another two hours passed by, and under his tireless efforts, the black ripples were finally beginning to loosen a little.

Han Li was very encouraged to see this, and he redoubled his efforts once again.

The black ripples were trembling violently, particularly at their center, and right at this moment, Han Li channeled his Sword Observation Arts, upon which a streak of translucent light shot out of his soul, then transformed into a blurry sword projection before striking the center of the black ripples.

Finally, a small gash was sliced into the black ripples, and the spiritual sense sword flew out from within before entering the Flower Branch domain.

Immediately thereafter, the black ripples mended themselves once again, but at this point, Han Li had already completed his objective, and the spiritual sense sword flew deeper into the Flower Branch space at his behest.

At this moment, Daoist Xie was standing in his bamboo pavilion in the Flower Branch domain, looking up at the sky.

Right at this moment, a burst of translucent light descended into the pavilion before transforming into a blurry projection of Han Li.

"What happened, Fellow Daoist Han? Our spiritual connection was suddenly severed," Daoist Xie asked as it approached the projection of Han Li.

"It's a long story. Right now, I've been captured, and my immortal spiritual power has been sealed away..."

The projection of Han Li gave a brief recount of what had transpired up to this point, and Han Li was hoping that Daoist Xie would perhaps have a way to unravel the restriction in his body, given its proficiency in the laws of lightning.

"There is indeed some information in my memories pertaining to the laws of baleful lightning. Essentially, it comes from the same origins as my laws of lightning, so I should be able to help you break the restrictions in your dantian. Having said that, those restrictions were planted by a Great Encompassment Stage being, so I'm not fully confident," Daoist Xie said.

"That's fine. As long as you can break one of the seals in my dantian, I'll be able to channel my time law powers and take care of the rest of the restrictions on my own," the projection of Han Li said with an elated expression.

"In that case, I feel a bit more confident," Daoist Xie replied with a nod.

"Alright, I'll go make some preparations, and we can begin soon," the projection of Han Li said, then flew over to a corner of the spirit medicine garden, where the Myriad Soul Herb had been planted.

Han Li was concerned that storing the spirit plant in a jade box for an extended period of time would impact its medicinal properties, so he planted it in the Flower Branch space.

The projection of Han Li raised a hand to release a streak of light, which wrapped itself around the Myriad Soul Herb before uprooting it, and an elated look appeared on the projection's face.

This was exactly what he needed right now, so it was an immense stroke of fortune that he had decided to plant it in the Flower Branch space.

By his estimates, with the help of this Myriad Soul Herb, he had a roughly 50% chance of unraveling the black ripples in his mind.

If he could do that, then he would have much better chances of breaking the baleful lightning restrictions in his dantian with Daoist Xie's assistance.

With that in mind, the projection of Han Li began to fly out of the Flower Branch domain with the Myriad Soul Herb, only to abruptly stop in its tracks as a grim look appeared on its face.

Right at this moment, Yin Gua drifted onto the ninth floor of the infernal prison.

Han Li could only grit his teeth and lower his head in frustration.

In the next instant, Yin Gua appeared in front of the cell that Han Li was in, observing him with a fervent look in his eyes.

Han Li's heart completely sank upon seeing this, and he slowly rose to his feet.

Before he had a chance to think about anything else, Yin Gua made a hand seal, and the door of the cell sprang open at his behest.

Upon entering the cell, he swept a sleeve through the air, conjuring up two giant hands of black lightning that grabbed onto Han Li, locking him firmly into place.

Han Li felt the air constrict around him, and he was completely immobilized, while Shi Chuankong and the others could only look on in alarm.

Han Li made no effort to resist, merely looking directly at Yin Gua as he asked, "Are you planning to refine me into a puppet?"

Chapter 735: Bug Implantation

"Oh? It sounds like you already know what's about to happen to you. That saves me the trouble of having to explain things. With your time law powers, you'll be a fantastic asset to me, so as long as you remain loyal, I'll be sure to treat you well," Yin Gua said with a faint smile, then raised a hand to release a ball of black light, which then transformed into an ovular object that very much resembled an insect's egg.

Yin Gua made a hand seal with a solemn expression, and the black egg immediately began to squirm and wriggle. Shortly thereafter, a small black bug burrowed its way out from within.

The creature resembled a slug with dozens of feelers of different lengths all over its body, and it had a human face that strongly resembled Yin Gua's, presenting a harrowing sight to behold.

Han Li's expression instantly darkened significantly at the sight of the creature.

"Don't try to resist, just let it enter your soul. It's actually quite an enjoyable process, so make sure to savor it!" Yin Gua said in a cold voice, and the Infernal Soul Bug shot forward at his behest, quickly burrowing its way into Han Li's glabella.

Han Li felt a burst of sharp pain spear through his head, as if someone had forced a red-hot nail into his mind, and he couldn't help but give a muffled groan as his body began to tremble uncontrollably.

The Infernal Soul Bug quickly entered his mind before burrowing its way toward his soul, and it was completely unaffected by the black ripples in his mind.

Before long, it had already reached Han Li's consciousness, and a tiny soul figure that was identical to Han Li in appearance emerged.

The soul figure channeled the Sword Observation Arts to send a translucent sword projection flying out of its body, and the sword projection hurtled through the air, slicing through the Infernal Soul Bug with ease, causing it to explode into two clouds of black qi.

However, the two clouds of black qi then instantly fused back together to form the Infernal Soul Bug again, and it continued onward, seemingly completely unscathed.

The soul figure was quite surprised to see this, but it remained calm and collected as a spiritual sense chain flew out of its body, then instantly wrapped itself several times around the Infernal Soul Bug, locking it firmly into place.

A mocking sneer appeared on the Infernal Soul Bug's face as its body exploded once again,freeing itself from the spiritual sense chain before flying onward as a cloud of black mist.

The Infernal Soul Bug wasn't that far away from Han Li's soul to begin with, and the cloud of black mist that it had transformed into quickly came into contact with Han Li's soul.

The cloud of black mist then reverted back into the Infernal Soul Bug before pouncing onto Han Li's soul figure and attempting to burrow its way inside.

The soul figure let loose an alarmed cry as several spiritual sense chains shot out of its body, forming a spiritual sense cage around the Infernal Soul Bug.

Trapped within the spiritual sense cage, the Infernal Soul Bug was slowed down significantly, but at this point, close to half of its body had already burrowed its way into Han Li's soul, and it continued onward without pause, burrowing deeper and deeper, albeit at a slower rate than before.

An urgent look appeared in the soul figure's eyes upon seeing this, and more spiritual sense chains flew out of its body to ensnare the Infernal Soul Bug, wrapping it in a tight cocoon.

Yin Gua's brows furrowed slightly as he took a cold glance at the trembling Han Li, following which he harrumphed coldly, "If you insist on prolonging the pain, then I'll grant you your wish!"

Immediately thereafter, five streaks of black light shot out of his fingertips before piercing into Han Li's head, and blood instantly began to flow out of all of his orifices.

At the same time, his body began to tremble much more violently, looking as if he were spasming uncontrollably, and an agonized howl escaped his lips.

Shi Chuankong and the others were horrified to see this, but there was nothing that they could do, and the white-haired elderly man and the long-eared man were looking at Han Li while shaking their heads with forlorn expressions, lamenting the fact that he hadn't heeded their advice.

"Oh? How interesting! Let's see how much longer you can last!"

A look of sadistic pleasure appeared on Yin Gua's face as the five beams of black light shooting out of his fingertips became even thicker.

Only after a full fifteen minutes had passed did the beams of black light shooting out of Yin Gua's fingertips fade away, and at the same time, the two giant lightning hands grabbing onto Han Li also disappeared.

At this point, half of Han Li's body was already drenched in blood, and he collapsed to the ground in an unconscious state, while his aura had also become extremely feeble.

"Insolent fool!" Yin Gua scoffed as he strode out of Han Li's cell, then turned his gaze to Shi Chuankong.

Having witnessed what had just happened to Han Li, Shi Chuankong's heart had already completely sunk, and his expression instantly changed slightly at the sight of Yin Gua's menacing gaze.

Yin Gua passed straight through the restrictions around Shi Chuankong's cell, then conjured up two more black lightning hands to grab onto Shi Chuankong's body.

His patience seemed to have been completely exhausted by Han Li, and he grabbed onto Shi Chuankong's head before releasing a continuous burst of black light into it.

Shi Chuankong's expression changed drastically as he let loose a blood-curdling howl, and blood began to gush out of all of his orifices.

Around fifteen minutes later, Yin Gua released Shi Chuankong, who also fell to the ground in an unconscious state.

Yin Gua took a cold glance at Shi Chuankong, then left his cell and made his way toward Fox 3's cell.

......

An hour later, Yin Gua drifted out of Baili Yan's cell, and at this point, the entirety of Han Li's group had fallen unconscious.

Yin Gua's complexion was slightly pale, and he took a deep breath to steady himself.

The gray-robed man suddenly emerged, seemingly out of thin air, and there was a sycophantic look on his face as he said, "Congratulations on obtaining five more fine puppets, Master Yin Gua."

A faint smile appeared on Yin Gua's face, and he instructed, "These five puppets will be very useful to me, so make sure you keep a close eye on them. Do I make myself clear, Yin Chan?"

"Crystal clear, Master Yin Gua. I'll be sure to monitor them closely," the gray-robed man hurriedly promised.

"Infernal Soul Bugs have already been planted into their bodies, but it'll take a hundred days before the bugs completely fuse with them. Once they wake up, take them straight to the Profound Yin Palace, and don't let anyone from the other areas come into contact with them," Yin Gua instructed.

"Yes, Master Yin Gua. Will you be alright after planting five Infernal Soul Bug in succession?" Yin Chan asked with a concerned expression.

"I'll be fine, I just need some time to rest and recuperate. If you do a good job here, I'll be sure to reward you handsomely," Yin Gua replied, then vanished from the spot in a flash, seemingly in quite a hurry to begin the recuperation process.

Yin Chan hurriedly extended a grateful bow, and only after a long while did he stand up straight again.

He took a glance at Han Li and the others with a cold sneer on his face, then turned to depart, only to suddenly stop in his tracks.

As it turned out, You Luo was making her way down from the staircase leading to the ninth floor.

Yin Chan faltered slightly upon seeing this, following which a bright smile appeared on his face as he hurriedly approached You Luo and asked, "What brings you here, Ms. You Luo? My apologies for not coming out to greet you sooner."

"Am I not allowed to come here?" You Luo asked in an indifferent voice.

"Of course not! You're welcome to visit the infernal prison at anytime," Yin Chan hurriedly replied with a slightly fearful expression.

You Luo harrumphed coldly before making her way down the corridor, and Yin Chan hurriedly followed along as he asked in a careful manner, "May I ask the purpose of your visit, Ms. You Luo?"

You Luo paid no heed to him as she continued onward without pause, and before long, she drew to a halt in front of the cells of Han Li and the others.

Yin Chan's expression changed slightly as he thought back to Yin Gua's instructions not to let anyone from other areas come into contact with Han Li and the others, but before he could say anything, You Luo sighed, "Master Yin Gua can really be quite cruel sometimes. Even if he's going to refine these five into puppets, surely he didn't need to be so rough with them, wouldn't you agree, Chief Warden Yin Chan?"

Yin Chan gave a muffled response, not daring to comment on Yin Gua's actions.

You Luo raised a hand to release a burst of black light, which split up into five before flying into the cells.

"What are you doing, Ms. You Luo?" Yin Chan asked as he stepped forward with an urgent expression.

The five bursts of black light transformed into five slender feelers at You Luo's behest, and they briefly brushed over the glabellas of Han Li and the others to inspect their conditions before fading away, much to Yin Chan's relief.

"Looks like Master Yin Gua forcibly planted Infernal Soul Bugs into their souls. Such a direct and callous implantation method will work, but it'll take a very long time for the Infernal Soul Bug to fuse with their souls.

“I have some Heavenly Yin Soul Nourishing Pills here, feed each of them one pill a day, and the amount of time required for puppet refinement will be significantly reduced," You Luo said as she tossed black jade vial to Yin Chan.

There was a black talisman adhered to the mouth of the vial, and even through the vial, one could sense pure soul power fluctuations from its contents.

Yin Chan's expression changed slightly upon hearing this.

Heavenly Yin Soul Nourishing Pills were extremely precious soul nourishing pills that were effective even for Great Encompassment cultivators.

Under normal circumstances, it would take Han Li and the others around half a month to wake up, but with these pills, a few days would suffice.

However, Yin Chan couldn't understand why You Luo was willing to sacrifice a vial of Heavenly Yin Soul Nourishing Pills just to aid Yin Gua in his puppet refinement...

Chapter 736: Perplexed

Despite Yin Chan's befuddlement, he immediately extended a grateful bow as he said, "Please accept my gratitude on behalf of Master Yin Gua, Ms. You Luo."

"There are quite a few Heavenly Yin Soul Nourishing Pills left in this vial. Once the five of them wake up, you can keep the leftover pills. If I recall correctly, you only reached the mid-High Zenith Stage about a hundred years ago, and these pills should be very helpful for consolidating your cultivation base," You Luo said with a smile.

Yin Chan was ecstatic to hear this, and he hurriedly repiled, "Thank you, Ms. You Luo. If you ever need anything from me, I'll for sure be at your service."

There were forty Heavenly Yin Soul Nourishing Pills in the vial, so there should still be close to twenty leftover from what had to be allotted to Han Li and the others, and at the very least, these pills would be enough to save him several thousand years of arduous cultivation.

"Seeing as you made such a kind offer, I'll gladly accept. I'd like to borrow these five once they're awake, and I hope you can help me out there, Chief Warden Yin Chan," You Luo said with a smile.

Yin Chan's expression instantly stiffened upon hearing this, and he wanted to slap himself for making such a reckless promise.

"Is that going to be a problem?" You Luo asked.

"It's not that I'm unwilling to help, the problem is that the five of them are going to be refined into puppets by Master Yin Gua, so if you want to borrow them, I'll have to secure Master Yin Gua's permission first," Yin Chan replied in a careful manner.

"Master Yin Gua must've severely exerted himself by manifesting five Infernal Soul Bugs at once, so he definitely won't be coming out of seclusion for at least a month. I'm only going to be borrowing the five of them for two or three days at most, and as long as neither of us say anything, how is Master Yin Gua going to find out?" You Luo asked with a faint smile.

Yin Chan took a glance at the black jade vial in his hand, and an indecisive look appeared on his face.

"Besides, even if Master Yin Gua does somehow find out, surely he wouldn't mind lending the five of them to me, considering I contributed so many Heavenly Yin Soul Nourishing Pills to his cause," You Luo continued.

"That may be true, but Master Yin Gua specifically told me..."

You Luo's expression darkened slightly as she interjected, "I'm borrowing the five of them for a matter concerning the regional monarch, not for myself. If you don't want to help me, then I won't force you to do anything against your will, but if the regional monarch asks about the delay, then I'll have to tell him the truth."

Yin Chan's heart jolted slightly upon hearing this, following which a wry smile appeared on his face as he replied, "In that case, it seems like I don't have much choice in the matter."

"Alright, then I'll leave it to you, Chief Warden Yin Chan," You Luo said as the smile returned to her face, following which she turned to depart.

Yin Chan watched You Luo as she departed, and only after standing in silence for a long while did he heave a faint sigh before making his way into Han Li's cell.

There, he removed the talisman from the black jade vial, then tipped out a small gray pill from within.

After examining the pill carefully to ensure that there was nothing amiss about it, he fed it to Han Li, immediately following which his aura began to stabilize.

After that, Yin Chan repeated the process with all of Han Li's companions before departing.

......

In his unconscious state, Han Li felt as if claps of thunder and flashes of lightning were raging incessantly in his mind, and the intense agony was threatening to tear his consciousness apart.

Is this how everything's going to end?

A sense of despair welled up from the bottom of his heart.

He slowly opened his eyes, and everything felt very blurry and indistinct.

All of a sudden, his dimly lit prison cell began to brighten, and his surroundings also began to transform. The cell gradually disappeared, replaced by an elegantly furnished hall, and there were several pots filled with rare and exotic flowers beside him.

Seated on a wicker chair beside an ornate wooden table in the hall was an indistinct figure who was looking at something with their head lowered.

The figure gradually became clearer in Han Li's eyes, and it was revealed to a white-robed young woman.

"Wan'er!" Han Li called out involuntarily at the sight of the young woman, and she raised her head to reveal a set of beautiful features that had appeared countless times in Han Li's dreams.

It was none other than Nangong Wan!

However, right as he was about to say something to her, his consciousness abruptly shuddered, and everything around him disintegrated into darkness once again, while his body began to descend into a bottomless abyss.

After what felt like an eternity, a surge of warmth suddenly began to flow through his mind, and the excruciating pain in his consciousness rapidly faded away, allowing his fractured mind to piece itself back together.

Before long, the surge of warmth dissipated, and the excruciating pain returned to his mind, but it was already somewhat less potent than before.

Some time later, the surge of warmth reappeared to nourish his mind.

Han Li's consciousness gradually became more and more intact, and finally, after the fourth flow of warmth had surged through his mind, his eyelids fluttered slightly before springing open, and he found himself staring up at the ceiling of his cell.

Even though his consciousness had recovered, his body was still in a state of agony and completely immobile.

Before long, Yin Chan appeared in Han Li's field of view, looking down at him with a surprised expression as he remarked, "Your spiritual sense must be extremely powerful for you to have awakened in just four days."

Han Li wanted to say something, but he was too feeble to utter even a single sound.

"Now that you're awake, I suppose I may as well as feed you this fifth Heavenly Yin Soul Nourishing Pill," Yin Chan said as he tipped a gray pill out of a black jade vial, then fed it to Han Li, who made no effort to resist.

"You're a lucky bunch. If it isn't for these pills, you'd still have to suffer for at least ten more days before you can wake up," Yin Chan chuckled coldly, then quickly departed, exiting Han Li's field of view.

After taking a moment to collect himself, Han Li hurriedly examined his own internal condition, upon which he discovered that all of the restrictions in his dantian and mind were still present.

On top of that, his body and meridians had sustained severe damage, and the shackles on his body rendered him completely immobile.

Han Li paid no heed to his own physical injuries as he hurriedly examined his own soul, upon which a grim look quickly appeared on his face.

His soul was hovering within his consciousness in a stable fashion, so could it be that the Infernal Soul Bug had already completely fused into it?

Han Li couldn't help but shudder slightly at the thought of the Infernal Soul Bug, but he then quickly noticed that something wasn't quite right.

Inside his soul, the Infernal Soul Bug was trapped within several spiritual sense chains, outside of which was a layer of some type of transparent substance.

Whatever the transparent substance was, it seemed to have enveloped the Infernal Soul Bug and rendered it completely immobile.

On top of that, he didn't feel as if his consciousness had been compromised at all, which was naturally a huge relief, but also very perplexing.

Right at this moment, the gray pill that he had just been fed began to melt, and it quickly transformed into a surge of warmth that entered his mind before rapidly spreading outward.

The pain in his mind was instantly significantly alleviated, and he felt as if his soul were basking in a hot spring.

Thinking back to the surges of warmth that had periodically arisen in his mind during his unconscious state, it became apparent to Han Li that this gray pill had been the root cause.

Judging from the effects of the pill, it was clearly extremely precious, and according to Yin Chan, this was already the fifth one that he had been fed, and he couldn't help but wonder why he was being administered such valuable pills.

All of a sudden, Han Li noticed that a series of extremely thin streaks of barely detectable translucent light were being released into his mind, then fused into his soul before reinforcing the transparent light membrane around the Infernal Soul Bug.

A series of thoughts instantly flashed through Han Li's mind upon seeing this, but in the end, he shook his head to rid himself of the train of thought before closing his eyes and taking some deep breaths to steady himself.

Close to half a day later, his eyes abruptly sprang open, and having regained some strength, he was able to slowly struggle up into a seated position.

He took a subtle glance at his surroundings, then raised a hand to his own forehead while feigning a pained expression.

Immediately thereafter, a burst of translucent light flashed over his fingers, and Myriad Soul Herb suddenly appeared in his grasp before being instantly stuffed into his mouth.

After chewing the Myriad Soul Herb a few times, he quickly swallowed it.

Even though his immortal spiritual power had been completely sealed away, rendering him unable to access the Flower Branch domain, the shard of spiritual sense that he had projected into it earlier was able to retrieve some things from within the domain for him.

Right at this moment, the white-haired elderly man in the nearby cell turned to Han Li with a perplexed look in his eyes, while Han Li leaned back against the wall of his cell and closed his eyes in silence.

At this moment, his consciousness was churning violently as all of his spiritual sense was stirred up into a frenzy, relentlessly attacking the black ripples in his mind.

Perhaps it was thanks to the five pills that he had been fed, but his spiritual sense had been further enhanced, and the black ripples were trembling incessantly.

At the same time, bursts of black qi were surging into his mind in a steady stream, and it was none other than the medicinal power of the Myriad Soul herb.

The black qi was giving off immense soul power fluctuations that were only slightly weaker than Han Li's own, but they were extremely violent and untamed, much like a wild stallion that refused to be ridden.

Furthermore, resentful roars could be heard ringing out within the black qi.

Myriad Soul Herbs were found in dark places where deceased spirits converged, and in essence, it was a spirit plant formed by the resentful energy of countless souls. This made it very difficult to absorb its medicinal power to enhance one's soul, and most of its medicinal power was often wasted during this process.

However, Han Li's current objective wasn't to absorb its medicinal power. Instead, he was using it to attack the black ripples in his mind, so this worked out perfectly for him.

Chapter 737: Who is She?

Han Li took a deep breath, then closed his eyes and focused single-mindedly on directing the black qi from the Myriad Soul Herb toward the black ripples in his mind, attempting to break the restriction.

With his past experience in contending against this restriction, he was able to make some rapid progress, and the black ripples quickly began to display signs of loosening.

Han Li's eyes lit up as he unleashed his Sword Observation Arts once again, but this time, he conjured up three spiritual sense swords at once, all of which shot forth in unison to strike three different points in the black ripples.

Three tiny gashes were instantly sliced into the black ripples, which immediately attempted to seal the gashes, but right at this moment, three translucent spiritual sense chains shot out of Han Li's soul, forcing their way into the three gashes.

The black ripples were doing everything in their power to seal the gashes, but the spiritual sense chains were extremely resilient and remained firmly in place. On top of that, they were releasing bursts of translucent light while wriggling incessantly, attempting to widen the three gashes.

A fierce clash ensued between the black ripples and spiritual sense chains, plunging Han Li's mind into a state of complete chaos, but Han Li was ecstatic to see this, and he closed his eyes while continuing to attack the black ripples with his spiritual sense and the power of the Myriad Soul Herb.

A day and a night flew by in the blink of an eye.

Han Li remained completely still, leaning against the wall of his cell this entire time, while the unrest in his mind continued to rage incessantly.

At this point, dozens of gashes had already been torn into the black ripples, every single one of which was filled by a spiritual sense chain that was squirming incessantly.

Upon closer inspection, one would discover that the restriction had dimmed significantly, and it was also trembling violently, but it remained stubbornly intact.

At this point, Han Li's complexion had turned quite pale, and large droplets of sweat were dripping down from his face.

After a day and a night of tireless toil, his spiritual sense had been severely overexerted, and the Myriad Soul Herb's medicinal power was also close to running out, so he wouldn't be able to keep this up for much longer.

As expected of a seal planted by a Great Encompassment cultivator. I have to make my move now!

With that in mind, Han Li gritted his teeth, and the dozens of spiritual sense chains in his mind lit up in unison while also flailing violently like tentacles, further widening the dozens of gashes in the black ripples and causing them to flash erratically.

At the same time, all of the spiritual sense in Han Li's mind was being directed into the spiritual sense chains, rapidly strengthening and thickening them.

Simultaneously, the black qi formed by the Myriad Soul Herb transformed into a pair of giant black hands that grabbed onto the black ripples before tearing them apart to widen the gashes even further.

Despite this, the restriction was still standing strong, displaying no signs of breaking apart.

In one final effort, Han Li conjured up a series of translucent sword projections with his Sword Observation Arts, and all of them instantly converged to form a giant sword projection that struck the black ripples with tremendous force.

A huge gash was instantly torn into the black ripples, and they were unable to hold themselves together any longer, exploding with a dull thump before quickly dissipating.

At the same time, what little remained of the Myriad Soul Herb's medicinal power was also completely scattered by the destruction of the black ripples.

Han Li immediately began gasping for air, and with all of his spiritual sense exhausted, he was on the verge of blacking out.

He had truly given everything that he had to give, and for his efforts, he had finally broken one of the restrictions in his body, much to his elation and excitement.

No, I can't fall asleep!

Han Li gritted his teeth tightly as he forced himself to remain conscious, and only after several hours of rest and recuperation did his spiritual sense recover somewhat.

It was still far from making a full recovery, but at the very least, no longer had much trouble remaining conscious.

A hint of elation flashed through his eyes as he inspected his own internal condition with his spiritual sense.

Prior to this, he had also been able to inspect his own internal condition, but to nowhere near the same level of detail that his spiritual sense provided.

As he did this, a grim look quickly appeared on his face.

The only restriction that was worthy of note in his body was the baleful lightning restriction on his dantian, and if that could be unraveled, then all of the other restrictions would also easily be dealt with.

However, the restriction on his dantian was far more powerful than he imagined, far more so than even the black ripple restriction in his mind, and it was most likely going to be impossible to unravel even with Daoist Xie's help.

Han Li's brows furrowed tightly as he tried to think of a way to unravel the baleful lightning restriction.

Right at this moment, the sound of footsteps rang out, and he immediately withdrew his spiritual sense while also lowering his head.

Two figures, one tall and one short, appeared at the entrance of the ninth level, and they were none other than Yin Chan and You Luo.

Han Li took a glance at You Luo out of his peripheral vision, and a perplexed look flashed through his eyes.

He had always felt like this woman was rather strange. In particular, it was only after he had been fed the pills that had been given to Yin Chan by her that he was able to unravel the restriction in his mind and give himself a glimmer of hope.

Could it be that she had some type of ulterior motive, or perhaps the Infernal Regional Master was plotting something?

Han Li lowered his head even further as these thoughts ran through his mind, and he condensed all of his spiritual sense, not daring to release even the slightest spiritual sense fluctuations.

"One of them is already awake!" You Luo remarked in a surprised manner as her gaze fell upon Han Li.

"His spiritual sense seems to be particularly powerful, and he already woke up yesterday. Of course, it's all thanks to your Heavenly Yin Soul Nourishing Pills. Otherwise, he'd be out for at least half a month," Yin Chan said.

"His spiritual sense must indeed be quite powerful if he woke up in only four days. Wake the other four up as well. There's not much time left, and the regional master is still waiting. Go and feed them their pills for today, and I'll give you a hand," You Luo instructed.

Yin Chan gave an affirmative response, then entered Baili Yan's cell before feeding him a Heavenly Yin Soul Nourishing Pill.

After that, You Luo made a strange-looking hand seal, and a series of black runes emerged from her hands before converging to form a black lotus flower, which drifted through the air while rapidly shrinking down into a speck of black light before vanishing into Baili Yan's glabella.

Bursts of black light instantly emerged over Baili Yan's head, illuminating the rest of his body black as well.

A projection of a barefoot woman sitting on a lotus flower chair appeared within the black light, and the woman had a benevolent smile of unconditional love on her face, as if she were the mother of all things.

The projection raised an arm before gently stroking a hand over Baili Yan's hand while murmuring something to him, much like a mother waking her child.

A series of black ripples instantly appeared over Baili Yan's head before spreading outward, and in the next instant, he abruptly shuddered before slowly opening his eyes, following which the projection of the woman faded away.

A bewildered look flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

"No matter how many times I see it, your soul calling ability still never ceases to amaze me, Ms. You Luo. I've heard that even if someone's dead, as long as they haven't been dead for more than three days and their soul is still intact, you can resurrect them using this technique. Is that really true?" Yin Chan asked with an admiring look in his eyes.

"Next," You Luo said with a cold expression, completely ignoring Yin Chan's question.

"My apologies for speaking out of turn, Ms. You Luo," Yin Chan apologized with a sheepish smile, then hurriedly entered Fox 3's cell before feeding him a Heavenly Yin Soul Nourishing Pills.

You Luo unleashed the same soul calling technique again, and Fox 3 quickly awakened as well.

Before long, Mo Guang and Shi Chuankong had also returned to consciousness, and You Luo turned to Yin Chan with a serious expression as she warned, "What happens next is strictly confidential, so it would be best if you didn't know anything about it."

Yin Chan faltered slightly upon hearing this, then nodded in response before making a hand seal, conjuring up black light barriers around all of the cells aside from the ones that Han Li's group were in.

"I've already activated the restrictions on all of the other cells, so take your time, and call for me when you're done," Yin Chan said, then turned to depart.

In the instant that he turned around, You Luo reached out like lightning to tap a finger against the back of his chest, releasing a burst of black light into his body.

Yin Chan's expression changed drastically, but before he had a chance to do anything, a ball of black light emerged over his head, and he was completely immobilized and rooted to the spot with an alarmed look on his face.

Han Li and the others were naturally very surprised to see this, and they all turned to You Luo with wary expressions.

You Luo withdrew her arm, then made her way into Han Li's cell.

Han Li struggled to his feet as he looked directly at You Luo and said, "It sounds like you need us to do something for you. May I ask what that is?"

All of a sudden, You Luo made a hand seal, releasing a streak of white light that flew around Han Li in a flash, severing all of the shackles on his body.

"Who are you, and what's the meaning of this?" Han Li asked.

"Do you still not know who I am?" You Luo asked with a faint smile.

Chapter 738: Tumultuous Experiences

Han Li's expression changed slightly upon hearing this, and he replied, "I don't believe we've met before."

Indeed, he had no recollection of You Luo, but strangely enough, he had felt a sense of familiarity as soon as he had laid eyes upon her. It was just that given the urgency of the situation that he was in, he had no time to ponder where this sense of familiarity was coming from.

You Luo's smile widened slightly as bursts of black light suddenly emerged from her body, then intertwined above her to form a projection of a three-eyed giant ape with a strange horn on its head.

"You're the Weeping Soul Beast!" Han Li exclaimed with a stunned expression. [1]

"Looks like we've been apart for so long that you've already forgotten about me, Master," Weeping Soul sighed with a dejected expression.

"Of course not, I'm just so surprised! Didn't you ascend to the True Immortal Realm after being summoned all those years ago? How did you end up in the Gray Realm?" Han Li asked with a mixture of shock and elation in his eyes.

Meanwhile, Shi Chuankong and the others were all looking on with bewildered expressions.

They had no idea how Han Li had suddenly gained such a powerful subordinate in the Gray Realm, and all of a sudden, Han Li was looking even more unfathomable in their eyes.

Only Mo Guang appeared to be quite calm and collected, seemingly already accustomed to Han Li's ability to work miracles.

"That's a story for another time. For now, use this Gold Rinse Lightning Bead to undo the restriction on your dantian first," You Luo replied as she flipped a hand over to produce an egg-sized golden bead that was riddled with lightning patterns.

The bead was giving off a powerful yang-attribute aura that was rather similar to that of Han Li's Divine Devilbane Lightning, and as soon as it appeared, all of the surrounding baleful qi instantly dissipated.

"Could it be that this bead contains Bone Rinsing Golden Lightning?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

A hint of surprise flashed through Weeping Soul's eyes upon hearing this, and she replied, "You know of Bone Rinsing Golden Lightning? That's right, this bead was refined from Bone Rinsing Golden Lightning, which directly counteracts Yin Gua's baleful lightning law powers."

The golden lightning bead shot forward at her behest as she spoke, vanishing into Han Li's dantian in a flash.

Arcs of golden lightning instantly emerged within his dantian before spreading outward in all directions, filling his entire body in the blink of an eye.

Han Li immediately sat down with his legs crossed, and right at this moment, arcs of black lightning began to rise up from his lower abdomen to clash against the golden lightning.

He shuddered violently in pain as cold sweat came pouring down his face, which was spasming uncontrollably from the agony that he was being subjected to.

More and more golden lightning was erupting out of the lightning bead in his dantian, instantly eradicating the arcs of black lightning upon contact, but there were far too many of these arcs of black lightning, and they seemed to have a mind of their own, converging to form thicker and more powerful arcs of black lightning to contend against the golden lightning.

The golden lightning was unable to quickly eradicate these thicker arcs of black lightning, and an impasse ensued.

Right at this moment, rays of radiant golden light surged out of Han Li's body, giving off bursts of time law power fluctuations that fused together with the golden lightning to contend against the black lightning.

With the assistance of his time law powers, the golden lightning instantly gained the upper hand, and several dull thumps rang out within his body in quick succession, following which a burst of black qi was forced out of his dantian.

The golden light radiating from his body instantly brightened significantly, causing the nearby space to buzz and tremble violently, and even Weeping Soul was forced back a few steps.

A hint of surprise flashed through her eyes as she praised, "Your immortal spiritual power is incredible, Master! It's not inferior even compared with the average High Zenith cultivator."

"These baleful lightning restrictions were personally planted by Yin Gua. Now that mine has been removed, will he be able to sense it?" Han Li asked with a serious expression.

"Rest assured, Master. Yin Gua has severely overexerted himself after manifesting five Infernal Soul Bugs at once, and he's currently recuperating in seclusion, so he won't detect anything," Weeping Soul assured with a smile.

Han Li's expression eased slightly upon hearing this, and he opened his mouth to release the Gold Rinsing Lightning Bead, but it had shrunk down slightly compared with before.

At the same time, he flicked a finger through the air to release four streaks of sword qi, which instantly pierced through the restrictions on the doors of the cells occupied by Shi Chuankong and the others before severing their shackles.

Han Li then tossed the Gold Rinsing Lightning Bead at Shi Chuankong as he instructed, "Use this lightning bead to remove the restrictions in your bodies."

Shi Chuankong immediately pressed the lightning bead to his own lower abdomen, and after the lightning bead vanished into his body, arcs of golden lightning began to emerge over his body as well.

Meanwhile, Fox 3 and the others emerged from their cells before gathering around Shi Chuankong.

"By the way, these are your things, Master. These nine Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords are your bonded treasures, and I took them at the time so that I could give them to you now," Weeping Soul said as she swept a sleeve through the air to summon the nine Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords and Han Li's storage tools.

An elated look flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this, and he quickly stowed all of his recovered belongings away, then turned to Weeping Soul as he sighed, "You really saved us, Weeping Soul. If you hadn't been around, this would've been the end of the road for all of us."

"There's no need to thank me, Master. It was all thanks to your tireless nurturing that I was able to get to this point, so I'm only repaying the favor," Weeping Soul said with a shake of her head.

"Alright, let's not talk about that then. By the way, what's happened to the Infernal Soul Bug in my mind? It seems to have been trapped in something," Han Li said.

"The ability to manifest Infernal Soul Bugs is one that's unique to the Infernal Tribe, and they're very difficult to deal with. Thankfully, I was able to find a type of special substance that can temporarily seal Infernal Soul Bugs away, and I mixed the substance into the Heavenly Yin Soul Nourishing Pills that were fed to you," Weeping Soul explained.

"I see. Can I ask how you ended up in the Gray Realm and why you seem to hold such a lofty status in the Infernal Tribe?" Han Li asked.

"That's a long story. When I was summoned all those years ago in the Spirit Realm, I really did ascend to the True Immortal Realm, and the one that had summoned me was a Great Encompassment cultivator of the Heavenly Court," Weeping Soul recounted with a complex expression.

Han Li's heart stirred slightly upon hearing this, but he didn't interject.

"However, he only summoned me to the True Immortal Realm as my ability to devour souls was helpful for his cultivation of a certain ability. I cultivated under him for over five thousand years, and my cultivation base improved quite a bit during this time, reaching the Golden Immortal Stage.

“He also make constant progress in his cultivation, and he began severing his three corpse souls, but due to a mishap, his severed corpse soul managed to escape, and it abducted me before fleeing to the Gray Realm," Weeping Soul continued.

"I see, but aren't Three Corpse Immortals supposed to go to the Reincarnation Region after arriving in the Gray Realm? How did you end up in the Infernal Region?" Han Li asked.

"That corpse soul didn't harbor any good intentions for me, so I found an opportunity to escape, and I fled to the Infernal Region and joined the Infernal Tribe," Weeping Soul explained.

She made the process sound very simple, but Han Li could guess that she had to have gone through countless struggles to get to this point.

However, given the urgency of the situation, he didn't ask for any further details.

"I am a yin-attribute being to begin with, and not only did I not experience any discomfort in the Gray Realm, the environment here is very suitable for my cultivation. On top of that, I mastered a very rare type of law power related to soul devouring, and I caught the eye of the Infernal Regional Master, becoming his disciple," Weeping Soul continued.

"It sounds like you were ultimately quite fortunate then. What is your current cultivation base?" Han Li asked.

"The Infernal Regional Master has looked after me quite well and bestowed upon me a lot of cultivation resources, so I was able to reach the High Zenith Stage just over a century ago. By the way, I haven't had a chance to ask you yet, how did you end up in the Gray Realm and Asura City, in particular?" Weeping Soul asked.

"We came here for the Baleful Cleansing Pond. You can probably sense that I'm currently at the pinnacle of the Golden Immortal Stage and that I'm struggling with my baleful decay, so I need to use the Baleful Cleansing Pond here," Han Li explained.

"I see. That's not going to be an easy feat to accomplish. The Baleful Cleansing Pond is a sacred area of the Infernal Tribe, and it's situated in the Soul Cleansing Area. With the Three Region Conference currently taking place, there's been a drastic spike in the number of outsiders in Asura City, so security will most likely be even tighter in the Soul Cleansing Area than usual," Weeping Soul said with slightly furrowed brows.

Han Li's expression darkened slightly upon hearing this, but before he had a chance to say anything else, they were approached by Shi Chuankong and the others.

Judging from their auras, it was clear that the baleful lightning restrictions in their bodies had already been removed.

"Thank you, Fellow Daoist Weeping Soul. We are eternally indebted to you for saving us in our time of need," Shi Chuankong said as the four of them extended grateful bows toward Weeping Soul.

"You're all friends of my master's, so there's no need to thank me. Here are your things."

Weeping Soul swept a hand through the air as she spoke, and all of the belongings that had been taken from Shi Chuankong and the others appeared amid a flash of light.

Shi Chuankong and the others were ecstatic, and they hurriedly recovered their belongings.

[1]. For more information on the Weeping Soul Beast, please refer to https://rmji.fandom.com/wiki/Weeping_Soul_Beast

[Back]

Chapter 739: Escape

"Master, I know your mind might be set, but I still want to remind you that right now, all of the monarch and most other Great Encompassment Stage Infernal beings are currently at the Fallen Lake Area, so the security on the outskirts of Asura City is likely to be as loose as it'll ever be. If you want to leave Asura City, I can act as your guide, but time is of the essence, so we must set off right away. If we miss this opportunity, it'll be very difficult to get away," Weeping Soul said.

Han Li took a glance at Shi Chuankong and the others to find that they were all in very bad condition, and his brows became tightly furrowed upon seeing this, but a determined look then quickly appeared on his face.

"We've already made it so far, if we turn back now, then we would've suffered for nothing. Besides, given the urgency of my baleful decay, I can't afford to turn back. If any of you don't want to continue, then you can leave now," Han Li sighed.

"My condition isn't any better than yours, so I can't afford to turn back, either," Baili Yan said with a wry smile.

"I don't have a habit of doing things halfway," Fox 3 chuckled, then immediately grimaced in pain.

"Our Vast Origin House never accepts losses, and backing out now would be accepting a huge loss. I'll make these people pay for what they've done," Shi Chuankong chimed in with a determined expression.

Mo Guang didn't say anything, and he still looked as nonchalant and aloof as ever.

"In that case, I won't try to dissuade you any further, Master," Weeping Soul said with a nod.

"It would be rather inconvenient for us to travel in such a large group, so before we reach the karmic fire crater, I'll get all of you to stay in my domain treasure," Han Li said, then conjured up a door of silver light, which led straight to the first floor of the bamboo pavilion.

Rich world's origin qi surged out of the door of light, striking Shi Chuankong and the others with a sense of comfort that they hadn't felt in a very long time.

"Is this the domain treasure from the Jade Kun Pagoda auction? I recall that it was purchased by an elder of the Hundred Creations Mountain at the time, was it not?" Fox 3 asked with a surprised expression.

"No, this is a different domain treasure that I obtained from elsewhere. Please get in the domain treasure for now. The world's origin qi in the bamboo building is very abundant, so just stay in there and rest and recuperate for now," Han Li said.

Mo Guang stepped into the bamboo pavilion first, and everyone else quickly followed suit.

All of the restrictions in the entire domain had been activated, while the bamboo pavilion had also been sealed, but these safety precautions were understandable in the eyes of Shi Chuankong and the others.

At the moment, all of them were stunned by the abundance of spiritual qi in the bamboo pavilion, and they quickly sat down with their legs crossed to rest and recuperate.

After closing the Flower Branch domain, Han Li suddenly grimaced in pain.

Even with his physical constitution, the torment that he had endured earlier had taken a heavy toll, and that wasn't even to mention the damage that he had sustained to his soul from the Infernal Soul Bug.

"Are you alright, Master?" Weeping Soul asked in a concerned voice.

Han Li made a reassuring gesture, then took a golden pill and closed his eyes to rest for a short while.

Moments later, he reopened his eyes, then forced a smile onto his own face as he said, "I'm fine. Let's go."

"This is going to be a very perilous journey, Master. Will you really be alright to go in your current condition?" Weeping Soul asked.

"The longer I stay in the Gray Realm, the more baleful qi infiltrates my body. I have a feeling that if I don't get to the Baleful Cleansing Pond soon, then I won't be able to suppress my baleful decay, and once that happens, I'll be doomed anyway," Han Li replied with a wry smile.

"The Soul Cleansing Area is a very special area that can only be accessed by Infernal beings. Even as the regional monarch's disciple, I can only enter the area with his accompaniment, so if you want to enter the Soul Cleansing Area, then you'll have to take the path that you originally planned out," Weeping Soul said.

"Won't we trigger the restrictions again if we try to go through that karmic fire passageway?" Han Li asked.

"You can leave that to me, Master. However, once you get to the Soul Cleansing Pond, I don't know what'll await you on the other side," Weeping Soul replied.

"At this point, I can only take things one step at a time," Han Li sighed.

Weeping Soul nodded in response, then said, "I'm sorry to have to do this, Master, please brace yourself."

She then raised a hand to release a bright red chain, which pierced through Han Li's shoulder.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly, but he didn't utter a sound.

With that, Weeping Soul escorted Han Li up the staircase.

Due to her special status in the Infernal Tribe, even the average Great Encompassment Stage Infernal being had to be wary of her, let alone normal Infernal Servants, so the journey was very smooth, and not even a single Infernal Servant dared to approach her to ask what she was doing.

Before long, the two of them had made it out of the infernal prison, and they quickly arrived at the karmic fire crater.

After walking over a long passageway, Han Li spotted a tall and imposing figure standing next to the entrance of the karmic fire passageway, and it was none other than Su Liu.

His arms were crossed in front of his chest, and he was staring blankly ahead in a completely expressionless manner. Even though Han Li had already seen them once before, the sewn scars on Su Liu's body still presented a harrowing sight to behold.

He certainly didn't feel any affection for this former immortal envoy, but given that they were both from the True Immortal Realm, he couldn't help but feel a sense of pity for Su Liu.

Right as they were about to pass Su Liu by, he suddenly uncrossed his arms, then stepped to the side to block Weeping Soul's path.

Weeping Soul's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and she raised a hand to summon a badge that was giving off wisps of black baleful qi, which hovered in the air momentarily in front of Su Liu before returning to her grasp.

Su Liu immediately returned to his original position upon seeing this.

Han Li and Weeping Soul stepped through the entrance to find that the bridge was completely deserted, and the cage that Immortal Lord Hot Flame and Chi Rong were held captive in was still hanging under the bridge.

As they approached the cage, Han Li stopped in his tracks.

"What's wrong, Master? Do you know them?" Weeping Soul asked as she took a glance down at the cage.

"Are you able to undo the restrictions on their bodies?" Han Li asked after a brief moment of contemplation.

"That's not a difficult task. With my infernal badge, it'll only take me a few seconds, but these two have already been scorched by karmic fire for too long, and they're already close to halfway to becoming gray immortals. My concern is that if I remove the restrictions in their bodies, they'll immediately go insane and embark on a rampage," Weeping Soul replied.

"Alright, in that case, release them from the cage for now, and we'll undo the restrictions another time," Han Li said.

Weeping Soul did as she was told, flying down to the cage before releasing a string of incantation seals into it.

A series of peculiar patterns instantly appeared on the cage before vanishing after a flash of dark red light, following which the cage was opened.

Immortal Lord Hot Flame was leaning against a corner of the cage, completely oblivious to what was happening. In contrast, Chi Rong turned his gaze to Han Li and Weeping Soul, and a hint of befuddlement and panic flashed through his eyes, but he didn't move or say anything.

"It looks like you're still lucid. I'm afraid I can't remove the restrictions on your body for now, but if you can stand up, then come out on your own," Han Li said.

Chi Rong remained still for a moment, then slowly rose to his feet and helped Immortal Lord Hot Flame up from the ground as well.

Han Li conjured up the same door of silver light, then continued, "Get in there."

Chi Rong didn't understand why Han Li was saving him, but he still did as he was told, stepping into the bamboo pavilion with Immortal Lord Hot Flame, following which Han Li closed the Flower Branch domain again.

As the two of them reached the end of the bridge, Weeping Soul said, "Please wait for a moment, Master."

After that, she descended into the karmic fire and vanished out of sight.

Around half a minute later, the black flames down below suddenly reared up slightly, and Weeping Soul reemerged as she declared, "It's done. The restrictions in the crater and in the karmic fire passageway have been temporarily sealed by me, so you can go now."

"Thank you," Han Li replied with a smile and a nod.

Right at this moment, a cold voice suddenly rang out.

"You Luo, do you understand what you're doing right now?"

Han Li hurriedly turned to discover a tall and thin middle-aged man stepping onto the bridge, holding a small furry white beast in his arms.

It was none other than Gui Mu, the Great Encompassment cultivator that Han Li had encountered earlier!

Behind him were dozens of puppets and Infernal Servants, with Su Liu standing among them.

"Elder Gui Mu, I'm here under instructions from my master to subject this man to karmic fire refinement, and I'll take him back to the infernal prison soon," Weeping Soul explained in a calm manner.

Gui Mu took a glance at the bright red chain in Weeping Soul's hand, the other end of which was pierced through Han Li's shoulder, and he said in a cold voice, "Prior to going into seclusion, Elder Yin Gua requested me to look after the Rashom Area in his absence, and he specifically told me not to report this matter to the regional monarch for now, so how could you possibly have received such instructions from him?"

Weeping Soul knew that she wouldn't be able to bluff her way through this, so she withdrew her chain from Han Li's body, and the hole left behind by the chain quickly healed.

"Do you insist on betraying the regional monarch?" Gui Mu asked with tightly furrowed brows.

A hesitant look flashed through Weeping Soul's eyes, following which she replied, "I'm willing to accept any punishment from my master for my transgressions, but if you can let us go today, I'll be sure to provide you with satisfactory compensation."

"It seems like I'll need to beat some sense into you!" Gui Mu harrumphed coldly as he set down the furry white beast down beside his feet.

The little beast rubbed itself against Gui Mu's leg for a moment, then turned to Han Li and bared its fangs in a menacing fashion before scurrying away.

Chapter 740: Agreement

"Go!" Weeping Soul suddenly yelled, then swept a hand through the air, conjuring up a dark red light barrier that transformed into a spirit domain, which enveloped both herself and Han Li.

Han Li instantly felt as if he had been isolated from the Gray Realm, and he no longer felt oppressed by the ever-present baleful qi as he sprang back and descended toward the karmic fire crater with Weeping Soul.

"The karmic fire will have far less of an impact on you in my spirit domain, but you still have to keep your guard up, Master," Weeping Soul cautioned.

As soon as her voice trailed off, a dark shadow suddenly appeared overhead, and it was none other than Su Liu, who was swooping down at them with his ax and mace brandished.

A string of metallic clangs rang out as the metal ball in the cavity in his chest revolved incessantly, and the runes on its surface were also flashing erratically, while a ball of black karmic fire was burning inside it.

A series of black patterns appeared over his body, and bursts of black flames erupted out of the chains on his body like blooming black lotus flowers.

Han Li summoned his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword with a flick of his wrist upon seeing this, and a layer of golden scales appeared over his arms as his muscles bulged.

He gripped onto the hilt of his sword with both hands, then stepped forward through the air before slashing his sword diagonally upward.

A resounding boom rang out as the scorching black flames surging out of Su Liu's ax clashed against the golden lightning from Han Li's sword, sending countless arcs of golden lightning and specks of karmic fire flying in all directions.

Neither Han Li nor Su Liu was able to get the better of the other, and a brief impasse ensued.

However, another deafening boom then instantly rang out as Su Liu swung his mace down upon Han Li as well, and this blow was even more powerful than the one delivered with the ax.

Even though Han Li was fighting with all his might to withstand the barrage, he was still sent flying like a cannonball, plummeting straight into the karmic fire crater, followed closely by Weeping Soul.

"You're not getting away!" Gui Mu roared.

However, Han Li and Weeping Soul were rapidly gliding along the bottom of the fiery crater, using their momentum to fly toward the karmic fire passageway on the other side.

Even though Han Li had been plunged back into the karmic fire, the experience didn't feel as grueling as he was insulated within Weeping Soul's spirit domain.

That was quite reassuring to him, and he began to channel his Spirit Refinement Technique. The Infernal Soul Bug had caused significant damage to his spiritual sense, and even though it had been temporarily suppressed, he still didn't dare to get complacent.

In the blink of an eye, Gui Mu appeared above the karmic fire crater, then reached down with one hand, and tendrils of black light instantly began to spread rapidly over his hand like a series of vines.

Countless branches split off from these vines to form a dense and uniform black net, which extended into the fiery crater before swooping down upon Han Li's duo.

At the same time, the Infernal Servants and puppets had also arrived above the fiery crater, and all of them lashed out in unison with their weapons.

As soon as the black net entered the karmic fire crater, its speed instantly increased by severalfold, and it began to close itself around Han Li and Weeping Soul at an astonishing speed.

Right at this moment, Han Li flipped a hand over to produce a green gourd, then thrust the palm of his other hand into the underside of the gourd.

A layer of green light instantly surfaced over the gourd, as did countless tiny runes, and it released a burst of formidable law power fluctuations that forced back all of the karmic fire within a radius of several dozen feet.

A sharp clang rang out as a streak of radiant golden swordlight erupted out of the mouth of the gourd, slicing a wide gash through the karmic fire before crashing into the giant black net.

The black net shuddered violently, and it swelled drastically in the face of the vast expanse of golden lightning and violent sword qi, looking as if it were about to be torn apart at any moment.

The attacks unleashed by the Infernal Servants and puppets were also eradicated by the oncoming blast of force.

A cold sneer appeared on Gui Mu's face upon seeing thi, and he instantly appeared directly in front of Han Li's duo, following which his hand disintegrated into a cloud of gray mist that enveloped the entirety of the black net.

At this point, the net was on the verge of collapse, but it seemed to have suddenly received an injection of power, and it began to slowly close in around Han Li and Weeping Soul like a cage.

At the same time, a thin and long black branch wrapped itself around the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword, then forcibly dragged it toward Gui Mu.

"Don't let him take your sword, Master! Elder Gui Mu has mastered the laws of ghost vines, and the venom on his vines can tarnish immortal treasures and turn them into Gray Realm treasures!" Weeping Soul hurriedly warned, following which a pair of bright red chains re-emerged from his hands before hurtling toward the oncoming Su Liu.

Drops of black liquid were seeping out of the black net, giving off a decaying odor much like that of the rotten mud dug out of a swamp.

The black liquid dripped down onto Han Li's Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword, and the sword immediately began to tremble and buzz, while arcs of golden lightning sprang out of its surface.

To Han Li's shock and dismay, he could see that a series of stark white marks had appeared on the blade of the sword, and he hurriedly attempted to summon it back to himself, only to discover that his connection with his flying sword had somehow been impeded.

"This is quite a fine sword, and it seems to be part of a set. How about you show me the full set?" Gui Mu remarked as he took a glance at the other Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword in Han Li's hand.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he raised the green gourd once again before thrusting a palm into its underside, and a streak of green light flew out of its mouth, wrapping itself around the sword that had been ensnared by the ghost vines before attempting to pull it back.

"Is that a Profound Heavenly Gourd? You sure have a lot of fine treasures up your sleeve. Seeing as you're being so kind as to offer them all up to me, I'll gladly accept," Gui Mu chuckled as several ghost vines shot out of the black net before extending toward the Profound Heavenly Gourd and the other Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword.

Right at this moment, a strange sound suddenly rang out from the mouth of the gourd, following which a streak of dark green light shot out in a flash, severing the oncoming ghostly vines upon contact.

The ghost vines wrapped around the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword were also severed, allowing Han Li to recover the sword before storing it back into the gourd.

"Destruction law powers! No wonder Yin Gua specified to me so many times to spare your life, you're absolutely full of surprises!" Gui Mu exclaimed with a stunned expression.

Right at this moment, Weeping Soul clashed against Su Liu before flying back to Han Li's side, and her brows were tightly furrowed as she said, "Master, these puppets have no souls, so my powers are very limited in their effectiveness against them. On top of that, Gui Mu is a Great Encompassment cultivator, so at the very most, I'll only be able to hold him off for you for a while, but you won't be able to go to the Soul Cleansing Area."

A hesitant look appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this. In the face of a Great Encompassment cultivator, he had no chances of winning, even with his time law powers.

Right at this moment, Mo Guang's voice suddenly rang out in his mind.

"Let me come out, Fellow Daoist Han!"

"What are you planning to do, Fellow Daoist Mo Guang?" Han Li asked with a puzzled expression.

"This body doesn't belong to me, so my soul and body aren't very cohesive with each other, and as a result, I was somewhat suppressed by Weeping Soul's abilities, which led to my defeat, but I won't be so inept against Gui Mu. As long as you're willing to fulfill a condition of mine, I'm willing to put my life on the line and fight for you," Mo Guang replied.

"You want me to dissolve our Heavenly Devil Contract, right?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"That's right. I have no chance of victory against Gui Mu, but I should be able to hold him off for fifteen minutes. If I die within that time, then so be it, but if I survive, then all ties between us will be severed. What do you say?" Mo Guang proposed.

Han Li considered the proposal for a moment, then replied, "Alright, you have yourself a deal."

He swept a sleeve through the air as he spoke, and Mo Guang flew out amid a flash of silver light.

The usual nonchalant look in his eyes had been replaced with a serious and focused expression, one that felt very alien to Han Li.

"Get out of here, I'll take him on," Mo Guang said to Han Li and Weeping Soul as he stared intently at Gui Mu.

"Such insolence from a mere High Zenith cultivator! Looks like I'll just have to crush you first," Gui Mu chuckled coldly as he flew directly toward Mo Guang, who took a deep breath before suddenly letting loose a resounding roar.

Radiant silver light appeared within his eyes, and a series of strange patterns began to surface over his glabella and his face. At the same time, baleful qi billowed out from under his robes, and his aura swelled all the way to the late-High Zenith Stage.

When did he get to the late-High Zenith Stage? Han Li thought to himself with a stunned expression.

Mo Guang swept a sleeve through the air, and the karmic fire down below rose up as if it had been summoned, transforming into a giant fiery tornado that swept directly toward Gui Mu, while Mo Guang made a chopping motion to the side with his other hand.

A burst of black light erupted out of his fingertips before gliding through the air, slicing an opening into the black net up ahead, and Han Li hesitated momentarily, then cupped his fist in a parting salute toward Mo Guang before rushing toward the karmic fire passageway with Weeping Soul.

Chapter 741: Loss of Contact

Right as Han Li and Weeping Soul were about to fly into the passageway, Su Liu descended upon them once again, and he swung his ax through the air to unleash a dense wall of ax projections.

Han Li was just about to raise his sword in retaliation when Su Liu was abruptly rooted to the spot, frozen in his current posture, and all of the ax projections also drew to a halt.

Upon closer inspection, Han Li noticed that there were wisps of black mist flowing out of Su Liu's mouth and nostrils, and a cloud of black mist had also appeared in his chest cavity, rendering the metal ball inside unable to rotate.

"Let's go, Master!" Weeping Soul yelled as she led Han Li into the karmic fire passageway.

In the next instant, a vast expanse of black ghost vines swept past Mo Guang before descending upon the entrance of the passageway.

The entire mountain face trembled violently as countless loose rocks came tumbling down, completely burying the entrance of the karmic fire passageway.

Han Li and Weeping Soul could sense the violent tremors behind them, but they had no time to look back as they flew toward the other end of the passageway as quickly as they could.

The passageway abruptly tapered as they advanced, concentrating the surrounding karmic fire, and a burst of baleful qi began to seep through Weeping Soul's spirit domain, making Han Li feel as if there were needles being driven into his mind.

He gritted his teeth tight as he attempted to suppress the unrest in his consciousness, but an irrepressible sense of violent anger was welling up in his heart, making him feel extremely frustrated.

Weeping Soul could sense his discomfort, and the dark red light emanating from her body became even brighter as she sped through the passageway.

However, the further they went, the more viscous the surrounding karmic fire became, and the baleful qi that they contained also became more abundant, thereby further exacerbating Han Li's pain.

"The closer we get to the Soul Cleansing Area, the purer and more invasive the karmic fire will become. I have to focus on controlling my spirit domain, so you'll have to look after yourself, Master," Weeping Soul cautioned.

"I'll be fine," Han Li replied in a slightly hoarse voice.

At this point, he was already channeling his Spirit Refinement Technique with all his might, but his mind was still becoming foggier by the second, and his heart was beating like a drum. At the same time, his blood was pumping through his veins, and the baleful qi lurking within his immortal acupoints was beginning to grow more and more restless.

Countless indistinct crimson figures had appeared in his consciousness, and they were rushing around in a frenzied state as if they were on a battlefield. He could even smell the sickly sweet odor of blood, and if someone of lesser mental fortitude were in his place, they would've most likely already given in to insanity.

At this rate, Han Li didn't feel as if he would be able to last until they reached the Baleful Cleansing Pond.

"We're almost there, Master, just a bit longer now," Weeping Soul urged with a concerned look in her eyes.

Right at this moment, Han Li's vision gradually began to blur, and his pupils took on a gray color, while the unrest in the baleful qi in his immortal acupoints also began to escalate out of control.

If his soul hadn't sustained so much damage from the Infernal Soul Bug earlier, then perhaps he would've been able to persevere thanks to his immense spiritual sense and Spirit Refinement Technique, but he was truly about to be overwhelmed now, and once his consciousness faded, he would no longer be able to channel his Spirit Refinement Technique.

If his baleful decay were to return while he was in such a vulnerable state, then he would truly be doomed.

Right at this moment, a glimmer of dark red light suddenly flashed in front of Han Li's glabella, and he discovered that it was Weeping Soul pressing a longan-sized red bead against his forehead.

The bead had a smooth surface that was giving off a warm glow, and there was a tiny beast projection inside, one that resembled the Weeping Soul Beast's true form.

Bursts of gentle soul power seeped into Han Li's mind alongside the warm light emanating from the bead, quelling the unrest in his spiritual sense while also clearing away all of the warring crimson figures.

As Han Li's consciousness returned to a stable state, he was able to ward off the infiltration of the baleful qi using his Spirit Refinement Technique.

As his vision returned to normal, he noticed that Weeping Soul was looking a little pale, and a concerned look immediately appeared on his face as he asked, "Are you alright?"

"I'm fine. This bead contains my soul essence, but I'll be fine once it returns to my body," Weeping Soul replied with a shake of her head.

Han Li was silent for a moment, then began focusing his attention on fortifying his own spiritual sense.

The karmic fire passageway wasn't very long, only less than ten thousand feet in length, and the hole on the other side was several hundred feet tall, resembling a cavernous mouth.

There were no restrictions inside, and Han Li and Weeping Soul flew out of the hole, then arrived at an enormous underground karmic fire lake.

The two of them rose up into the air to hover above the lake as they inspected their surroundings, and they discovered that the roof up above was pitch black and riddled with glittering black stalactites, while many giant stone pillars were standing around the karmic fire lake, stretching all the way up to the roof above.

Even further away on the edge of the lake was a series of embankments, branching out from which were close to a hundred paths that led to the surrounding mountain faces.

There was a series of smooth and uniform caves that had been drilled into the mountain faces, making the place resemble a giant underground palace, and to Han Li's surprise, there were no Infernal Tribe forces waiting to ambush them here.

"It looks like Gui Mu didn't alert the Soul Cleansing Area to our arrival," Han Li remarked.

"The karmic fire passageway has already collapsed, so even without an alert from Gui Mu, Elder Yin Xu won't be far away," Weeping Soul said with tightly furrowed brows.

Right at this moment, the sound of faint conversation suddenly rang out from within one of the caves on a nearby mountain face, and Han Li and Weeping Soul immediately drifted down onto a nearby embankment.

From there, they hid themselves in another cave, then concealed their own aura as they monitored what was happening outside.

A pair of children from the Infernal Tribe drifted out of the hole, then arrived at the bank of the karmic fire lake.

Both of them were wearing identical black robes, and they were very similar in appearance as well. It seemed that they were a pair of twins.

"Brother Lian, the elder may have told us that there's something important happening in the city today, so we can take a day off from cultivation if we please, but we're already ten years old now, and we'll be coming of age in two years. If we don't work hard in our cultivation, we won't be able to pass the final trial," one of the children said.

"My eardrums are going to grow calluses if I hear you say that one more time, Brother Yin! Don't worry so much, I won't let Yin Chang surpass me," the other child replied in a nonchalant manner.

Compared with adult Infernal beings, these two children had far more expressive faces, so they weren't so cold and forbidding to look at.

As the two of them were speaking, they sat down with their legs crossed by the karmic fire lake, then each made a strange hand seal, upon which bright black light began emanating out of their bodies, and wisps of pure baleful qi flowed out of the lake toward them.

As they breathed, two wisps of black qi were constantly worming their way in and out of their nostrils, presenting quite a peculiar sight to behold.

"Those two are only ten years old, yet they're already close to the Core Formation Stage and can cultivate safely in such close proximity to karmic fire... Infernal beings truly are terrifying," Han Li remarked in a low voice.

"Infernal beings have far superior karmic fire tolerance to beings from other tribes, and all of them possess tremendous cultivation aptitude. When it comes to aptitude, these two children are actually only below average," Weeping Soul said.

Han Li ducked back into the cave before walking some distance into it with Weeping Soul, then swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up a door of silver light.

At this moment, Shi Chuankong and the others were all meditating on the first floor of the bamboo pavilion, and they all rose to their feet at the sight of Han Li's arrival, with the exception of Immortal Lord Hot Flame, who had been bound by a chain of silver light.

His body was trembling slightly, yet he was unable to make any sound as his lips had been sealed by a purple talisman.

Chi Rong was leaning against the wall beside him with a concerned expression, and he turned to look at Han Li with a complex look in his eyes.

"What happened to Fellow Daoist Hot Flame?" Han Li asked.

"He's been driven insane by baleful qi contamination, and he suddenly began to go on a rampage, so we had to restrain him by force," Baili Yan explained.

"At this rate, it won't be long before his dao foundation is completely destroyed, and he's reduced to a gray immortal," Fox 3 mused with slightly furrowed brows, and Han Li fell silent upon hearing this.

As soon as everyone emerged from the Flower Branch domain, they immediately adopted measures to ward off the karmic fire and baleful qi while also hurriedly concealing themselves.

"Right now, we should already be in the Soul Cleansing Area, which is the most special one out of all of Asura City's major areas. Even Fellow Daoist Weeping Soul hasn't been here many times, and the area is also completely blank on our map. Does anyone have any suggestions on how we can find the Baleful Cleansing Pond?" Han Li asked.

"Can't we just grab those two children and perform a soul search on them?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"Last time, we alerted Yin Gua to our presence just by killing a puppet, who knows if there are any special restrictions placed on these children? We can't afford to take the risk," Baili Yan said with a shake of his head.

Han Li was just about to say something when his expression suddenly changed drastically, and he seemed to have been stunned into silence.

"Are you alright, Master?" Weeping Soul hurriedly asked with a concerned expression, thinking that he was suffering a recurrence of his baleful decay, and everyone else was also looking rather concerned.

"By the way, where's Fellow Daoist Mo Guang?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"Just now, my spiritual connection with Mo Guang was completely severed. I tried to communicate with him, but I'm unable to even sense him anymore," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

A stunned look appeared on Shi Chuankong's face upon hearing this.

"Could it be that Fellow Daoist Mo Guang has already met his demise?" Fox 3 asked with an incredulous expression.

"He said that he was going to hold off Gui Mu for fifteen minutes for me. Regardless of whether he lived or died, he fulfilled his promise," Han Li replied in an ambiguous manner, and everyone fell silent upon hearing this.

Chapter 742: Uniting Against the Enemy

"Gui Mu already knows that we've escaped, and now that I've lost contact with Fellow Daoist Mo Guang, I'm sure Gui Mu will catch up to us soon. We have to get to the Baleful Cleansing Pond as soon as possible," Han Li said.

"In that case, we don't have to worry about being exposed, so the best way to proceed would be to search the souls of those two Infernal children. I'll go right now," Shi Chuankong said, then abruptly vanished from the spot.

Han Li and the others hurriedly made their way to the entrance of the cave before turning their attention to the bank of the karmic fire lake.

The two children were still cultivating with their eyes closed, completely oblivious to the looming threat behind them.

In the next instant, Shi Chuankong appeared behind them without any warning, then reached out for the backs of their necks.

Han Li was looking on from afar when Weeping Soul suddenly sprang out of the cave, instantly arriving behind Shi Chuankong before raising a hand, and a burst of bright red light emerged over the palm of her hand as she chopped down toward the back of his neck.

Everyone was very alarmed to see this, but before they had a chance to do anything, Shi Chuankong was sent flying forward before tumbling heavily onto the ground, then crashed into a mountain face in the distance.

Only then did Han Li and the others notice that there was a gray shadow clinging to his back, and that had been the target of Weeping Soul's attack.

Shi Chuankong reacted very quickly, and a burst of tremendous spatial force surged out of his body before erupting in all directions, and the gray shadow that was clinging to his back was sent flying like a kite, but quickly drifted back down onto his back to cling to him again.

A grim look appeared on Weeping Soul's face as she swept a sleeve through the air to release a bright red chain, which sprang at Shi Chuankong's back like an agile spirit snake.

The gray shadow seemed to be quite wary of the red chain, and it voluntarily detached itself from Shi Chuankong before drifting away to the side.

The two Infernal children were rather taken aback by this turn of events, but they remained calm and collected as they rushed to hide behind the gray shadow.

The gray shadow gradually transformed into an Infernal being with a hook nose and a deathly pale complexion, and he screeched in a high-pitched voice, "You Luo! What is the meaning of this?"

"I owe no explanation to you, Yin Xiao," Weeping Soul replied in a cold voice.

At the same time, she was also communicating to Han Li and the others through voice transmission.

"This man has mastered the laws of shadow illusion, and he's at the pinnacle of the High Zenith Stage. His law powers grant him exceptional concealment abilities, so make sure to be on your guard."

"We can't afford to be delayed here. Everyone, attack at once and aim to end this battle as quickly as possible," Han Li said with slightly furrowed brows.

A cold look appeared on Weeping Soul's face as she released around dozen bright red chains out of her sleeves, all of which intertwined in mid-air as they converged toward Yin Xiao.

A cold sneer appeared on Yin Xiao's face, and instead of retreating, he advanced directly toward the chains.

In the instant that all of the chains pierced into his body, he began to ripple like the surface of a disturbed lake, and the chains passed through him without any impediment before piercing into the ground amid a chorus of loud clangs.

After passing through the chains, Yin Xiao sped forward at an astonishing speed while slamming a hand down toward Weeping Soul's head, and a tiny vortex of gray light that was giving off tremendous suction force emerged on the palm of his hand.

A hint of panic flashed through Weeping Soul's eyes upon seeing this, and she attempted to withdraw her chains, only to discover that they refused to budge, as if they had been nailed firmly to the ground.

Right as the gray palm was about to smash her head open, a sly grin suddenly flashed across her face, and she slid a finger over her own glabella, upon which a dark red gash emerged.

The skin and flesh of the gash then parted down either side to reveal a dark red demonic eye.

Yin Xiao's expression changed drastically at the sight of this demonic eye, and he immediately began to spring back in retreat, only for a burst of dark red light to surge out of Weeping Soul's demonic eye before shining down upon his face.

In that instant, it was as if his soul had been struck by a bolt of lightning, and he began to sway unsteadily from side to side, seemingly unable to maintain his balance.

At the same time, Han Li abruptly appeared behind him, and arcs of golden lightning flashed violently over his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword as it was pierced directly at the back of Yin Xiao's head.

However, right at this moment, Yin Xiao suddenly seemed to have regained control over his own body, and he ducked to the side, just barely evading the blade of Han Li's sword, following which a second identical face appeared on the back of his head.

"I knew there were more than two of you," he chuckled, and his body abruptly split up into two, with one half darting directly at Han Li, holding a black dagger that was aimed straight at Han Li's throat.

Han Li seemed to have already anticipated this, and his Mantra Treasured Axis flew out of his body amid a flash of golden light, then began to revolve rapidly while releasing a series of golden ripples.

As soon as Yin Xiao's arm reached into the golden ripples, it was instantly slowed down significantly, and Han Li didn't even need to take evasive measures as he grabbed onto Yin Xiao's throat with one hand, then drove his sword straight into Yin Xiao's head with the other.

However, in the instant that the tip of his sword pierced into Yin Xiao's head, Han Li was struck by the sense that something was amiss, and he hurriedly retracted his hand while simultaneously ducking down.

However, immediately thereafter, he felt a sharp pain spear through his lower abdomen, and he discovered that another Yin Xiao had emerged from this Yin Xiao's lower abdomen, and it was holding a black dagger that had pierced into Han Li's body just above his dantian.

A sinister grin appeared on Yin Xiao's face as he abruptly dragged his dagger upward, and a blade formed by a burst of powerful baleful qi erupted forth to slice Han Li into two, sending his internal organs and blood gushing down onto the ground.

Yin Xiao withdrew his dagger before running his tongue over its blade with a gleeful look on his face, but in the next instant, Han Li's voice suddenly rang out nearby.

"Are you ready, Fellow Daoist Shi?"

"I am," Shi Chuankong replied.

Han Li instantly scattered his Mantra Domain upon hearing this, and Yin Xiao felt his vision blur momentarily, following which he discovered that Han Li was nowhere to be seen, while the two Infernal children were also in the clutches of Fox 3, having already fallen unconscious.

An alarmed look appeared on Yin Xiao's face upon seeing this, and he was just about to throw himself at Fox 3 when he suddenly discovered that the space around his body was warping slightly, as if it were being compressed by some kind of spatial force, rendering him unable to move or disintegrate his own body into an insubstantial form.

Not far away behind him, Shi Chuankong was maintaining a strange hand seal while pressing down tightly onto the strings of a silver lute, and his face had turned very pale, while blood was flowing from his fingertips, but he continued to hold on with all his might.

"Hurry, Fellow Daoist Li! I can't keep this up for long," Shi Chuankong yelled.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a streak of sword light shot forth, and it pierced through Yin Xiao's chest in the exact same instant that he was freed from Shi Chuankong's spatial restriction.

Simultaneously, a black dragon claw swooped down from above before closing itself around Yin Xiao's head, preparing to crush both his head and soul at once.

"Hold on a second!" Han Li hurriedly called out, and at the same time, he summoned a series of Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, all of which were flashing with Divine Devilbane Lightning and plunged into various important acupoints on Yin Xiao's body.

Ravaged by the Divine Devilbane Lightning, Yin Xiao howled in agony, while Shi Chuankong heaved a long sigh of relief.

Earlier, Weeping Soul had jolted Yin Xiao's soul with her powers, and Han Li had pounced on the opportunity to unleash his Mantra Domain, buying Shi Chuankong enough time to use his silver lute, and that was how they had managed to subdue Yin Xiao so quickly.

However, Shi Chuankong was still yet to recover from his injuries, so he had suffered a great deal of backlash from forcibly unleashing the power of his silver lute.

Even after Yin Xiao was subdued, Baili Yan was still on high alert, keeping his claws firmly locked around Yin Xiao's head.

Han Li was just about to approach Yin Xiao when Weeping Soul said, "Master, you already overexerted yourself back in the karmic fire passageway, so take a rest for now and leave the soul searching to me."

"Alright," Han Li replied with a nod, and Weeping Soul stepped forward before tapping a finger against her own glabella, upon which the dark red demonic eye re-emerged.

A burst of dark red light erupted out of the demonic eye before sweeping across Yin Xiao and the two Infernal children, and Han Li was quite surprised to see this.

Even with his immense spiritual sense, he definitely wouldn't be able to search the souls of three people at once.

All of a sudden, the two Infernal children opened their eyes, then got up into seated postures in an unsteady fashion, and their eyes were completely dim and devoid of life, making them resemble a pair of puppets.

As for Yin Xiao, he reflexively resisted momentarily, following which the light in his eyes also began to fade.

Moments later, the red light emanating from Weeping Soul's demonic eye faded, and the two children immediately fell unconscious again.

"Did you find out anything?" Han Li asked.

"The Baleful Cleansing Pond is a sacred area of the Infernal Tribe, and these two children are yet to undergo their baptism by karmic fire, so they're not true Infernal beings yet. Hence, they haven't actually ever been to the Baleful Cleansing Pond. As for Yin Xiao, his spiritual sense is quite powerful, and even in his current state, he's still able to resist my soul search technique, but I've managed to get a rough idea of the Soul Cleansing Area's layout," Weeping Soul replied.

"That should be enough," Han Li said with a nod.

"In that case, we no longer have any use for him, right?" Baili Yan asked, and before anyone had a chance to reply, he closed his dragon claws in one forceful motion, crushing Yin Xiao's head.

"No!" Weeping Soul exclaimed, but it was already too late.

Baili Yan turned to her with a perplexed expression, as did Han Li, and he realized that even though Weeping Soul was willing to help him, that didn't mean that she was willing to truly betray the Infernal Regional Monarch.

After all, she had benefited immensely from his care, and she didn't want to repay his kindness with ingratitude.

Chapter 743: Hot Pursuit

"Fellow Daoist Baili, please hold off from killing Infernal beings unless it's absolutely necessary," Han Li sighed.

"I understand. My apologies, Fellow Daoist Weeping Soul," Baili Yan said as he cupped his fist in an apologetic salute toward Weeping Soul, in response to which she merely gave a silent nod.

"What should we do with these two?" Fox 3 asked as he hoisted the two unconscious Infernal children up from the ground.

Weeping Soul was just about to respond when Han Li replied, "I'll keep them in my domain treasure for now. The fact that a peak-High Zenith Stage elder was assigned to protect them indicates that they're no ordinary children, so perhaps we can use them as leverage at some point."

He swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up a door of silver light as he spoke, and Fox 3 tossed the two children into the bamboo building.

However, before Han Li had a chance to close the Flower Branch domain, his expression abruptly changed slightly as he declared in an urgent voice, "Gui Mu's coming!"

He immediately closed the door of silver light as he spoke, and Weeping Soul led everyone down deeper into the cave that they had previously been hiding in.

As they advanced through the cave, the terrain gradually began to elevate, and at the end of the path was a crossroads.

Weeping Soul took a moment to ascertain the right way to go, then led everyone down the left crossroad.

No more than a few seconds after their departure, a cloud of dense baleful qi surged out of another cave on the bank of the karmic fire lake, and it drew to a halt on the embankment before converging to form none other than Gui Mu.

No non-Infernal beings were permitted to enter the Soul Cleansing Area without permission, so he had to leave the puppets and Infernal Servants behind before entering the Soul Cleansing Area, accompanied only by the furry white beast.

As soon as he reached the embankment, he spotted the headless Yin Xiao, and a look of stunned fury instantly appeared on his face.

A tremendous aura erupted out of his body in all directions, causing the karmic fire lake to rumble violently, and thick pillars of fire rose up all the way to the roof above.

"How dare they! They've killed Yin Xiao and abducted our ceremonial children! I'm going to crush them and use their bodies to fertilize my ghost vines! Find them!" Gui Mu spat through gritted teeth as he threw the furry white beast down from his shoulder.

In his fit of rage, he had been quite forceful, and the furry white beast grimaced in pain as it fell to the ground, but its eyes were full of fear, and it didn't even dare to utter a single sound as it began meekly sniffing along the ground.

All of a sudden, its eyes lit up as a burst of white ripples surged out of them before rapidly spreading in all directions, and shortly thereafter, it began yelling in excitement as it pointed its two front paws directly at the cave that Han Li's group had fled into.

"Well done!" Gui Mu praised with a pleased smile, following which a sympathetic look appeared on his face as he gently smoothed down the little beast's fur, seemingly feeling rather guilty about handling it in such a rough manner.

After that, he sprang forward and transformed into a cloud of black mist that poured into the passageway.

......

Han Li and the others were racing onward under Weeping Soul's guidance, twisting and turning left and right.

The underground tunnels in the Soul Cleansing Area were extremely complex, with countless branching paths, and the terrain also undulated in a completely chaotic and haphazard fashion.

After rounding a corner and rushing downhill for several thousand feet, a mountain face suddenly appeared in front of the group.

"What's going on? Why have we hit a dead-end?" Shi Chuankong hurriedly asked with an anxious expression.

"Don't be fooled, it's just a false wall," Weeping Soul explained, then crashed straight into the mountain face up ahead without pause.

As soon as she crashed into the mountain face, it immediately slid back several feet to reveal an opening that was around three feet wide, and everyone hurriedly rushed into it.

Behind the mountain face was a spacious underground hall, and they had only just set foot into it when they heard a loud yell.

"There they are, Elder Yin Fu!"

Immediately thereafter, Han Li and the others were confronted by a group of Infernal Tribe cultivators, led by a peak-High Zenith Stage elder.

"We can't afford to get caught up here with Gui Mu hot on our heels!" Han Li yelled, then darted directly toward an opening on the other side of the hall, followed closely by everyone else.

The Infernal Tribe cultivators immediately set off in pursuit, but right at this moment, a sly grin appeared on Baili Yan's face as he casually tossed something behind him.

It was a collection of black balls, and as soon as they landed on the ground, they immediately began to glow with black light.

Immediately thereafter, a string of deafening explosions rang out as enormous bursts of black flames erupted out of the black balls, forming a violent sea of fire that proliferated outward in all directions.

At this point, Han Li and the others were already very far away, but they were still struck by the powerful shockwaves from the explosion, striking them with a dull and nauseating sensation in their chests.

The pursuing Infernal beings naturally fared even worse. They still hadn't even had a chance to use the Karmic Fire Baleful Lightning, yet it was now being used on them in a rather ironic twist.

Bursts of rumbling reverberated incessantly within the underground hall, and the shockwaves from the explosion lingered for an extended period of time.

Han Li and the others had only just flown out of the hall when another figure flew in from a passageway to the left.

It was a thin black-robed man who appeared to be quite advanced in age, looking much like an elderly scribe, and it was incredible to think that someone so unremarkable in appearance could be a mid-Great Encompassment cultivator, but the reality was that he was none other than Yin Xu, the Great Encompassment cultivator stationed in the Soul Cleansing Area.

At this moment, he was also alone as he hovered in mid-air, and his eyes were seething with fury as he looked down at the Infernal beings that had just been ravaged by the Karmic Fire Baleful Lightning explosion

Right at this moment, Gui Mu flew out of the tunnel that Han Li and the others had just emerged from, and he hurriedly asked, "Did you manage to intercept them, Elder Yin Xu?"

"No, I was too late," Yin Xu harrumphed coldly with a dark expression.

Gui Mu knew that he was to blame for allowing Han Li and the others to escape from the Hundred Treasure Area, so he felt in no position to reprimand Yin Xu.

"I didn't get a chance to tell you this earlier, but these people killed Yin Xiao by the karmic fire lake and also abducted two ceremonial children," Gui Mu said.

"What? Just how incompetent can you and Yin Gua be? How did you let them get away with the ceremonial children?" Yin Xu exclaimed as his expression darkened even further.

"Elder Yin Gua had originally already captured them, and it was only because of You Luo's sudden betrayal that they were able to escape from the infernal prison," Gui Mu explained.

"You Luo betrayed us? How is all of this happening at once? Where is Yin Gua right now?" Yin Xu asked.

"Elder Yin Gua is currently resting in seclusion to recover from the strain of manifesting some Infernal Soul Bugs, but I've already sent someone to notify him of the situation, so I'm sure he'll be here soon as well," Gui Mu replied.

"He's still in the mood to be resting in seclusion? Right now, we're at a vital stage in the Three Region Conference. If the regional monarch finds out about the ceremonial children, all of us will be in huge trouble!" Yin Xu grumbled.

"We absolutely cannot report this matter to the regional monarch, Elder Yin Xu! You and Elder Yin Gua will perhaps be able to get away with just some physical punishment, but I'll have my organs gouged out and be refined into a puppet!" Gui Mu hurriedly pleaded in a fearful voice.

"Let's catch them before anyone finds out then," Yin Xu said with tightly furrowed brows.

"Thank you, Elder Yin Xu," Gui Mu replied in a grateful voice, and the two of them sped away as two streaks of light, instantly vanishing from the spot.

Meanwhile, Weeping Soul was leading everyone toward a wide tunnel that sloped downward, when Han Li abruptly took a glance behind them with an alarmed expression.

Everything behind them had been plunged into complete darkness, and the parts of the tunnel that they had just passed through had completely vanished.

He immediately activated his Infernal Devilish Eyes, upon which he discovered that there was an enormous black shadow that was rolling toward them, filling up the entire tunnel.

Everything that was encompassed within the shadow was plunged into complete darkness, and an Weeping Soul exclaimed in an alarmed voice, "This is bad! Elder Yin Xu is coming after us as well!"

As if in response to her voice, the black shadow instantly sped up by twofold, and it wouldn't be long before it caught up to them.

Han Li could sense the terrifying aura emanating out of the black shadow, and he knew that this definitely wasn't something that they could deal with.

He gritted his teeth as he channeled his Reversal True Axis ability to propel himself forward at an extraordinary speed.

At the same time, two bursts of azure light erupted out of his sleeves, sweeping up everyone and pulling them along with him.

Moments later, Han Li's group flew into another tunnel, and even before landing on the ground, Han Li took a glance at his surroundings to discover that he had arrived in an enormous underground cave.

The cave was over a hundred thousand feet wide, and the terrain was very flat. There was a large white plaza nearby, and beyond the plaza was a cluster of strange-looking palaces with dome ceilings.

Outside the cluster of palaces was a red light barrier with black runes flashing over it, forming a sealing array.

"What is this place, and why has it been sealed away?" Han Li asked.

"It's a place that I saw in Yin Xiao's memories. All I managed to find out is that this is an extremely important place that's taken very seriously even by the regional monarch. Entry is normally strictly prohibited, and battles are forbidden in the nearby vicinity," Weeping Soul replied.

Chapter 744: Storming Into a Restricted Area

All of a sudden, an alarmed look appeared on Han Li's face as he exclaimed, "Yin Xu and Gui Mu are catching up to us again!"

"We can't keep running away like this," Baili Yan spat through gritted teeth. "At some point, we'll just have to turn around and fight them."

"In my current state, I can only use my spatial powers one more time to teleport us some distance away from those two, but it won't buy us much time at all," Shi Chuankong sighed.

"Looks like we'll have to make a final stand here, but I'm not optimistic about our chances," Fox 3 said in a grim manner.

"Don't be so quick to resort to extremes. Yin Chengquan forbade battles in the nearby vicinity, so this must be an important place that is not to be damaged. In that case, why don't we go and hide inside the palace for now?" Han Li suggested.

"That could work!" Weeping Soul replied as her eyes lit up.

No one else raised any objections, so the group quickly made its way to the palace.

Through the light barrier, they could see that the gates of the palace were tightly shut, and there were two massive reliefs engraved onto them.

The relief on the left was laden with white bones of different sizes and skulls of various descriptions, and they piled up all the way from the bottom of the gate to above its midsection, while a large chair of bones was engraved onto the top part of the gate. Seated in the chair was a male Infernal being holding a giant scythe with his arms spread open and an indulgent look on his face.

The gate on the right was riddled with all types of fearsome-looking beasts that were tearing at one another in a horrific scene of gore and bloodshed.

The lifeless bodies of all types of fearsome beasts also piled all the way up to the top of the gate, which was occupied by a giant beast in a strange crouched posture. There was thick smoke swirling all around it, and the creature had an enormous horn on its head, while its cavernous mouth was opened up wide, as if it were about to devour all of the surrounding beasts.

"This restriction looks quite complex, so it'll probably take a lot of time to unravel," Shi Chuankong remarked with tightly furrowed brows as he observed the array engraved onto the ground.

"We don't have any time," Han Li said with a grim expression, following which a long black saber appeared in his grasp amid a flash of dark red light.

Fox 3's gaze fell upon the black saber, and a stunned look appeared on his face at the sight of the twin fox heads engraved onto the guard of the saber.

However, the situation was too urgent for Han Li to be gauging his reaction, and at this moment, he was focused on communicating with Shi Qinghou.

"Fellow Daoist Shi, we're in a dire situation right now, and I need your help to break this restriction open. Please lend me your assistance."

"I have a feeling that whatever's sealed in here isn't to be messed with lightly. Have you really made up your mind?" Shi Qinghou asked.

"If we don't do anything, we'll just be killed by our two pursuers anyway. Time is of the essence, so please lend me your power, Fellow Daoist Shi," Han Li replied without any hesitation.

"Alright, in that case, I won't try to dissuade you. Just attack the restriction with the saber with all your might, and leave the rest to me," Shi Qinghou said.

"You have my thanks," Han Li replied, then grabbed onto the hilt of the saber with both hands before raising it up high.

From there, he cast his gaze toward the light barrier before him, and his aura began to rapidly elevate.

Shi Chuankong and the others all instinctively took a few steps backward to open up some distance between themselves and Han Li, while the bewilderment in Fox 3's eyes only became even more pronounced.

All of a sudden, a burst of crimson light flashed through the eyes of the twin fox heads on the saber, and rays of dark red light emerged over its blade, giving it a particularly abnormal appearance.

As Han Li's aura continued to elevate, shockwaves that were visible even to the naked eye were beginning to proliferate outward from his body in all directions, causing the entire underground space to rumble incessantly.

Right at this moment, Yin Xu and Gui Mu stormed into the tunnel outside amid a cloud of black mist, and Yin Xu exclaimed in an alarmed voice, "They're trying to break the array in the restricted area!"

"Even if they combine their powers, they shouldn't be able to break the Profound Infernal Vermilion Array anytime soon..."

As soon as Gui Mu's voice trailed off, a burst of violent tremors spread through the tunnel up ahead.

"Crap!" Yin Xu exclaimed as the cloud of black mist accelerated significantly, reaching the entrance of the underground cave in the blink of an eye.

From there, Yin Xu and Gui Mu were just in time to see Han Li stepping forward and swinging the black saber down onto the light barrier.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as the dark red light on the saber brightened significantly, forming a giant crimson saber projection that was over a thousand feet in length before crashing down upon the light barrier.

There seemed to be a two-headed white fox resting atop the saber projection, and it turned to Yin Xu and Gui Mu with a sinister grin.

In the next instant, a resounding thunderclap rang out as countless arcs of dark red lightning erupted out of the saber projection, forming an extremely irregular screen of lightning.

Arcs of dark red lightning were flailing around in all directions like whips, but the shockwaves from the clash between the saber projection and the light barrier formed an umbrella-like barrier of lightning that shielded Han Li's group.

"You did it!" Shi Chuankong exclaimed in an ecstatic voice as he stared intently at the point on the light barrier that had been struck by the saber projection.

Sure enough, a long gash that was around a hundred feet in length had appeared on the light barrier, and Fox 3 hurriedly urged, "We have to hurry!"

After unleashing that saber strike, Han Li had exhausted almost all of the immortal spiritual power in his body, and he felt completely drained.

Baili Yan and Weeping Soul immediately stepped forward to support him, one from the right and the other from the left, and they flew into the light barrier together.

Both Yin Xu and Gui Mu's expressions had darkened significantly upon seeing this.

The two of them flew toward the gash in the light barrier, only to be stopped in their tracks by the barrier of lightning, and they could only look on helplessly as Han Li's group opened the gates and made their way into the palace.

By the time the lightning barrier faded away, the opening on the light barrier had also closed.

In the next instant, two streaks of light shot forth from afar, then faded to reveal Gui Mu and Yin Xu.

"Impossible! How did they break the restriction? What was that saber that he used?" Gui Mu exclaimed with an incredulous expression.

"Now's not the time to be thinking about that! We have to chase after them!" Yin Xu replied with a furious expression as he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a black badge that had a sinister ghostly head engraved onto its surface and emanating rays of black light.

Yin Xu made a rapid string of hand seals, and the black badge instantly began to glow brightly, while the ghostly head engraved onto its surface began to move as if it had sprung to life.

Gui Mu also hurriedly focused his efforts on assisting Yin Xu, and the light radiating from the badge grew brighter and brighter, while the ghostly head on its surface swelled to around twice its original size.

At the same time, two specks of radiant white light had appeared in its eyes, giving it a fearsome appearance.

All of a sudden, two beams of gray light shot out of the ghostly head's eyes into the black light barrier, and a gash that was around ten feet in length instantly appeared on its surface before slowly widening.

Even though Yin Xu and Gui Mu were giving it everything they had, the gash on the black light barrier still wasn't widening very quickly, and only after close to twenty seconds had passed did it widen to a point where the two of them could just barely squeeze through.

Yin Xu stowed the black badge away before flying into the opening on the light barrier, followed close by Gui Mu.

By the time they entered the palace, they discovered that Han Li and the others were nowhere to be seen, clearly having already fled deeper into the palace.

Gui Mu and Yin Xu exchanged a glance with each other before setting off in pursuit, but as they did so, both of them were suppressing their aura fluctuations with all their might, seemingly fearful of alerting something.

"This is becoming too much for us to handle, Yin Xu. Should we report this matter to the regional monarch?" Gui Mu asked with a hesitant expression.

Yin Xu's expression changed drastically upon hearing this, and he hurriedly replied in a low voice, "We can't do that! Are you not aware of his temper? If he finds out what we let a group of outsiders into the restricted area, we'll be as good as dead! Have you forgotten about what happened to Elder Yin Hou all those years ago?"

"But if we don't report this matter and those people stir up some trouble inside, then our punishment will only be even more severe. If that happens, we'll be wishing we were dead!" Gui Mu said as he shuddered in an uneasy manner.

"It'll be fine. The array in the restricted area is extremely powerful, and even you and I aren't able to break it. At first glance, it looks like they were quite smart to have fled into this place, but in reality, they've backed themselves into a corner. All we have to do is capture them and make sure that no word of this escapes," Yin Xu assured with a mocking sneer.

"Alright," Gui Mu replied after a brief hesitation.

As the two of them were speaking to one another, they had already passed through a plaza inside the palace.

Beyond the plaza were seven or eight smaller palaces, between which were around a dozen small paths that led deeper into the area.

The interior of the palace was very dimly lit, so visibility was limited to within a thousand feet, and there was also an ever-present restrictive power that prevented one from being able to make use of their spiritual sense.

There were still no signs of Han Li and the others here, not even the slightest abnormal energy fluctuations, and it seemed impossible to tell where they had fled to.

Chapter 745: Final Stand

Yin Xu's pupils contracted slightly as he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a speck of black light that swelled rapidly in size at a rate that was discernible even to the naked eye, forming a black mirror that was revolving incessantly while releasing bursts of strange black light in all directions.

A series of projections appeared in the surrounding space in the wake of the black light, and they were either walking or flying around, seemingly belonging to the people who had previously passed through this point.

Some of these projections were quite clear, while others were very indistinct.

Among all of the projections, the ones belonging to Han Li and the others were particularly clear, and they were flying toward one of the paths up ahead.

"After them!"

Yin Xu and Gui Mu immediately set off in that direction.

......

Deep inside the black palace, Han Li and the others were racing along, passing through a seemingly endless expanse of palaces, pavilions, and pergolas, which looked as if they belonged to an imperial city.

They didn't dare to fly too high, so they could only dart along between the buildings close to the ground.

As they traveled onward, the light became dimmer and dimmer, and wisps of black mist began to appear in the air. Everything that was beyond three hundred to four hundred feet away was blurry and unclear, and spiritual sense was also severely restricted.

With the eyesight of Fox 3 and the others, visibility was only just over a thousand feet, and even with Han Li's Infernal Devilish Eyes, he was only able to see about three thousand feet.

Aside from that, there was some type of immense spatial pressure hanging in the air, which wasn't enough to harm Han Li and the others, but it was slowing them down significantly.

"What the hell is this place? Why does it feel so strange here? Have you discovered anything, Fellow Daoist Weeping Soul?" Fox 3 asked.

"No, this is my first time here as well," Weeping Soul replied with a shake of her head.

"The fact that battles are prohibited works very much in our favor. How about we make a final stand here?" Fox 3 proposed.

"We can't do that. Even if such a rule is in place, those two may not follow it if it comes down to a battle of life and death, so it would be too risky to bank on that. Even if we're going to make a final stand, we have to make sure that it's at a place that'll give us a definite advantage," Shi Chuankong immediately said, and Fox 3 nodded in response.

All of a sudden, a peculiar look appeared on Han Li's face, and he remarked, "The layout of the surrounding palace is quite profound, almost like it's some type of array. Perhaps that has something to do with the spatial pressure in the air."

The layout of the surrounding buildings didn't appear to be remarkable in any way, but in reality, there was some type of pattern to them. On top of that, all of these buildings had many runes engraved upon them, and they seemed to be connected somehow.

"You're right," Baili Yan agreed with a nod. "This place appears to be very important, so it's rather strange that there are no guards stationed here at all."

All of a sudden, an alarmed look appeared on Weeping Soul's face as she exclaimed, "Gui Mu and Yin Xu are catching up to us!"

Everyone immediately sped up upon hearing this, but their cultivation bases were far inferior to those of Gui Mu and Yin Xu, and the spatial pressure in the air certainly wasn't doing them any favors, so the gap between them was rapidly closing.

"There's a passageway up ahead that leads underground, and there's a peculiar aura inside. Should we go in?" Han Li suddenly asked as he turned to a certain direction.

"We may have no choice," Shi Chuankong replied with a grim expression.

"Surely whatever's inside can't spell more trouble than the two chasing after us," Fox 3 chuckled.

"Indeed. At this point, we may as well go in and have a look. At this rate, we'll be dead anyway, and this may be our only chance at survival," Baili Yan agreed.

As for Weeping Soul, she was naturally happy to follow Han Li's lead.

"Come with me," Han Li said as he veered slightly to the left.

Everyone immediately followed along, and they arrived at a fake mountain that was several thousand feet tall, at the foot of which was a cave that was around thirty to forty feet tall.

The sides of the cave were white in color, and they were giving off faint rays of light that illuminated the interior of the cave.

Inside the cave was a long passageway that appeared to lead underground, and Han Li and the others were met with a rush of heat that carried a slightly acrid, sulfurous odor.

The group immediately flew into the passageway without any hesitation, and they had only just vanished into it when Gui Mu and Yin Xu appeared at the entrance.

"How did they know to go in there? Could it be that they know the secret of this place? But that's impossible, even You Luo hasn't ever been allowed to visit this place!" Gui Mu grumbled with tightly furrowed brows.

"Cut the chit-chat, we need to go in and capture them right away," Yin Xu harrumphed coldly as he flew into the tunnel, while a hint of anger flashed through Gui Mu's eyes, but he quickly composed himself after taking a deep breath before following along behind Yin Xu.

Meanwhile, Han Li and the others were forging ahead as quickly as they could. The tunnel had no branches and very few bends, and it became brighter and brighter the deeper they progressed, so they were able to travel very smoothly.

However, this only meant that it would be easier for their pursuers to catch them, so none of them were particularly encouraged by this.

All of a sudden, everyone's expressions changed slightly as they drew to an abrupt halt.

The tunnel up ahead had suddenly expanded into a giant square space that seemed to be an enormous hall, which was around three hundred to four hundred feet in size.

This was also the end of the tunnel, and at the deepest point of the hall was a tightly shut stone gate. The spatial pressure in this area had also escalated to unprecedented levels, and the stone gate was riddled with all types of patterns that were giving off lights of various different colors, all of which were emanating powerful aura fluctuations.

It was clear that these were all extremely powerful restrictions, and the most eye-catching one among them was the silver light, which had formed a barrier over the stone gate.

The silver light barrier was rippling incessantly, presenting a lustrous sight to behold.

The other walls of the hall were also riddled with similar array patterns that were connected to the restrictions on the stone gate, forming a rather special restriction.

Everyone inspected their surroundings momentarily, and it began to dawn on them that they had been backed into a corner.

Fox 3 gritted his teeth as he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a conical white immortal treasure that was around a foot in length.

Judging from its aura, it was at least a seventh-grade immortal treasure, and there were arcs of white lightning flashing along the entirety of its length as it shot forth as a blurry white shadow that hurtled directly toward the stone gate.

Right before it was about to make contact with the stone gate, Fox 3 made a hand seal, and a deafening thunderclap rang out as a radiant white sun appeared before exploding violently.

Countless incandescent arcs of white lightning erupted forth in all directions, completely inundating the stone gate in blinding white radiance.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as purple light flashed within his eyes, and the blinding white rapidly faded to reveal the conical white immortal treasure, which had struck the stone gate, but was kept out with ease by all of the restrictions.

Everyone's expressions changed once again upon seeing this.

They had all witnessed the power of the immortal treasure, but it hadn't even been able to leave the slightest mark on the stone gate.

"Sorry for getting us into this mess, everyone. Looks like we're in a world of trouble now," Han Li said with a wry smile.

"You have nothing to apologize for, Fellow Daoist Li. We all made the choice to enter this place, so we have to bear the consequences together. In any case, continuing to run like this isn't going to get us anywhere, and this confrontation was always inevitable, so let's make a final stand," Fox 3 said with a faint smile as the conical white immortal treasure flew back to him at his behest.

"I agree. Those people wouldn't dare to fight all-out here, but we have no such qualms, so our fate is far from sealed," Baili Yan chimed in with a smile of his own.

Weeping Soul remained silent, but she stood firmly by Han Li's side, making her stance clear.

In contrast, Shi Chuankong wasn't standing with everyone else. Instead, he flew over to the stone gate before making a hand seal to summon an antiquated golden mirror, which projected a beam of silver light onto the gate.

The restrictions on the stone gate immediately began to ripple, and in particular, the silver light barrier was trembling incessantly.

"Fellow Daoist Shi, do you have a way to unravel these restrictions?" Baili Yan asked with an elated expression upon seeing this.

"The restrictions here are very advanced, so I can't make any guarantees. I'll need some time to study them carefully," Shi Chuakong replied in a non-committal fashion.

"Alright, then take as much time as you need, Brother Shi, and I'll do my best to hold off our pursuers," Fox 3 promised.

Shi Chuankong nodded in response, then turned his full attention to the restrictions on the stone gate.

Han Li took a glance at Shi Chuankong, then quickly turned his gaze back to the entrance of the tunnel.

"Here they come!" Weeping Soul said in a low voice, and in the next instant, Gui Mu and Yin Xu emerged from the tunnel.

"You sure scurried away quite quickly for a ragtag bunch of rats!" Yin Xu sneered in a cold voice.

A cold sneer also appeared on Gui Mu's face, and he began, "I suggest you lay down..."

Before he had a chance to finish, Fox 3's conical immortal treasure hurtled directly toward him amid an explosive thunderclap.

"If you want to fight, then cut the chit-chat!"

Chapter 746: More Dire Straits

The conical white immortal treasure sped through the air as a bolt of golden lightning, and all of a sudden, over a hundred identical immortal treasures appeared in the blink of an eye.

Every single one of them were surrounded by arcs of white lightning that were giving off tremendous power, and they took up virtually half of the entire hall as they descended upon Gui Mu and Yin Xu in an unstoppable barrage.

"Don't get cocky, you little rat!" Gui Mu sneered as he spread his fingers open before making a grabbing motion.

A ball of radiant black light appeared over his hand, releasing countless black vines that shot forth in a frenzy. Countless branches extended out of the vines to form a dense net, and all of the conical immortal treasures were instantly stopped in their tracks.

They were like fish that had been caught in a net, whizzing around within the net of vines in a chaotic fashion.

Right at this moment, Fox 3 made a hand seal, and all of the lightning cones released arcs of radiant white lightning to strike the net of black vines.

However, the net of vines only shuddered slightly, and all of the arcs of white lightning were instantly scattered, while the net remained completely unscathed.

Immediately thereafter, numerous black vines shot out of the surface of the net, instantly ensnaring all of the white lightning spikes trapped within it.

A cloud of what appeared to be black vapor then began to seep out of the vine before enveloping the lightning spikes, and it was giving off a nauseating odor of decay, much like the smell of a rotting swamp.

The lightning spike immediately began to tremble incessantly as the white light emanating from them flashed erratically, and their auras were also rapidly fading, as if they were being corroded.

An urgent look appeared on Fox 3's face as he made a rapid string of hand seals, and the lightning spikes began to struggle with all their might.

Black light and white lightning clashed violently amid strings of rumbling thunderclaps, causing the nearby space and the entire hall to tremble and quake.

"Gui Mu! What do you think you're doing?" Yin Xu yelled in a furious voice.

Gui Mu's eyelids twitched slightly upon hearing this, then hurriedly made a hand seal, and the black light emanating from the net of vines instantly receded.

Fox 3 pounced on this opportunity to redouble his efforts, and a burst of lightning law powers erupted out of the lightning spikes as they freed themselves from the net of vines in one fell swoop.

Just as they had predicted, Gui Mu and Yin Xu's hands were somewhat tied here.

All of a sudden, a burst of azure light flashed over Han Li's body, and in the next instant, nine azure flying swords appeared out of thin air in front of Yin Xu before hurtling directly toward him in unison.

Yin Xu's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and a layer of dark shadows emerged over his body, then swelled drastically to form a spherical black barrier around him.

The nine Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords struck the spherical barrier, plunging most of the way into it before being brought to an abrupt halt.

Yin Xu gave a cold harrumph as a series of black runes emerged over the spherical barrier, and vortex-like ripples appeared over the spots on the barrier that had been struck by the nine swords.

A burst of tremendous suction force surged out of the spherical barrier, attempting to suck in the nine Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, and Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, but he remained calm and collected as he opened his mouth to release a ball of azure light.

The ball of azure light was giving off immense immortal spiritual power fluctuations, and it split up into nine, with each part vanishing into one of the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

Each burst of azure light contained a time law thread, and with this injection of power, the nine flying swords immediately began to tremble violently, which thick arcs of golden lightning flashed over their blades.

There were also time law runes present within the arcs of lightning, and the spherical black barrier immediately began to tremble violently as an explosive aura began to build from the clash between the black light and golden lightning.

Yin Xu immediately eased up on the pressure upon seeing this, while Han Li's Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords only glowed brighter and brighter, and it didn't take long before the spherical barrier was shattered into countless black shadows.

The Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords flew back to Han Li in a flash, while Yin Xu looked on with a frustrated expression.

Before he had a chance to do anything, two dark red chains shot out of the space behind him without any warning, then began to wrap themselves around him like a pair of spirit snakes.

Yin Xu's body instantly transformed into a slender shadow that vanished into the surrounding darkness, only to reappear on the other side of the hall an instant later.

"You Luo, how dare you collude with these outsiders and betray our Infernal Region? Have you forgotten everything that our regional monarch has done for you?" Yin Xu accused in a cold voice.

"I..."

Weeping Soul shuddered slightly upon hearing this, and a conflicted look appeared on her face.

"Cut the chit-chat!" Han Li yelled as he made a hand seal, and a mountain of sword projections erupted out of his nine Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords before crashing down upon Yin Xu with tremendous sword qi fluctuations.

Yin Xu took a glance at the walls of the giant hall around him, and on this occasion, he thrust his palms forward to oppose the vast mountain of sword projections instead of taking further evasive measures.

A series of black shadows sprang out of the palms of his hands, then intertwined to form a black wave that clashed against the sword projections.

A string of muffled explosions rang out as the mountain of sword projections was vanquished, but the black shadows had also faded.

Yin Xu's complexion paled ever so slightly, but he recovered just a moment later.

He didn't dare to unleash too much power, and he had to ward off Han Li's attack while also minimizing the impact of the clash, which was far more difficult said than done.

"Now's not the time to be hesitating, Weeping Soul. We have to seize this opportunity!" Han Li communicated to Weeping Soul through voice transmission, then made another hand seal, and the swordlight emanating from the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords transformed into a series of azure lotus flowers, all of which hurtled directly toward Yin Xu once again with tremendous sword qi fluctuations.

At this point, Weeping Soul had also hardened her resolve again, and she swept both sleeves through the air to release a pair of dark red chains that shot forth toward Yin Xu like lightning.

Baili Yan also sprang into action, opening his mouth to release a ball of black fire, which transformed into a series of thick streaks of black swordlight aimed at Gui Mu.

Every single streak of swordlight had black flames burning over it, and they were giving off incredibly formidable baleful qi fluctuations.

Lights of all types of different colors were flashing within the hall as the battle raged on.

Just as they anticipated, Yin Xu and Gui Mu were very afraid of further escalation, and they didn't dare to unleash their full power or damage any part of the hall, so they had to be excessively cautious.

In contrast, Han Li and the others had no such inhibitions, and at times, they would intentionally unleash large-scale attacks to force the two Great Encompassment cultivators to stop them.

As the battle continued, Yin Xu and Gui Mu were feeling extremely frustrated as they weren't able to unleash even a fraction of their power.

However, they were still Great Encompassment cultivators, and their proficiency in the use of law powers far surpassed that of Han Li and the others, so they were able to quickly consolidate and slowly gain the upper hand.

Despite their best efforts, there wasn't much that Han Li and the others could do in the face of such an enormous cultivation base disparity, and they were slowly but steadily being forced onto the back foot.

At this point, the battlefield had already been reduced to just a small part of the hall, while the rest of the hall had returned to darkness.

On one side of the hall, Han Li and Weeping Soul were locked in battle against Yin Xu.

Right at this moment, Han Li and Yin Xu passed each other by like lightning, and a dull thump rang out as Han Li stumbled back with a long, bleeding gash torn into his shoulder.

Yin Xu also swayed momentarily, but then immediately steadied himself before lashing out at Han Li again.

The black light around his body rippled slightly, following which two thick black spear projections shot out of it, hurtling toward Han Li and Weeping Soul at an incredible speed.

The spear projections weren't giving off particularly formidable auras, but there was a layer of rippling black light over each of them that was giving off peculiar vibrations.

Han Li was still yet to steady himself, a grim look appeared on his face as he immediately made a hand seal, upon which the nine Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords circling around above his head swelled drastically in size before clashing against the oncoming black spear projection in rapid succession.

A string of dull thumps rang out as the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords struck the spear projection, only for all of them to slide down its length, and the spear projection wasn't slowed down in the slightest as it continued to hurtle toward Han Li.

Han Li's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and he hurriedly sprang back in retreat. At the same time, radiant golden light erupted out of his body, while a layer of fine, purplish-golden scales emerged over his fists as he rammed them against the tip of the spear projection.

However, contrary to his expectations, there was no earth-shattering explosion. Instead, the black spear projection exploded without posing any resistance in the face of Han Li's fists.

Han Li faltered slightly upon seeing this, following which his expression changed drastically as he could sense a burst of peculiar energy fluctuations entering his body from the detonated spear projection.

Immediately thereafter, his entire body turned numb, while his immortal spiritual power circulation also became very sluggish, and was instantly rooted to the spot.

Weeping Soul was also in a similar situation, and right at this moment, Yin Xu made a hand seal, upon which tendrils of black shadows sprang out of Han Li and Weeping Soul's bodies to ensnare them.

At the same time, these shadows rapidly intertwined to form a giant black cage around them in the blink of an eye.

Han Li was only immobilized for a moment before regaining his mobility, but at that point, he had already been trapped in the cage.

These tendrils of black shadows were extremely resilient, and they had wrapped themselves around him in layers. On top of that, there were also bursts of tremendous pressure converging from all directions within the cage.

Meanwhile, Fox 3 and Baili Yan had also been ensnared by Gui Mu's ghost vines, which had formed tight cocoons around them.

In a matter of mere minutes, everyone had been captured, and the situation was looking dire once again.

Chapter 747: Taking a Risk

Gui Mu's gaze roamed over the ensnared Fox 3 and Baili Yan as a sinister grin appeared on his face, following which he summoned a pair of objects that resembled withered black branches.

There were lines of gray text on these branches that were flashing incessantly, giving them a rather profound appearance.

A burst of gray ripples surged out of the branches alongside a fearsome cloud of baleful qi, and in the next instant, a fierce look flashed through Gui Mu's eyes as he swept a sleeve through the air, sending the two branches flying toward Fox 3 and Baili Yan.

On the other side of the hall, Yin Xu also raised both hands to release around a dozen black threads.

These black threads were hair-thin needles, each of which was around a foot in length. There were black runes flashing over the needles, giving them a rather indistinct appearance, and they were flying toward all parts of Han Li's body at an alarming speed.

A grim look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, but he didn't panic, and his Mantra Treasured Axis appeared behind him before immediately beginning to revolve rapidly.

Even though the black cage had trapped him, it wasn't able to restrict the immortal spiritual power in his body.

Dense waves of golden ripples surged out of the Mantra Treasured Axis, instantly encompassing the entire surrounding area within a radius of several hundred feet, and everything caught within the golden ripples instantly fell completely still, regardless of whether it be the black needles, the withered branches, the black cage, or the ghost vine cocoons.

Yin Xu, Gui Mu, and Shi Chuankong were also instantly rooted to the spot by the golden ripples, leaving Han Li as the only person in the hall that was still able to move.

However, he knew that he had only managed to immobilize the two Great Encompassment cultivators with his time law powers by catching them off guard, so they definitely weren't going to be stopped for long.

Taking advantage of this brief window of opportunity, Han Li immediately began to chant an incantation, and golden light surged over his body as he extended a finger forward.

The golden light around his body converged toward his fingertip, as did all of the remaining time law threads in his body.

A golden finger projection appeared before piercing into the black cage, and it wasn't very large, but it was giving off an extremely formidable aura, as if it were capable of tearing a hole into the very heavens.

A large hole was instantly pierced into the cage like a finger poking through a sheet of paper, and at the same time, he made a grabbing motion to summon his Profound Heavenly Gourd.

A streak of golden light shot out of the mouth of the gourd, then quickly revolved around Fox 3 and Baili Yan.

The streak of golden light was extremely bright and was also giving off peerlessly sharp law power fluctuations, which had come from the destruction of a metal-attribute immortal treasure of an extremely high caliber.

The ghost vines around the two were instantly severed, while Han Li flew out of the hole in the black cage, taking Weeping Soul along with him.

At the same time, he swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of azure light that enveloped both Fox 3 and Baili Yan, following which he shot back in retreat.

At this point, Gui Mu and Yin Xu had already freed themselves from the restraints of Han Li's time law powers, and black light was surging out of their bodies to resist the surrounding golden ripples.

The golden ripples were instantly torn apart without being able to pose any resistance, and the flow of time around the two of them was returned to normal.

However, at this point, Han Li and the others had also been freed, and they flew over to Shi Chuankong's side.

All of the golden ripples in the hall then vanished in a flash at Han Li's behest, and everything in the hall returned to normal.

"Thank you, Fellow Daoist Han," Fox 3 said.

Baili Yan was staring at Han Li with a stunned look on his face, and he also expressed his gratitude.

As for Shi Chuankong, he seemed to be completely oblivious to what had just happened, and he was still intently studying the restrictions on the stone gate.

At this moment, there were hundreds of silver array flags hovering around him to form several silver arrays.

All of these arrays were glowing radiantly, casting bright silver light onto the stone gate, while also releasing countless silver runes into the silver light barrier, which was flashing and buzzing incessantly.

"We've only been able to survive up to this point thanks to the inhibitions of our opponents, but let's not forget that they're still Great Encompassment cultivators, so we have to be extra careful from here onward," Han Li said as he stared intently at Yin Xu and Gui Mu.

Fox 3 and the others immediately nodded in response with grim expressions.

Instead of immediately lashing out at Han Li and the others again, Yin Xu communicated to Gui Mu through voice transmission, "That brat is a real pain in the backside."

"Even for us, it takes some time to counteract his time law powers. It's not a long time, but it's enough for them to regroup. At this rate, they'll be able to drag this battle on indefinitely, and the situation will be beyond salvation if they manage to break the restrictions on the gate," Gui Mu replied as he cast a glance at Shi Chuankong.

"The restrictions on the gate were personally set up by the regional monarch, there's no way that these brats could break them so easily. On top of that, the baleful qi here is far denser than it is outside. I can sense that they're already struggling with the effects of baleful qi corrosion, so even if we don't do anything, they won't be able to last much longer," Yin Xu said with a sinister grin.

Gui Mu faltered slightly upon hearing this, and he turned his gaze back to Han Li and the others, following which a hint of elation flashed through his eyes.

At the same time, Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as the baleful qi in his body began to stir once again.

"Master..."

A concerned look appeared on Weeping Soul's face, and she was just about to say something when Yin Xu and Gui Mu suddenly sprang forward.

Right as the battle was about to resume, a burst of incredibly radiant silver light abruptly surged out of the stone gate, illuminating the entire hall in blinding radiance.

Shi Chuankong was making a rapid string of hand seals, and the array flags in the silver arrays around him were flying down in rapid succession before embedding themselves into the silver light barrier on the stone gate in an orderly fashion.

The silver light barrier immediately began to flash erratically, and all of the array patterns on the other walls of the hall also began to light up.

Beyond the stone gate, a faint roar rang out, causing the entire hall to shudder slightly.

Yin Xu and Gui Mu's expressions changed drastically upon seeing this.

"What the hell are you doing? Stop!"

The two of them immediately abandoned Han Li and the others to pounce at Shi Chuankong instead.

"Stop them! Don't let them disturb Fellow Daiost Shi!" Han Li yelled as he appeared before the two Great Encompassment cultivators in a flash, then swept a sleeve through the air, upon which the nine Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords around him swelled drastically in size before hurtling directly toward Gui Mu.

At the same time, a beam of crimson light erupted out of the Profound Heavenly Gourd toward Yin Xu.

Fox 3 and the others also sprang into action, summoning a vast array of immortal treasures to form a barrier in the path of Yin Xu and Gui Mu.

Even with their Great Encompassment Stage cultivation bases, Yin Xu and Gui Mu didn't dare to take these attacks lightly, and they could only stop in their tracks to protect themselves.

Meanwhile, bright silver light was radiating from Shi Chuankong's body, releasing a series of translucent silver threads that quickly vanished into the silver light barrier.

At the same time, the silver lute appeared in his grasp, and he began rapidly strumming his fingers over its strings.

With each note that was played, a streak of silver light would fly out of the lute before also vanishing into the silver light barrier, causing it to glow even brighter.

On top of that, the buzzing ringing out from the light barrier had crescendoed to a violent rumbling at this point, and Shi Chuankong's hands were flying over the strings of the lute as a pair of untraceable blurs.

Right at this moment, one final streak of radiant silver light flew out of the lute. There was a faint silver humanoid figure inside, and it vanished into the light barrier, which shuddered one final time before falling away.

All of the other restrictions on the stone gate instantly dimmed significantly as if they had also been severely damaged.

At this moment, there was an unnatural flush in Shi Chuankong's cheeks, and blood was flowing down from the corners of his lips, but he was in extremely high spirits as he yelled, "Finally! I've finally managed to refine the Virata Lute!"

After turning around to take a glance at the battle raging behind him, he strummed the strings of the lute once more, and two ribbons of silver light shot out of the lute at an incredible speed, enveloping Gui Mu and Yin Xu in a flash.

In the next instant, both of them vanished without any warning, only to reappear near the entrance of the underground tunnel.

The two of them exchanged an astonished glance, then frantically flew back into the underground tunnel.

Han Li and the others were also momentarily rooted to the spot upon seeing this, while Shi Chuankong continued to strum the strings of his lute as he said, "I've already disabled the spatial restriction on the gate, but only on a temporary basis thanks to the power of the Virata Lute. The restriction will recover again very soon, so we have to get in right now."

Streaks of silver light flew out of lute as he spoke, descending onto the nearby ground to form a teleportation array.

Han Li and the others immediately stowed away their immortal treasures upon hearing this, then flew into the array.

Shi Chuankong chanted a brief incantation, and the group vanished from within the array amid a flash of silver light.

Almost as soon as they disappeared, two streaks of black light flew into the underground cave, then faded to reveal Yin Xu and Gui Mu.

At this point, the hall was already completely empty, and their steely expressions darkened even further upon seeing this.

The silver light barrier on the stone gate was already taking shape again, but it was still rippling violently in an unstable fashion.

"The seal is inside! We have to use the infernal badge to open the restrictions here and chase after them!" Gui Mu said in an urgent voice as he turned to Yin Xu, who summoned his infernal badge, but didn't use it right away.

"What are you waiting for?" Gui Mu asked.

"You think I want to wait? Right now, the restrictions on the gate still haven't recovered, so even the infernal badge can't open them!" Yin Xu snapped with a dark expression.

Gui Mu fell silent upon hearing this, and he stared intently at the stone gate with his hand balled up into tight fists.

Chapter 748: Ancient Mythical Beast

After entering through the stone gate, Han Li and the others passed through a dim passageway before arriving in an extremely spacious hall.

The interior of the hall was also quite dim, and there were some yellow oil lamps hanging from the walls on either side. Some type of white oil was being burned in the lamps, and it produced no smoke, but it did release a slightly sickly sweet aroma.

Han Li heaved a long sigh of relief, and everyone else was also looking quite relieved.

Escaping from two Great Encompassment cultivators was no mean feat, and if the restrictions had been opened just a moment later, perhaps all of them would've been wiped out.

Even though they were now temporarily safe, Han Li hadn't let down his guard in the slightest.

He had no idea what this place was, and if it weren't for the desperate nature of their circumstances, he definitely wouldn't have ventured into this type of place. In most cases, restricted areas of major tribes were places of special meaning, usually either containing some cultivation arts, secret scriptures, or treasures, or places where certain things were sealed.

Given how apprehensive Gui Mu and Yin Xu were about damaging the restrictions in this place, it was very likely that there was something sealed in here.

After taking a brief moment to catch their breath, everyone immediately split up to search the hall.

The entire ground in the hall was riddled with layers upon layers of extremely complex array patterns, while two very long murals had been carved onto the walls on either side. The scenes depicted in the murals mostly consisted of battles between different beasts, much like what had been seen on the palace gates.

"Something's not right... It's a dead-end up ahead. We're stuck here," Fox 3 declared upon reaching the end of the hall.

Han Li turned to discover that there were no tunnels that led anywhere deeper at the end of the hall. Instead, there was a giant humanoid beast relief engraved onto the entire wall, and it was the same beast as the one engraved onto the right side of the palace.

However, on this occasion, the giant beast was in an upright position, rather than a crouching one, revealing its legs to resemble those of a horse or a deer, rather than those of a human. There was a clear bend at the knee joint, and a series of giant black scales had been engraved all over them.

It had one hand raised up high with its fingers curled up into claws and a ball of black mist hovering over the palm of the hand, while in its other hand was a very strange-looking giant fiery sword. It appeared to be roaring to the heavens, and there was a primordial aura of menace emanating from it.

"The fact that we were able to break the spatial restriction outside means that it definitely won't be able to keep them out for long," Shi Chuankong said as he scoured his surroundings with a concerned expression.

"Let's not panic. We should figure out what kind of place this is first," Han Li said.

"This seems to be some type of ceremonial site. Take a look at the murals over there," Weeping Soul suddenly said.

Everyone turned to the innermost part of the wall on the right hand side, and sure enough, the murals there depicted some type of ancient humanoid beings performing a ceremony for an ancient deity.

The scene depicted in the mural displayed bloodshed on an enormous scale, with tens of thousands of Gray Realm beings serving as sacrifices. There were both unintelligent Gray Realm demons, as well as beings from civilized tribes thrown into the mix, and all of them had been herded into a giant crater that resembled an enormous bowl.

Outside the crater crouched the giant beast engraved onto the wall. Half of its body was leaning over the edge of the crater, and its cavernous mouth was opened slightly with a look of greed on its face.

Han Li recognized some of the beings in the crater, and using them as reference, he was able to determine that the giant beast had to have been at least ten thousand feet in size.

After taking a glance at the giant crater, Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he took a few steps back, then turned to a strange indentation in the ground.

The lines and patterns on the ground seemed to be completely chaotic and haphazard, but he had noticed that all of them actually converged to this small indentation, which was only several dozen feet in size.

"Have you discovered something, Fellow Daoist Li?" Baili Yan asked.

"Take a look at that indentation there. Doesn't it look like a miniature version of the crater depicted in that ceremonial mural?" Han Li asked.

"Now that you mention it, it does look rather similar. It looks like this place really is a ceremonial site then," Shi Chuankong replied.

"There's a very good chance that the creature on the murals is being sealed here, and that's why this is a restricted area," Han Li speculated.

"No wonder no fighting is allowed here, the Infernal Tribe must be afraid of damaging the seal and releasing that creature," Fox 3 said.

Right at this moment, the entire hall suddenly shuddered violently as a burst of rumbling rang out from outside.

"They've begun breaking the restrictions..." Weeping Soul said.

"At this point, there's already no way back for us. Seeing as the Infernal Tribe is clearly apprehensive of this thing, let's find a way to release it, and perhaps that could give us some chance of surviving this," Han Li said with a grim expression.

A hesitant look flashed through Weeping Soul's eyes upon hearing this, but ultimately, she didn't say anything.

Han Li was just about to say something upon noticing her hesitant expression when Shi Qinghou's voice rang out in his mind.

"I suggest you don't do that. I've already recalled what this thing is, and if you release it, there's a very good chance you'll all be killed before those two can even get to you."

"You know what this creature is?" Han Li asked.

"Have you heard of the Kun Hou?" Shi Qinghou asked.

"What's that?"

"The Kun Hou is a being that's existed since the very inception of the Gray Realm. It's said that it was formed by the baleful essence of the Gray Realm, and its power is unmatched. Even to this day, many of the Gray Realm's tribes still worship it as an ancient deity.

“As for exactly why it's been sealed here by the Infernal Tribe, that's beyond me. I'm telling you this as a precautionary warning, but ultimately, the decision is still up to you," Shi Qinghou explained, then fell silent again.

"Master, what should we do?" Weeping Soul asked.

Everyone else also turned to him, and it was clear that they had all grown accustomed to looking to him for leadership.

"Desperate times call for desperate measures. Regardless of what's down there, let's release it first," Han Li decided.

Outside the hall, the rumbling was becoming louder and louder, and it seemed that Gui Mu and Yin Xu were becoming more and more agitated.

"The restrictions here are extremely complex. I don't think we currently possess the power to destroy it by force in a short time, so we should perhaps try and set up some arrays to unravel it," Shi Chuankong suggested.

Han Li nodded in agreement, then declared, "Time is of the essence, so let's get to work."

With that, everyone split up and began searching for the important points in the array.

Han Li activated his Infernal Devilish Eyes as he turned his gaze to the ceremonial altar ahead of him, and he quickly discovered that there were many squiggly worm-like patterns engraved onto the altar, which had previously appeared quite smooth. These patterns filled the entire altar, and there appeared to be no rhyme or reason to them. On top of that, all of the patterns were filled with some type of black dirt-like substance.

The ceremonial pit was also filled with patterns, which formed a strange flame-like design.

After conducting an extensive examination, Han Li didn't notice anything amiss, and he turned his gaze to the surrounding murals, but once again, he wasn't able to find any points of interest.

"Have any of you found anything?" Fox 3 asked as he made his way back from a corner of the hall.

"There are some patterns on the ground, but they're completely random and appear to only be there for decorative purposes," Shi Chuankong replied with a shake of his head.

Han Li raised his head to look up at the ceiling, where there were a total of seven circles of runes engraved, with each successive circle larger than the previous one, and at the very center of the seven circles was an upside-down black pillar.

"Take a look up there," Han Li suddenly said, and everyone immediately obliged.

"That seems to be some sort of spatial array," Shi Chuankong remarked as his eyes lit up.

"Do you recognize it, Brother Shi?" Fox 3 asked.

Instead of immediately responding, Shi Chuankong's brows became tightly furrowed as he fell into deep thought, and only after a brief silence did he reply, "This restriction is split up into two parts, and its overall layout shares some similarities with the All-encompassing Restrictive Array of our Devil Realm. On top of that, the patterns on its surface overlap with many of the spatial array patterns that I've seen earlier in Gray Realm scriptures related to arrays."

"Can any of the information on those scriptures be referenced here?" Han Li asked.

"I can't say for sure. There are some similarities, but also some clear differences. For example, there are many fire-attribute array patterns in this array, and I don't know what they're there for," Shi Chuankong replied with a hesitant expression.

Right as he was speaking, another resounding boom rang out from outside, and the ground trembled beneath everyone's feet.

"We don't have any time left. Just take a gamble and do what you think is right. If worse comes to worst, we'll just have to wait for Yin Xu and Gui Mu to get here, then fight them to the death and attempt to use their power to destroy the seal in here," Han Li said in a calm manner.

"Alright, in that case, please follow my instructions and lend me your assistance, everyone," Shi Chuankong replied with a solemn nod.

Everyone gave a collective affirmative response, and Shi Chuankong began handing out Baleful Inkstones and array plates, all of which were to be set up on the ground in the hall.

After that was done, he began instructing everyone to embed the same items into the ceiling above.

Aside from the sounds of Shi Chuankong's verbal instructions and everyone's shuffling feet, the only other sound that could be heard was the rumbling from outside, and the atmosphere had become extremely tense.

Chapter 749: Emergence

Close to twenty seconds later, a resounding boom rang out in the hearts of Han Li and the others as Yin Xu and Gui Mu broke through the array outside.

"Just a bit more! Hurry!" Shi Chuankong urged through gritted teeth as sweat poured down his forehead.

"We don't have time. Keep going, I'll find a way to buy us some time," Baili Yan declared as he rose to his feet.

"Master, I can't really help out much here, so I'll go with Fellow Daoist Baili," Weeping Soul volunteered.

"It's too dangerous for the two of you to go like this. We're dealing with two Great Encompassment cultivators that can probably kill both of you just by lifting a finger!" Han Li said with tightly furrowed brows while continuing to work without pause.

"But if we don't go, they'll get in here before we can release that thing, and if that happens, all of us will truly be doomed. Back when the Blaze Dragon Dao was destroyed by Xiao Jinhan, I almost succumbed to baleful qi backlash, and it was only thanks to the High Zenith Pill that you secured that I was able to survive.

“This time, we were captured, only to be saved by Fellow Daoist Weeping Soul, so I should've already died twice anyway, why not keep pushing my luck?" Baili Yan said with a faint smile.

"Rest assured, Master. I'm a prized disciple of the Infernal Regional Monarch, so I'm sure they wouldn't dare to kill me. If I accompany Fellow Daoist Baili, we should be able to buy some time," Weeping Soul said.

"Alright, then be careful, and try to avoid direct confrontation," Han Li sighed with a conflicted look in his eyes.

Baili Yan and Weeping Soul exchanged a glance with each other, following which both of them flew out of the hall.

Meanwhile, Gui Mu and Yin Xu had only just rushed onto the small plaza outside the hall when they ran headfirst into a massive black fireball.

The giant fireball exploded violently, sending flames erupting in all directions like shooting stars.

Amid the storm of fire, a huge dark green shield split up into countless ghost vines, all of which were quickly retracted back into Gui Mu's sleeves.

"You fools! Do you know what this place is? You have no idea what you're getting yourselves into!" Gui Mu yelled in a cold voice as he cast his gaze toward Weeping Soul and Baili Yan, who were on the other side of the plaza.

"Don't waste any more time, we have to end this quick," Yin Xu urged as he took a quick glance at his surroundings.

Baili Yan wasted no time with words as he made a hand seal while chanting an incantation, then suddenly pointed a finger at his own dantian.

A heart-wrenching roar rang out as a burst of bright red light that resembled the radiance of molten lava emerged from his dantian, and a series of bright red cracks branched out of the burst of red light, rapidly spreading over his entire body.

Immediately thereafter, black flames began to erupt out of the cracks, releasing plumes of thick black smoke that quickly encompassed the entire plaza.

Weeping Soul also sprang into action upon seeing this, darting away to the side before clenching her fists as she took a step forward while letting loose a feral roar that completely belied her feminine appearance.

Black light surged rapidly over her body while her eyes turned bright red, and she swelled rapidly in size, quickly transforming into a giant black ape that was over a thousand feet tall.

The ape's fur was as hard as steel needles, and there was a strange horn on its head, while its sharp fangs were fully bared. Furthermore, a third crimson demonic eye had appeared on its glabella, and three black bone spikes were protruding out of its back.

"You Luo, you traitor! Is this how you plan to repay our regional monarch's kindness? You're going as far as to reveal your Xing Beast form for the sake of these outsiders! This is unforgivable!" Gui Mu yelled in a furious voice.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a string of resounding booms suddenly rang out from above him, and it seemed as if there were countless arcs of lightning clashing against one another deep within the dense black smoke.

A giant black dragon could just barely be made out within the smoke and lightning. There was karmic fire swirling around its entire body, and it was slowly twisting around in mid-air, blocking the way to the hall behind it.

Due to the enormity of its frame, the dragon's back was scraping violently against flight restrictions up above, sending sparks flying in all directions.

"They only dare to oppose us like this because they're convinced that we don't dare to go all-out against them for fear of damaging the restrictions here. Elder Gui Mu, go and open all of the restrictions here," Yin Xu said with a cold sneer.

"What? No, we can't do that!" Gui Mu hurriedly refused in an alarmed voice.

"They've already made it in here, so what's the point in keeping the restrictions outside active? They'll only act as a hindrance to us. If we damage the restrictions, that could trigger a chain reaction that directly destroys the seal inside, so we may as well open all of the restrictions and aim to put an end to this battle as quickly as possible," Yin Xu said with a dark expression.

"But..."

Gui Mu was still a little hesitant.

"You're familiar with the layout of this place, take the infernal badge and go right now. This is no longer just a matter of whether we'll be punished or not. If we delay the regional monarch's plans, both of us will be killed!" Yin Xu urged.

A decisive look appeared on Gui Mu's face upon hearing this, and he immediately rushed away without any further hesitation.

"You've pushed your luck one too many times, you insolent scoundrels!" Yin Xu roared, and his aura instantly swelled by severalfold.

A vast expanse of black light emerged beneath his feet, then quickly proliferated outward like a rapidly spreading puddle of black ink. The black light then rose up into the air toe encompass the entire plaza and the air above it before closing like a giant mouth.

All of a sudden, it was as if Baili Yan and Weeping Soul had been sucked into another dimension, one in which all of their senses were stripped, and they couldn't even sense the aura of the world around them anymore.

Moments later, the light barriers outside the palace faded away, and an incredibly dense shadow began to rapidly expand amid a burst of violent rumbling.

......

Meanwhile, a faint crack rang out within the hall, immediately followed by the sound of turning mechanical parts ringing out from all directions.

Han Li's trio were standing around the ceremonial pit while looking up with bated breath.

The circular patterns on the ceiling began to glow with black light, then began to turn, while the stone pillar at the very center began to slowly descend.

A faint clang rang out as the stone pillar slotted seamlessly into the ceremonial pit down below.

As the sound of more turning mechanical parts rang out, a burst of incredibly dense black baleful qi rose up from the ground, inundating the entire hall.

Han Li's trio reflexively sprang back upon seeing this, and in the next instant, the entire stone chamber began to tremble violently, while all of the Baleful Inkstones embedded into the ground and the ceiling lit up to illuminate the hall, as did all of the patterns on the ground.

Right at this moment, a sound akin to that of a panting wild animal rang out from somewhere within the hall.

"Something doesn't seem right," Han Li said as a hint of foreboding welled up in his heart, while Shi Chuankong and Fox 3 were also looking on with tense expressions.

All of a sudden, Han Li spotted a flash of light from the relief of the Kun Hou engraved onto the wall behind Fox 3. It was as if a flash of crimson flame had swept over its surface, and a layer of murky mist had emerged over it, giving it an indistinct appearance.

Immediately thereafter, all of the fearsome beasts engraved onto the walls began to shudder, as if they were about to spring to life, and the reliefs also seemed to have become more vibrant and lifelike. The mountainous piles of skeletons were also trembling incessantly, as if they were about to roll into the hall at any moment.

Right as he was about to say something, the eyes of the Kun Hou relief on the wall suddenly lit up.

"Get out of the way, Fox 3!" Han Li yelled.

Fox 3 immediately acted without hesitation, darting away to the side as quickly as he could, right as something flashed past his ear.

Two fist-sized fireballs, one crimson and one black, flew out of the relief's eye sockets while intertwining with one another, then struck the stone pillar that was descending out of the ceiling.

Flurries of sparks erupted out of both fireballs in unison, following which they began to rise up along the black stone pillar in a revolving fashion, much like a pair of winding fiery snakes. One of them climbed to the ceiling of the hall, while the other descended toward the altar, lighting up all of the array patterns in their wake, while Han Li and the others looked on in bewilderment.

The bright black light up above was resonating with the crimson light down below, as if a flame had been lit under the night sky.

Bursts of rumbling were ringing out underground, and the crimson light on the ground grew brighter and brighter while releasing waves of scorching heat.

All of a sudden, a loud crack rang out, and the altar connected to the stone pillar shuddered violently. Cracks instantly began to appear on the surrounding ground, which then began to fall away entirely.

"Look out!" Han Li warned as he immediately rose up into the air, as did Shi Chuankong and Fox 3.

The three of them looked down with tightly furrowed brows to discover that the entire ground below was beginning to split up into countless fragments before tumbling down into a giant underground crater, one that was unfathomably deep.

Within the crater were crimson and black flames that were burning ferociously, and beneath the stone pillar connected to the altar was another pillar that extended deep into the ground.

This stone pillar was riddled with ancient runes, and it was bright red from being scorched by the intense flames underground.

Han Li activated his Infernal Devilish Eyes as he cast his gaze downward, and he could sense traces of fire law auras within the crimson and black flames.

On top of that, he could sense tremendous karmic fire and baleful qi, and there seemed to be a series of intertwining red chains wrapped around the stone pillar deep within the crater.

Furthermore, he could see an indistinct shadow that was constantly flashing beneath the masses of chains.

Right at this moment, Han Li's pupils suddenly contracted drastically, and he reflexively shot up into the air, crashing straight into the ceiling of the hall up above.

At almost the exact same moment, a tremendous wave of fire came erupting out of the underground crater, accompanied by an earth-shattering roar.

A gargantuan hand then reached out of the flames before swatting through the air right where Han Li had been just a moment ago, and after missing Han Li, the hand fell onto the edge of the crater.

The hand was several thousand feet in length and looked as if it had been chiseled out of rock. It was riddled with angular chunks of black rocks, as well as sharp, thorn-like spikes, swirling over which was a layer of incredibly dense black flames.

Chapter 750: Second Unsealing

Han Li's trio was astonished by the sight of the gargantuan creature that they had just released.

Just a single one of its hands resembled a mountain, and they couldn't even imagine how massive it would be in its full glory.

The black flames were clearly also karmic flames, but the baleful qi aura and scorching heat that were radiating from them were countless times more formidable than those of the flames in the karmic fire lake.

What was even more astonishing to them was the fierce primordial aura that was emanating from deep within the crater. The aura exuded a sense of almighty power, as well as thunderous fury that had been accumulating over the course of countless centuries.

"Looks like Asura City is going to be experiencing some trouble for at least the near future," Shi Chuankong remarked in a grim voice.

"Fellow Daoist Li, should we really release this thing?" Fox 3 asked as he turned to Han Li with a hesitant expression.

"If we don't release it, we'll be dead for sure, but if we do, perhaps there could be a twist in the tale," Han Li replied.

As soon as his voice trailed off, the harsh sound of metal grating against metal rang out from underground, and around a dozen incredibly thick red chains abruptly shot forth.

Every single chain link was riddled with countless runes, and these chains seemed to have a mind of their own, wrapping themselves around the giant hand before instantly stretching themselves taut.

The sound of the chains tightening rang out as all of the patterns on the stone pillar flashed erratically, and immediately thereafter, a thunderous roar of fury rang out from underground.

Han Li's trio felt as if their internal organs were shuddering in the face of this deafening roar, and all three of them hurriedly retreated a little.

The giant hand gouged three enormous trenches into the ground as it attempted to resist the tugging chains, but ultimately, its resistance proved to be futile, and it was dragged back into the crater.

"The seal doesn't seem to have been completely broken. Why is that?" Han Li asked with furrowed brows.

Shi Chuankong hurriedly flew over to the altar on the ground upon hearing this, then began conducting a close examination.

Moments later, his gaze settled on a flame pattern that had been revealed on the edge of the altar after the ground around it had fallen away.

"On the surface, this array looks similar to the All-encompassing Restrictive Array of our Devil Race, but its internal makeup is actually very different. We seem to have loosened the seal, but judging from the presence of these array patterns, it appears that fire-attribute law powers must be injected into the array in order to completely break the seal," Shi Chuankong said in a rather unsure manner.

"Fire law powers will be required? Fellow Daoist Baili is still out there buying time for us, where are we supposed to find fire law powers from?" Fox 3 asked with a wry smile.

Shi Chuankong fell silent upon hearing this. Indeed, none of Han Li's trio had mastered the laws of fire.

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to Han Li, and he mused, "Perhaps he can help..."

Right at this moment, a resounding boom rang out from outside, immediately followed by a draconic roar that sounded like a cry of agony let loose by the blaze dragon formed by Baili Yan.

Han Li immediately sprang into action without any further hesitation upon hearing this, raising a hand to conjure up a door of silver light.

Inside the door of light, Chi Rong was seated against the wall, while Immortal Lord Hot Flame had also already woken up, but his eyes were still completely wooden and soulless. As for the two Infernal children, they were still in an unconscious state.

"Fellow Daoist Chi, right now, we're all trapped in the Gray Realm together, so we have to work together..." Han Li began.

"Tell me what you need me to do," Chi Rong interjected before Han Li had a chance to finish.

"I need to borrow your fire law powers," Han Li immediately replied.

"My cultivation arts primarily specialize in the laws of time, so my fire law powers are only secondary to my time law powers. On top of that, the restrictions in my body haven't been lifted, and too much of my fire law powers had been extracted by those Infernal Servants to refine some type of treasure, so I don't have much left to give. If you need me to help in a big way, then I'm afraid you'll be disappointed," Chi Rong said.

Han Li turned to Shi Chuankong upon hearing this, and the latter said, "It's fine, we only need a small amount of fire law powers to set things into motion."

Chi Rong wasted no more time upon hearing this, quickly stepping out of the door of silver light before flying toward the altar on the ground below.

As he approached the altar, he suddenly swayed slightly as if he were unable to support himself, and Shi Chuankong hurriedly reached out to lend him some stability.

"Just inject your fire law powers into the flame patterns here," Shi Chuankong said as he pointed at the edge of the altar.

Chi Rong took a glance at the altar, then looked into the crater down below before raising an eyebrow.

"We don't have much time, so please make haste, Fellow Daoist Chi," Han Li urged.

Chi Rong promptly obliged, laying a hand down onto the flame patterns on the edge of the altar before injecting his fire law powers into it.

Right as all of their attention was focused on the altar, two figures suddenly flew out of the open door of silver light together, then began darting their way out of the hall.

Han Li took a glance out of the corner of his eye, and he discovered that it was the two Infernal children.

"Should I go capture them again, Fellow Daoist Li?" Fox 3 asked.

"Just let them go. In this situation, it makes no difference whether we have them or not," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

However, right as Chi Rong's fire law powers illuminated the flame patterns on the altar, a low roar rang out as black whirlwind abruptly swept out of the crater, then instantly caught up to the two fleeing children.

Han Li and the others immediately turned their attention to the two children, only to see their robes instantly disintegrate, while their exposed bodies rapidly fell away.

Their skin and flesh decomposed, while their bones were cracked and pulverized, and they quickly transformed into two viscous globules of blood that were swept back by the black whirlwind.

Han Li could sense a very unique aura within the two globules of blood that were rather similar to the true spirit bloodlines in his body, but were also somewhat different.

Before he had a chance to figure out what had just happened, the entire hall began to tremble violently once again, following which a vast expanse of crimson and black flames erupted out of the crater like a volcanic eruption.

"Get back!" Han Li hurriedly yelled as he darted away while closing the Flower Branch domain, and Shi Chuankong's trio instantly followed suit.

The sound of grating chains rang out insistently from within the flames surging out of the crater, and the same enormous hand from before emerged once again, only to be ensnared by more bright red chains as soon as it reached the entrance of the crater.

However, on this occasion, the giant fiery hand was clearly several times more powerful than before, and the chains wrapped around it were only able to pose brief resistance before they were snapped.

The giant hand rose up into the air with its fingers pointed straight at the ceiling of the hall, and it pierced straight through the ceiling with ease. Immediately thereafter, it hooked its fingers into the stone material, using the entire hall as leverage to forcefully hoist itself upward.

The sound of more clanging chains rang out as flames churned violently within the underground crater, and an incredibly powerful aura was emanating from within.

Han Li and the others were swept away in an uncontrollable fashion by the tremendous aura, and they were sent crashing into the surrounding walls in a lopsided fashion.

The crimson flames in the crater gradually faded, while the black flames were only going from strength to strength, erupting out of the crater with tremendous force. At the same time, the cracks on the ground rapidly elongated, and they quickly extended their way out of the hall altogether.

On the plaza outside the hall, Yin Gua had already withdrawn his Dark Hell, and the all-encompassing shadow had faded.

There were eight giant arms formed by dense shadows behind him, all of which were raised high up in the air, and each hand was locked firmly around a vital acupoint on the body of the black blaze dragon formed by Baili Yan.

It was clear that the blaze dragon was no longer fit for battle, and its entire body was riddled with massive wounds, while black blood was flowing out of its slightly agape mouth.

Not far away from it was a black cage formed by countless wooden branches, trapped inside of which was a petite figure. However, it was impossible to make out the situation inside the cage as the figure was ensnared within layers upon layers of black ghost vines.

Bursts of dull rumbling were ringing out incessantly from underfoot, and the ever-widening cracks quickly spilled out of the hall and onto the plaza beneath their feet.

Before long, the cracks had spread over an area of tens of thousands of feet, filling virtually the entirety of the underground space.

Clouds of dust were rising up everywhere, while tongues of black karmic fire were flickering out of the cracks on the ground before blooming like fiery black lotus flowers.

"Finally... It's come out..." the blaze dragon said in a feeble but exultant voice.

"Elder Yin Xu..."

Gui Mu turned to Yin Xu with a grim expression.

"Those fools!" Yin Xu roared, and his eyes were burning with fury as the eight giant shadowy hands behind him abruptly exerted force in unison.

Black blood came cascading down like rain as the blaze dragon was torn into nine pieces like a silken ribbon, and the pieces of its body came tumbling down onto the ground.

Its head, which was still relatively intact, fell beside Yin Xu's feet and was pulverized by a single stomp, but in the instant right before the head exploded, a black shadow flew out of it before darting away.

This didn't fail to attract Yin Xu's attention, but at this point, he had no time to chase after the shadow, and he could only make a dash for the entrance of the hall.

Chapter 751: Ongoing Conference

Right at this moment, the ground beneath Yin Xu's feet rumbled violently, then split open entirely amid a burst of earth-shattering tremors.

Black karmic flames erupted out of the cracks as rocks came tumbling down from above, destroying entire sections of the surrounding palace.

Before long, an even more massive underground crater had emerged, and all that remained was a giant stone pillar standing at its center. As the ground fell away, the remnants of Baili Yan's body also tumbled into the earth.

Han Li and the others flew out of the karmic fire, then didn't stop even for a second before flying toward the edge of the underground space.

Meanwhile, Yin Xu and Gui Mu exchanged a look of despair, and they also began rushing back the same way they had come from.

All of a sudden, a violent roar of fury rang out from underground, and it was accompanied by an incredibly fearsome primordial aura that felt as if it belonged to an ancient deity and was filled with intense fury, resentment, and killing intent.

The giant black hand that had pierced into the ceiling of the hall reached upward once again before pulling up with tremendous power, and the black flames within the massive crater instantly began to churn violently as a gargantuan figure slowly rose up.

As the flames subsided, the indistinct figure finally gradually became clear.

It was an enormous head that was close to twenty thousand feet in size and was entirely black in color, looking as if it had been chiseled out of black rock. It was riddled with sharp edges and fangs, and its features only just barely resembled those of a human.

In its eyes were two balls of strange black flames that were flickering slightly, and on top of its head were two giant curved ox horns that were thousands of feet in length, resembling a pair of mountains sitting on its head.

Whenever the creature exhaled, two bursts of black flames would erupt out of its nostrils, giving off an unprecedentedly fearsome baleful aura that struck everyone with a sense of insignificance.

"What on earth have we let out..." Shi Chuankong murmured to himself as he looked back at the gargantuan head from a corner of the underground space.

"We've finally managed to release the Kun Hou, but it looks like Fellow Daoist Baili may have fallen," Han Li said with a wistful expression after examining the surrounding area with both his eyes and his spiritual sense.

"Hold on a second, it doesn't look like that thing has been completely freed yet. It seems like only its head and one of its arms have been freed," Fox 3 suddenly said.

Sure enough, there were still countless intertwining chains wrapped around the creature's body, the majority of which was still deep in the underground crater.

"This should be enough to keep the Infernal Tribe busy for a while. Thank heavens we didn't fully release it. Otherwise, I don't think we would've been able to get out of there alive," Han Li said as he took a glance at the horrified Yin Xu and Gui Mu.

"Where's Fellow Daoist Chi Rong?" Fox 3 asked.

"Right before the ground collapsed, he seemed to have discovered something within the karmic fire, and he flew straight into it instead of retreating," Shi Chuankong replied with a shake of his head.

"Leave him. You two find a way out, I'll go save Weeping Soul," Han Li said.

Right at this moment, the Kun Hou suddenly threw its head back and let loose a furious roar. Scorching karmic flames surged out of its mouth, forming a giant pillar of flames that struck the ceiling of the hall up above.

The ceiling consisted of rock that was thousands of feet thick, yet it was melted away in an instant, creating a giant hole through which a ray of dim light shone down from above.

......

At the Fallen Lake Area conference venue.

The elevated stone platform was glowing radiantly while releasing bursts of white light in all directions, presenting a majestic sight to behold.

All of the regional monarchs of the Gray Realm were seated behind the round table on the platform, and all of them wore different expressions.

At this moment, the atmosphere in the venue was rather tense. There weren't many people speaking, but the tension in the air was palpable.

Yin Chengquan, Huang Fuyu, and Xiao Buye were seated at the head of the table in a triangular formation.

The entire conference was set to last twenty days, the first seven of which was the initial discussion stage, during which the representatives of three regions were going to discuss the purpose of the conference, as well as the different stances at play, and independent small-scale discussions could also take place during this stage.

The three days after that were when the decision was going to be made through a vote.

As for the final ten days, those were reserved for discussing the possible problems that could arise from the outcome of the conference, as well as how the decided outcome was going to be achieved.

On the surface, this conference was quite a straightforward one. Everyone simply had to express their stance toward the True Immortal Realm, but what made things very complicated were the complex nuances between all of the regions, including their allegiances to the three major regions, territorial disputes, trade problems, and personal vendettas.

Even though each regional monarch was only required to express their stance on this matter, there were far too many factors involved.

Over the past few days, many of the regions had been constantly at each other's throats, while the three major regions were doing everything in their power to win over the smaller regions, and many smaller sub-conferences had been set up, plunging the entire situation into a state of chaos.

At this point, the initial discussion stage had already concluded, and this was the first day of the decision stage.

Even though it hadn't yet begun, the state of affairs was already quite clear.

Prior to the conference, the Reincarnation Region had sent out a great deal of manpower to win over the regional monarchs that had previously adopted neutral stances. In doing so, it had invested a tremendous amount of resources. The Infernal Region had the most subsidiary regions, but it hadn't done much work when it came to winning over neutral regions.

As for the Black Rope Region, it had always been a fence-sitter anyway, so it naturally hadn't made any big moves.

On top of that, most of the Gray Realm's regions harbored a great deal of enmity toward the True Immortal Region, but they were also envious of the True Immortal Region for its vast abundance of cultivation resources.

The Reincarnation Region was able to use this to its advantage to win over most of the previously neutral regional monarchs, including the Black Rope Regional Monarch.

Even though there were still some regional monarchs that still hadn't made their stances known, the overall state of affairs was already quite clear.

At this point, the conference was no more than an hour away from recommencing, but Yin Chengquan didn't seem to be agitated at all as he sat calmly in silence.

An elderly man beside Yin Chengquan leaned over slightly as he said in a quiet yet urgent voice, "Regional Monarch Yin, the current situation is not looking good for us at all. More and more regions are being won over by the Reincarnation Region."

The elderly man's name was Tian Ku, and he was the Valley Pond Regional Monarch. He had always been very close with the Infernal Region and was one of the Infernal Region's chief supporters.

"There's no need to be concerned, Regional Monarch Tian Ku. We still have plenty of time," Yin Chengquan replied with a faint smile, and it seemed like he had everything under control.

A skeptical look appeared on Tian Ku's face upon seeing this, but he didn't say anything further.

Yin Chengquan leaned back in his chair as he lifted the teacup in front of him, yet right as his lips were about to make contact with the rim of the teacup, he communicated through voice transmission, "Proceed according to the original plan."

There were two people currently standing behind Yin Chengquan, one of whom was a young man with a pair of large eyes and bushy brows. Overall, his features were quite handsome, and there was a curved gray horn on his forehead.

The other person was a gray-robed man with a set of unremarkable facial features with the exception of his eyebrows which resembles a pair of sharp swords.

Both of them were giving off Great Encompassment Stage auras, and at this moment, a faint glimmer of gray light flashed within the sleeve of the horned young man.

In the crowd below the elevated platform was a tall and thin black-robed figure, and upon spotting the faint glimmer of gray light, he immediately turned and departed, quickly fading into the crowd.

Yin Chengquan took a subtle glance at the black-robed figure out of his peripheral vision, then set down the teacup in his hand.

Right at this moment, Xiao Buye smiled and said, "I must say, it's very impressive that you're still so calm and collected even with the current state of affairs, Regional Monarch Yin."

"Likewise, Deputy Regional Monarch Xiao. You seem to be just as composed as I am, if not more so," Yin Chengquan replied.

"I don't think that's a fair comparison, Regional Monarch Yin. All our Black Rope Region wants is for all of the regions to coexist in harmony, and we're satisfied as long as no further major internal conflicts take place. The only reason why I'm here is to ensure that this conference can have a peaceful conclusion," Xiao Buye said, making sure to emphasize the word "peaceful", as if he were issuing a subtle warning.

"I see. The Gray Realm is truly fortunate to have a peace-keeping force like yourself. You have my utmost admiration," Yin Chengquan said with a faint smile.

Huang Fuyu was listening to the conversation between the two, and he took a glance at the two of them before looking away again as a mocking sneer appeared on his face.

Meanwhile.

A burst of low chanting suddenly rang out from within a passageway inside the tall city wall on the border of the Fallen Lake Area.

There were gray stone pillars that were each over a hundred feet tall standing at set intervals along the dark passageway, and the pillars were riddled with complex patterns that extended out of the pillars and into the surrounding city wall.

Atop each pillar sat an Infernal being, all of whom were currently chanting incantations while casting incantation seals into the gray pillars.

The patterns on the stone pillars quickly began to flash with gray light that was interspersed with specks of silver light, which were particularly eye-catching in the dark passageway.

The bursts of gray light grew brighter and brighter as they quickly connected together, and it was clear that this city wall was constructed from some type of special material, as evidenced by the fact that none of the flashing lights seeped outside.

The restrictions around the Fallen Lake Area slowly began to change as specks of silver light emerged within them.

Chapter 752: Surprising Turn

As the commencement of the decision stage drew closer, the conference venue gradually began to quiet down, and everyone turned their attention to the three figures seated at the head of the table.

Right at this moment, Xiao Buye abruptly raised his head to inspect his surroundings, and Huang Fuyu's expression also changed slightly.

"What's wrong, Palace Master Huang?" Wyrm 3 immediately asked.

All of the other regional monarchs had also noticed the changes in Xiao Buye and Huang Fuyu's expressions, and the tension in the air only became heavier.

All of a sudden, Huang Fuyu rose to his feet as a layer of radiant white light emerged over his body, and he glowered intently at Yin Chengquan as he asked, "What's the meaning of this, Regional Monarch Yin?"

As soon as Huang Fuyu rose to his feet, all of the regional monarchs who were allied to the Reincarnation Region immediately followed suit, and some of the more aggressive ones among them had even summoned immortal treasures in preparation for battle.

Xiao Buye hadn't risen to his feet, but he was also glowering intently at Yin Chengquan with an accusatory look in his eyes.

In the face of the rapidly escalating tensions, Yin Changquan remained calm and silent.

However, all of the regional monarchs allied to the Infernal Region had stood up to oppose those allied to the Reincarnation Region.

"This is the Three Region Conference! Is your Reincarnation Region trying to rebel?" Tian Ku accused in a scathing manner.

"Rebel? Are you implying that the Infernal Region is the ruler of the Gray Realm? What a joke!" Xiao Buye scoffed in a cold voice.

Tian Ku knew that he had misspoken, and he had no response to this.

Yin Chengquan remained seated as he took a glance at Huang Fuyu and Xiao Buye, then said, "What's going on all of a sudden, everyone? The decision stage is about to commence, and we're going to be deciding the future fate of our Gray Realm. Why have we suddenly all taken up arms against each other at a time like this?"

"Do you take us for fools, Regional Monarch Yin? You've activated spatial restrictions all around the Fallen Lake Area to isolate this place from the outside world. What is the meaning of this?" Huang Fuyu asked in a cold voice.

Only then did everyone finally understand what had just happened, and the entire conference venue erupted into chatter as everyone turned their attention to Yin Chengquan.

In the face of everyone's hostile scrutiny, Yin Chengquan remained calm and collected, and a faint smile had even appeared on his face.

At this point, all of the preparations were complete, so it hardly mattered that he had been caught.

After plotting for so long, he could finally enact his plan.

"Everyone..." Yin Chengquan began.

Right at this moment, an explosion rang out in the distance, and a tremendous evil aura erupted into the heavens before proliferating outward in all directions.

At the same time, an enormous ball of black light had also emerged from the epicenter of the explosion, and all of the baleful qi near Asura City was churning violently as rumbling thunderclaps rang out above the swirling gray clouds overhead.

Even the three dim suns in the sky were beginning to undergo a change as they were approaching each other, even overlapping in some parts, but they hadn't completely overlapped yet.

Furthermore, they were glowing far brighter than usual, and rays of bright gray light were emanating from the three suns before flowing rapidly down into the ball of black light in the distance like rivers flowing into the sea.

Everyone at the conference venue, including the bystanders below the elevated platform, were all looking at the ball of black light with alarmed expressions, and Huang Fuyu and Xiao Buye's expressions also changed drastically upon seeing this.

A hint of surprise also flashed through Yin Chengquan's eyes upon seeing this, but he then quickly improvized, "That's our city's Soul Cleansing Area, which is home to many of our treasure refinement and puppet refinement facilities. Some type of mishap must've taken place, leading to the activation of the spatial restrictions of the Fallen Lake Area.

“These are just prophylactic measures that our Infernal Region has taken to ensure the smooth running of the conference, so don't be alarmed, everyone."

Skeptical looks immediately appeared on many people’s faces upon hearing this, but the tension in the air had deescalated significantly.

The white light around Huang Fuyu's body faded, and he also gestures for all of the Reincarnation Region's allies to stow away their immortal treasures.

All of the Infernal Region's allies also followed suit upon seeing this.

Xiao Buye took a glance in the direction of the Soul Cleansing Area, then turned back to Yin Chengquan, and there was still some suspicion in his eyes, but it wasn't as apparent as before.

"Go and see what's happened, then take care of it as soon as possible," Yin Chengquan said to the two Great Encompassment cultivators behind him.

The two of them gave an affirmative response, then flew toward the Soul Cleansing Area as two streaks of black light.

"My apologies for the delay, everyone. I hereby declare the recommencement of the conference," Yin Chengquan said as he sat down.

Everyone exchanged some glances with one another, then sat down as well, but it was clear that everyone was still a little shaken, and no one said anything.

Wyrm 3 took a step forward, then asked through voice transmission, "Do you think Yin Chengquan was telling the truth just now, Palace Master Huang?"

"Of course Yin Chengquan is not to be trusted. He definitely has some type of ulterior motive for activating the spatial restrictions around the Fallen Lake Area, but that explosion was also rather strange. If I'm not mistaken, something most likely really has gone wrong in the Soul Cleansing Area," Huang Fuyu replied with a cold sneer.

"You've always been the head of our Reincarnation Palace's brains trust, Palace Master Huang. Have you managed to guess Yin Chengquan's plan?" Wu Yang asked.

"You're far too kind, Palace Master Wu Yang. My tactical nous can't even begin to compare with that of our regional monarch. Right now, I don't have enough leads to fully extrapolate what Yin Chengquan's plan could be," Huang Fuyu replied.

"What should we do then? Do we just stay here?" Wyrm 3 asked.

"There's no need to be concerned. Our regional monarch has already predicted that Yin Chengquan will be up to no good during this Three Region Conference, and he's already made preparations in advance, so let's just watch and see for now," Huang Fuyu replied.

Wyrm 3 and Wu Yang's eyes both lit up slightly upon hearing this, and they didn't say anything further.

......

In the underground palace in the Soul Cleansing Area.

Both Yin Xu and Gui Mu were staring at the giant arm and gargantuan head of the Kun Hou with deathly pale complexions.

Gui Mu took a deep breath, then took a glance at Han Li and the others, who were fleeing the scene, and he asked, "Elder Yin Xu, should we capture those people? Maybe if we take them to the regional monarch, that'll spare us from some punishment."

"It's almost time for our regional monarch to enact his plan, yet we've completely messed up! Do you really think catching a few rats will be enough to spare us from punishment? The only silver lining here is that the Kun Hou hasn't been completely freed yet. Our top priority right now is to contain it, then wait for reinforcements to arrive!" Yin Xu spat through gritted teeth, then flew directly upward while making a string of hand seals.

A streak of black light flew out of his body, then transformed into a black badge.

The badge appeared to be quite similar to the infernal badge, except there were nine ghostly heads engraved onto this one.

Yin Xu opened his mouth to expel several balls of blood essence into the badge, and it immediately began to glow radiantly with black spiritual light.

At the same time, the nine ghostly heads swelled to several times their original size before opening their mouths in unison, releasing nine bursts of black light that vanished into the nearby space in a flash.

Numerous red chains shot out of the nearby space, then wrapped themselves around the Kun Hou's arm and head.

However, these chains summoned by Yin Xu were clearly far thinner than the ones already around the Kun Hou's body.

Meanwhile, Gui Mu took another glance at Han Li, seemingly still rather reluctant to let them get away.

The flames within the Kun Hou's eye flared up as it swung its arm through the air again, releasing a burst of tremendous force that caused the nearby space to tremble violently.

A string of loud clangs rang out as most of the chains summoned by Yin Xu were instantly snapped.

Yin Xu's complexion instantly paled significantly as he threw up a mouthful of blood, then turned to Gui Mu as he yelled in a furious voice, "What the hell are you doing, Gui Mu?! Hurry up and help me!"

Gui Mu didn't dare to hesitate any longer, and he immediately flew over to Yin Xu's side before releasing two thick beams of light out of the palms of his hands and into Yin Xu's body.

Yin Xu's complexion instantly improved slightly, and he made a rapid string of hand seals, upon which more chains flew out of the black badge before wrapping themselves around the Kun Hou's body.

Han Li was ecstatic to see this from another corner of the hall, and he immediately flew toward the black vine cage that Weeping Soul was trapped in.

At the same time, the Profound Heavenly Gourd appeared in front of him, then immediately began to radiate bright green light.

As Han Li chanted an incantation while making a rapid string of hand seals, the green light radiating from the gourd grew even brighter, while the gourd itself swelled to several times its original, and rows of green runes appeared on its surface.

Gui Mu was curious to see this.

The entirety of Asura City was most likely on high alert at this point, so it didn't matter if he allowed Han Li and the others to get away for now as they would eventually just be captured again, but he couldn't allow You Luo to go with him.

With that in mind, Gui Mu let loose a low roar, and eight black talismans flew out of his body, then transformed into eight giant spiked mace-like weapons.

A tremendous evil law aura was emanating from these weapons, and every single one of them was no less formidable as a graded immortal treasure.

The eight giant weapons shot forth toward Han Li, and at the same time, the black cage around Weeping Soul rose up from the ground before flying toward Gui Mu and Yin Xu.

Instead of being dismayed by this turn of events, Han Li's eyes lit up as his Mantra Treasured Axis appeared behind him amid a flash of golden light.

The axis released countless golden ripples that encompassed the eight giant weapons, and they were instantly slowed down, but they were imbued with such tremendous power that the entire area of golden ripples immediately began to tremble violently, looking as if it could fall apart at any moment.

Chapter 753: Four-colored Lightning Restriction

Han Li paid no heed to this as he cast a rapid string of incantation seals into the Profound Heavenly Gourd, which lit up even further before releasing a vast expanse of green light that enveloped the eight giant weapons before rapidly revolving to form a green vortex.

The black light emanating from the weapons quickly faded, and in the blink of an eye, they had reverted back into eight black talismans.

Immediately thereafter, the green light shot back into the Profound Heavenly Gourd in a flash, carrying the eight black talismans along with it.

Gui Mu faltered slightly upon seeing this, while Han Li continued to cast more incantation seals into the Profound Heavenly Gourd, and a string of faint cracks quickly rang out within it.

In the next instant, a tremendous burst of translucent black light shot out of the mouth of the gourd before striking the black cage of vines with incredible speed.

A burst of immense law power fluctuations erupted out of the black light, and the cage of vines was sliced into two with ease, while Weeping Soul fell out of the sky.

At this moment, she appeared to be in terrible condition. Her entire body was riddled with holes, which seemed to have been inflicted by the ghost vines, and she was covered in blood.

Han Li appeared beside her in a flash, then caught her before immediately darting back in retreat.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and by the time Gui Mu finally reacted to what had just happened, Han Li had already fled with Weeping Soul.

He was both alarmed and furious to see this, and there was also a hint of greed in his eyes as he gazed upon the Profound Heavenly Gourd.

The giant weapons sealed in the eight talismans were once called Profound Heaven Shattering Maces, and they were a set of fifth-grade immortal treasures refined by a peak-Great Encompassment cultivator.

By the time he came into possession of them, they were already on the verge of destruction, and he used a Gray Realm secret technique to draw out their final law powers before sealing them into talismans.

Those eight talismans had taken care of countless formidable foes for him, and even though there wasn't much power in them left, it was still extraordinary that the Profound Heavenly Gourd had been able to instantly destroy them before unleashing an attack with the law powers that they contained.

Such an incredible Profound Heavenly Treasure was something that he had never even heard of!

Right at this moment, the Kun Hou let loose another thunderous roar, and countless bursts of black karmic fire surged out of its arm and head like fiery black pythons, rapidly melting away the chains around its body.

Yin Xu and Gui Mu hurriedly injected more power into the black badge upon seeing this, and the nine ghostly heads on the badge swelled drastically in size once again, while the nine red chains around the Kun Hou's body also became several times thicker.

However, before the two of them even had a chance to heave a sigh of relief, all of the karmic flames suddenly surged out of the Kun Hou's body, while the nine red chains snapped in unison. Immediately thereafter, the karmic fire formed a giant fiery black hand that came crashing down upon them.

The space near the fiery black hand was crackling and popping incessantly from the intense heat, and in response, Yin Xu conjured what appeared to be a giant black eye.

A streak of swordlight erupted out of the pupil of the eye to strike the center of the fiery black hand, and the streak of swordlight exploded upon contact, but the black hand was also stopped momentarily in its tracks, only to immediately continue crashing down with tremendous power.

After unleashing the giant eye ability, Yin Xu immediately grabbed onto Gui Mu before darting away to the side, and the two of them were only just barely able to evade the fiery black hand.

The giant hand fell upon a certain point in the underground space, but there was no violent explosions, as one would expect. Instead, the spot that was struck melted away instantly, creating a giant crater that was tens of thousands of feet deep.

At this point, Han Li had already taken advantage of the chaos to flee far away, and all of a sudden, he noticed something at the deepest part of the crater with his Infernal Devilish Eyes.

"Come with me!"

His voice rang out in the minds of Fox 3 and Shi Chuankong in unison, and the two of them only hesitated slightly before following Han Li deep into the crater.

As soon as they flew into the crater, bursts of thunderous rumbling rang out from outside once again, and it seemed that the battle between the Kun Hou and Yin Xu's duo had resumed.

"Why did you lead us in here, Fellow Daoist Li? We'll be safe in here for now, but there's no way out, and that puts us at risk of being trapped," Fox 3 said as he turned to Han Li with a puzzled expression.

Han Li offered no response as he held Weeping Soul in one arm while injecting his immortal spiritual power into her body to aid in her recovery.

At the same time, he released a streak of azure sword qi with his other hand, which sliced forcefully into the scorching wall of the crater.

A large section of the rock face was instantly sliced away to reveal a black tunnel.

An ecstatic look appeared on Shi Chuankong's face upon seeing this.

Many parts of the earth under Asura City had been dug out to create many underground spaces, and the Kun Hou's attack had pierced so deep into the earth that it had inadvertently connected this underground space to another.

"Let's get out of here. At this point, I'm sure the entire city's attention must've already been drawn here, so there will most likely be other Great Encompassment cultivators arriving on the scene very soon," Han Li said in an urgent manner, then led the way into the black tunnel.

Fox 3 and Shi Chuankong immediately followed along, and after entering the tunnel, the latter swept his left hand through the air to release a burst of white flames, which vanished into the nearby rock face, melting it once again so that it blocked the entrance to the tunnel.

After that, the three of them sped onward as quickly as they could.

This was quite a spacious black tunnel, one that was around seventy to eighty feet tall, and the rock faces on either side were riddled with what appeared to be some type of sealing runes.

However, it was completely dark up ahead, and spiritual sense was still severely restricted here, so they had no idea where this tunnel led to.

"There's not going to be something else sealed up ahead, is there?" Shi Chuankong murmured to himself.

"Just a single Kun Hou is enough to keep the Infernal Tribe busy. If we release another, the entire Gray Realm will be plunged into chaos!" Fox 3 chuckled.

"I'm already completely spent after undoing the previous seal, so even if we run into another seal, I won't be able to do anything about it," Shi Chuankong replied with a wry smile.

Right at this moment, a hint of purple light flashed through Han Li's eyes, following which an elated look appeared on his face, and he abruptly accelerated, speeding onward as a streak of azure light.

Fox 3 and Shi Chuankong immediately picked up the pace as well, and before long, the two of them had emerged from the tunnel into another giant hall.

At the deepest point of the hall was a stone gate with lights of different colors flashing over it. On the very outside was a radiant silver light barrier that was giving off spatial fluctuations, and it was almost identical to the seal that they had just broken, except on this occasion, there was a four-colored lightning restriction beyond the silver light barrier.

The four colors of lightning were azure, purple, silver, and gold, and they were giving off tremendous lightning law power fluctuations.

Among them, the golden lightning was none other than Bone Rinsing Golden Lightning!

"This is Bone Rinsing Golden Lightning! Could it be that the Baleful Cleansing Pond is what's sealed in here?" Shi Chuankong exclaimed with an ecstatic expression.

A hint of elation also flashed through Fox 3's eyes, followed by a mixture of other emotions.

"We'll have to count on you again to break the spatial restriction here, Fellow Daoist Shi," Han Li said.

"This spatial restriction is the same as the one from before, so I shouldn't have any trouble with it, given my earlier experience," Shi Chuankong said as he swept a sleeve through the air to release a series of silver array flags.

The array flags circled around in the air momentarily before forming several arrays at his behest, all of which slowly vanished into the silver light barrier.

Fox 3 couldn't provide any assistance, so he stood off to the side to keep a lookout for any potential pursuers.

As for Han Li, he laid Weeping Soul down onto the ground, then made a rapid string of hand seals to release several green talismans, all of which vanished into her body.

Countless thin strands of green light emerged from her wounds before intertwining with one another, and those wounds began to rapidly heal.

At the same time, Han Li flicked a finger through the air to release a black pill that carried several translucent crimson marks, and it flew straight into Weeping Soul's slightly agape mouth.

A ball of black light emerged over her lower abdomen, then quickly spread over her entire body, and her feeble aura began to quickly recover.

Just a few seconds later, her brows furrowed slightly, following which she slowly opened her eyes, but her complexion was still very pale.

"Master..."

She struggled up into a seated position as she looked up at Han Li with a grateful expression, and she was just about to say something when Han Li interjected, "Focus on refining the pill in your body that I just fed you first."

Weeping Soul nodded in response, then sat down with her legs crossed, while Han Li joined Fox 3 on lookout duty.

Thankfully, the tunnel that they had just passed through remained completely silent, and neither Gui Mu nor Yin Xu had come after them.

Meanwhile, Shi Chuankong was working as quickly as he could, and the array flags around him were piercing into the silver light barrier at a far faster rate than last time.

He took a deep breath, then summoned the Virata Lute amid a flash of silver light, and his fingers flew rapidly over the lute's strings to fill the entire space with solemn and urgent music.

The nearby space trembled before shattering altogether, and it was clear that Shi Chuankong now had far better control over the Virata Lute than before.

Bursts of silver light flew out of the lute with each strum of its strings, and all of the bursts of silver light vanished into the silver light barrier, rapidly whittling it down until there was only a thin layer left.

However, this final layer of the light barrier was extremely resilient, and it displayed no signs of giving way.

A sharp gleam flashed through Shi Chuankong's eyes as he forcefully strummed the strings of his lute five times, and five bursts of silver light shot forth before transforming into five silver sword projections.

Immense law power fluctuations were emanating from the silver sword projections, and they struck the silver light barrier in a flash.

A resounding boom rang out as the light barrier was finally unable to hold itself together any longer, disintegrating into countless specks of silver light.

Shi Chuankong was looking rather pale, clearly indicating that the ability that he had just unleashed had been quite taxing on him, but thankfully, his efforts had paid off.

After heaving a sigh of relief, he turned to call upon Han Li and Fox 3, but right at this moment, things took an unexpected turn...

Chapter 754: Heavenly Fox Patriarch

All of as sudden, the four-colored lightning restriction on the stone gate began to rumble violently while releasing a terrifying aura of destruction.

Four bolts of lightning that were as thick as water vats erupted out of the array, with each one a different color, and all of them hurtled directly toward Shi Chuankong.

Each bolt of lightning was giving off incredibly fearsome lightning law power fluctuations, and this turn of events had clearly caught Shi Chuankong off guard.

He immediately tried to dart back in retreat, but it was already too late, and the four bolts of lightning were on the verge of striking him.

Right at this moment, Han Li's Profound Heavenly Gourd abruptly appeared in front of him, and a burst of green light erupted out from within before sweeping up the four bolts of lightning, causing them to slow down significantly.

The four bolts of lightning struggled with all their might within the green light, but were unable to free themselves.

In the next instant, Han Li appeared beside the Profound Heavenly Gourd before laying a palm down onto it, and the four bolts of lightning instantly began to shrink down rapidly before being sucked into the gourd along with the burst of green light.

Inside the second internal space of the gourd, four balls of lightning had emerged, each of which was around the size of a prayer bead, and they were giving off formidable lightning law power fluctuations that weren't inferior to those of a graded immortal treasure.

Han Li was very pleased to see this. Having recently used the Profound Heavenly Gourd on several occasions, he had already used up most of the law powers stored within it, so these four balls of lightning had come at just the right time.

"Thank you, Fellow Daoist Li," Shi Chuankong said in a grateful voice as he heaved a sigh of relief.

"There's no need to thank me, Fellow Daoist Shi. Let's go in," Han Li said as he stowed the Profound Heavenly Gourd away.

"Brother Fox, Fellow Daoist Weeping Soul, we can go in now," Shi Chuankong called out.

Fox 3 immediately flew over to Han Li and Shi Chuankong upon hearing this, as did Weeping Soul.

Some color had returned to her cheeks, and she was looking in much better condition than before.

Shi Chuankong strummed his fingers over his lute to release more streaks of silver light, which landed on the ground to form a silver array, and the group vanished from within the array shortly thereafter.

Han Li's entire field of view was filled with radiant silver light, preventing him from being able to see anything else, but the silver light quickly faded, restoring his vision to normal.

Han Li looked around to discover that they were currently situated in a giant square hall, the ground and walls of which were all paved with some type of glowing white crystal.

The hall was enormous, standing at tens of thousands of feet tall and over a hundred thousand feet wide.

At the center of the hall were four square ponds that were roughly a thousand feet each, and each pond was a different color, namely azure, purple, silver, and gold.

Furthermore, the four ponds were filled with thick arcs of lightning, all of which were churning violently like furious dragons amid rumbling thunderclaps, presenting an awe-inspiring sight to behold.

There were some extremely complex array patterns engraved onto the ground, and they spanned the entire hall to form a highly complex array.

Occasionally, an arc of lightning would spring out of one of the four ponds, but whenever this happened, bursts of white mist would surge out of the surrounding array patterns to contain the escaping lightning.

However, what was most astonishing to Han Li and the others was that there was an enormous wooden cross on the ground at the center of the four lightning ponds.

Seated atop the wooden cross was an enormous white fox with nine tails resting feebly on the ground behind it.

There were four thick chains wrapped several times around the giant fox's body, binding it firmly to the cross, and the four chains were also azure, purple, silver, and gold in color.

Furthermore, arcs of lightning were constantly flashing over the chains, and it looked as if they had been formed by lightning.

One end of the chains was plunged into the fox's dantian, while the other end was connected to the bottom of the four lightning ponds, and all four were stretched taut.

Even though the giant fox was completely bound to the cross, it was still giving off an unfathomably powerful aura, making everyone feel as if they were standing before a primordial deity.

Right at this moment, the fox slowly opened its eyes to reveal a pair of light gray pupils, and a hint of surprise appeared on its face at the sight of Han Li's group.

"You're from the True Immortal Realm... How did you get into this place?"

"Who are you?" Han Li asked.

Right at this moment, Fox 3's excited voice suddenly rang out from beside him.

"You're Patriarch Liu Qi! I've finally found you! Ninth-generation disciple Liu San of the Heavenly Fox Race pays his respects to Patriarch Liu Qi!"

He flew over to the giant fox, doing so in such a hurry that he left a string of afterimages in his wake, then fell to his knees with an extremely excited look on his face.

Both Han Li and Shi Chuankong were rather bewildered to see this.

"I never thought that I'd see a member of the Heavenly Fox Race in the Gray Realm. How are things back home?" the giant fox asked.

"Everything is fine, but in the wake of your sudden disappearance all those years ago, our race was dealt a heavy blow, and we lost a lot of our territory," Fox 3 replied in a respectful manner.

The giant fox's expression eased slightly upon hearing this, and he asked, "How is Liu Qing right now?"

Fox 3 took a hesitant glance at Han Li and the others, but ultimately still revealed, "Our chief has already severed two corpse souls and reached the late-Great Encompassment Stage."

"That's not too bad," the giant fox mused with a nod.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged, but internally, he was stunned upon hearing this conversation.

It seemed that Fox 3 and this giant fox had both come from the Heavenly Fox Race, which was one of the most prominent powers in the primordial land between the Northern Glacial Immortal Region and the Black Mountain Immortal Region.

As for this Chief Liu Qing, that was most likely the white-robed Great Encompassment cultivator of the Heavenly Fox Race that he had encountered.

At the moment, Liu Le'er was cultivating in the Heavenly Fox Race, and it seemed like his fate was going to continue to be entangled with the Heavenly Fox Race.

Given the unfathomable aura emanating from Liu Qi's body, Han Li could sense that he was a Dao Ancestor, and he couldn't help but wonder how an almighty Dao Ancestor had ended up being imprisoned here in the Gray Realm.

"You have decent aptitude, considering you've already reached the High Zenith Stage at your age. Judging from what you just said, it sounds like you were looking for me. Did you know that I was in the Gray Realm?" Liu Qi asked.

"Ever since your disappearance, Chief Liu Qing has constantly been sending out people to search for you, and I was one of them. I joined the Reincarnation Palace by chance, and from there, I learned that you could be in the Gray Realm, so I found a way to come here, and here you are!" Fox 3 explained with an ecstatic expression.

Patriarch Liu Qi raised an eyebrow upon hearing this, and a peculiar look flashed through his eyes as he remained silent.

The change in his expression hadn't failed to escape Han Li's attention, and he could tell that Patriarch Liu Qi seemed to be hiding something.

"What happened to you all those years ago, esteemed patriarch? How did you end up here?" Fox 3 asked.

"I'll tell you about that some other time. For now, answer me this: how did you manage to get into this restricted area? This is where the Infernal Tribe's four Baleful Cleansing Ponds are situated," Liu Qi asked.

Han Li's heart stirred slightly upon hearing this. It seemed that by some miraculous stroke of luck, they had made it to their destination, and Shi Chuankong was also ecstatic to hear this.

After taking a glance at Han Li and the others, Fox 3 gave Liu Qi a brief recount of the time that they had spent in the Gray Realm and how they had managed to get here.

"I see, the Three Region Conference does present a slim window of opportunity that can be exploited. However, right now, the entirety of Asura City is definitely already in a state of lockdown, so there's no way any of you will be able to escape," Liu Qi said.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong's expressions darkened slightly upon hearing this, and the latter looked down at his Virata Lute with slightly furrowed brows.

He had already tried to use the lute to conjure up a long-distance teleportation array to teleport himself out of Asura City, but the spatial restrictions around the city completely foiled those plans.

"There's no way we'll be able to escape on our own, but as long as we can free you, I'm sure you'll be able to take us out of Asura City with your unmatched power!" Fox 3 said.

"You want to free me? I'm afraid that's much easier said than done. These four Lightning Entrapment Chains were personally created by Yin Chengquan, and they've sealed away my immortal spiritual power and law powers. Unless they can be severed, there's no way for me to escape," Liu Qi replied.

"Please bear with me for a moment, esteemed patriarch. My cultivation base may be nothing worthy of note, but I have some tricks up my sleeve," Fox 3 said as he stepped forward with a confident expression.

Liu Qi's eyes narrowed slightly upon seeing this, but he didn't say anything.

Han Li was just about to urge Fox 3 to proceed with caution, but he chose not to, seeing as even Liu Qi hadn't said anything.

Fox 3 strode forward before flipping a hand over to summon a silver longsword that was riddled with runes.

As soon as the sword emerged, bursts of rippling swordlight immediately began to spread through the air around it, and judging from the law power fluctuations that it was giving off, it had to have been at least a sixth-grade immortal treasure.

Chapter 755: Third-grade Immortal Treasure?

Shi Chuankong's eyes immediately lit up at the sight of the sword, and Han Li's gaze also lingered on it momentarily, but most of his attention was still focused on Fox 3.

At this moment, Fox 3 was a little different in appearance compared to his usual self. Layers of hemispherical light had appeared around him like layers of illusions, giving him a rather indistinct appearance.

After observing Fox 3 for only a short while, Han Li felt a throbbing pain in his eyes, and he couldn't help but massage his own glabella.

Right at this moment, a shimmering golden talisman appeared between the tips of the index and middle fingers of his left hand.

Han Li took a glance at the talisman, and a hint of befuddlement flashed through his eyes. He could sense that the talisman was brimming with spiritual power that was on the verge of overflowing, but he didn't recognize it.

"Is that... a Golden Spirit Gathering Sword Talisman?" Shi Chuankong exclaimed in a surprised voice.

However, Fox 3 seemed to have entered some type of profound state of immersion, and he didn't hear Shi Chuankong at all. He was carrying many injuries, and it was clear that he wasn't faking his condition, but at this moment, his aura was steadily climbing, and he was almost back to his peak condition.

"What is this Golden Spirit Gathering Sword Talisman, Fellow Daoist Shi?" Han Li asked.

"It's a type of talisman that can drastically enhance the power of an immortal sword for a short time, and the effectiveness of the talisman varies depending on the material used. That golden talisman is a premium talisman, and it's no exaggeration to say that it's a priceless treasure," Shi Chuankong explained.

Right at this moment, Fox 3 suddenly waved the talisman in his left hand through the air, then adhered it firmly to the blade of his sword, and the talisman instantly erupted into golden flames.

A golden rune that was around half a foot in length appeared on the silver longsword within the golden flames, and the sword instantly began to tremble violently, while the spiritual power fluctuations that it was giving off became ten times more formidable.

With this sudden change, the immortal sword had almost been elevated to the level of a fifth-grade immortal treasure.

At the same time, around a dozen giant projections of Fox 3 appeared all around him, each of which was several thousand feet tall and was wielding an enlarged version of the same silver sword, and as he took a step forward, all of the projections also stepped forward with him.

Liu Qi's eyes lit up slightly upon seeing this.

With a thunderous roar from Fox 3, all of the projections raised their swords in unison before sending them crashing down upon the azure chain in unison.

A sharp clang rang out as a burst of bright swordlight erupted from the azure chain, flooding the entire area with blinding radiance.

Gusts of ferocious wind swept through the air in all directions from the point where the sword was grating against the chain, causing the robes of Han Li and the others to flap audibly.

"Such incredible sword qi!" Shi Chuankong couldn't help but praise as he raised a hand in front of himself for cover.

Weeping Soul was still yet to recover from her injuries, so she was forced to stay back and watch from afar.

Han Li also took half a step backward, and at the same time, he heaved a forlorn internal sigh.

He had noticed that despite the tremendous power of Fox 3's sword strike, the chain that it had struck remained virtually completely unmoved.

Right at this moment, a burst of dull rumbling rang out from within the azure Baleful Cleansing Pond, immediately following which a bolt of azure lightning erupted out of the pond, then surged along the azure chain to reach Fox 3 in the blink of an eye.

In the instant that the bolt of azure lightning struck the radiant swordlight released by Fox 3's silver longsword, the latter instantly exploded into countless fragments.

An enormous ball of lightning appeared within the shattered remnants of the swordlight, and Fox 3 was trapped within it, unable to free himself as arcs of lightning ravaged his body from all directions, causing him to tremble violently while letting loose a string of agonized howls.

Massive arcs of azure lightning were constantly erupting out of the ball of lightning, causing the surrounding space to rumble and quiver, and a charred odor was quickly spreading through the air. This lightning was countless times more powerful than even the tribulation lightning that Han Li had endured to ascend to the True Immortal Realm.

An alarmed look appeared on Shi Chuankong's face upon seeing this, and he wanted to lend Fox 3 his assistance, but he had no idea how.

Weeping Soul's brows furrowed slightly as she turned to Han Li, who was, in turn, observing Patriarch Liu Qi.

Liu Qi was still in a crouched position, and arcs of azure lightning were being transmitted along the azure chain before striking his body, causing his fur to stand up on end, but he didn't seem to be in any pain at all.

His eyes habitually narrowed slightly, and he wasn't displaying much surprise or disappointment in response to Fox 3's failed attempt to free him. All of a sudden, he raised one of his giant tails, then swept it through the air before wrapping it around the azure chain.

Immediately thereafter, a burst of azure light rose up around him alongside an incredibly violent aura, and the tail wrapped around the chain was lifted up even higher, hoisting the entire chain up into the air.

The tail then came plummeting down out of the sky, and the azure chain shuddered violently as a ball of dense black light shot out of Liu Qi's tail before hurtling toward the giant ball of azure lightning.

Both the black light and the ball of lightning exploded in unison upon contact, and arcs of azure lightning and specks of black light erupted forth in all directions alongside ferocious shockwaves, causing the surrounding space to tremble violently.

Han Li and the others immediately flew back in retreat while conjuring up layers of protective spiritual light around themselves, but their efforts proved to be unnecessary as Liu Qi raised another one of his massive tails, positioning it in front of them to shield them from the oncoming shockwaves.

Only after close to a minute had passed did the sound of the howling wind gradually subside. At this point, the azure lightning and black light had already faded, and everything had returned to normal.

Liu Qi slowly withdrew his tail, then carried Fox 3 over to Han Li and the others with another one of his tails.

At this moment, Fox 3's robes were in tatters, and many parts of his body had been charred black. It appeared his injuries were quite severe, but in reality, they were only minor external injuries. In contrast, the silver longsword in his hand had dimmed significantly, looking as if it had sustained some rather serious damage.

"Thank you for saving me, esteemed patriarch. It appears I overestimated my own abilities," Fox 3 said in an embarrassed manner as he extended a respectful bow.

"It's already very impressive that you were able to muster up such a powerful attack as a High Zenith cultivator, but you were too hasty and overconfident. I can see that you've managed to elevate that sixth-grade immortal sword into a faux fifth-grade immortal sword using that talisman of yours, but I can tell you now that even if you had a true fourth-grade immortal treasure, you still wouldn't have been able to severe this azure lightning chain," Liu Qi said.

Han Li was internally rather disgruntled to hear this. If Liu Qi knew in advance that Fox 3 wouldn't be able to sever the chain, then why didn't he stop him?

"Even a fourth-grade immortal treasure wouldn't be able to sever this chain?" Fox 3 asked in an astonished manner.

"That's right. The four chains in these Baleful Cleansing Ponds were crafted by the Infernal Tribe using many types of precious materials gathered from all over the Gray Realm and the Immortal Realm, and there are also many types of fortification runes inscribed upon them, allowing them to fuse perfectly with the Baleful Cleansing Ponds. Otherwise, they wouldn't have been able to trap me for so many years," Liu Qi explained.

"If a fourth-grade immortal treasure can't even sever these chains, then there's nothing that we can do," Shi Chuankong mused with slightly furrowed brows.

"At your current levels of power, you'll perhaps only be able to sever these chains by using an immortal treasure of the third grade or above," Liu Qi said as he swept his gaze over Han Li in a subtle manner.

A dismayed look instantly appeared on Fox 3's face upon hearing this.

"Even in the Immortal Realm, third-grade immortal treasures are exceedingly rare, and even the average Great Encompassment cultivator wouldn't be guaranteed to have one. Where are we supposed to find a treasure of that caliber in the Gray Realm?"

A hesitant look flashed through Shi Chuankong's eyes upon hearing this, and he looked as if he were about to say something, but ultimately decided against it in the end.

His Virata Lute was a third-grade immortal treasure, but it was extremely significant to the Devil Race, so he chose not to offer it up.

Right at this moment, Liu Qi's gaze returned to Han Li, and he said, "If you're looking for a third-grade immortal treasure, then you don't have to look any further than this friend of yours here. Would you be willing to lend me your power?"

Han Li was very surprised and befuddled to hear this, and he didn't know if the third-grade immortal treasure that Liu Qi was referring to was the golden plate that he had obtained from the True Mantra Sect, the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber, or his Heaven Controlling Vial.

He could narrow it down to these three as they were the only three treasures in his possession that were completely unfathomable to him.

Before Han Li had a chance to say anything, Fox 3's eyes lit up with elation as he declared, "It has to be that strange saber of yours, Brother Li! Please lend us your assistance. Our Heavenly Fox Race will be sure to compensate you handsomely!"

Han Li heaved an internal sigh as he attempted to contact Shi Qinghou with his spiritual sense, but he received no response, and it was as if Shi Qinghou had gone into hibernation.

Hence, he could only manually summon the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber.

Liu Qi's eyes clearly lit up slightly at the sight of the saber, and he immediately declared, "That's precisely the treasure that I'm referring to."

"My apologies, Senior, but judging from the attempt that Fellow Daoist Fox 3 made just now, even with this Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber, I don't think I have any chance of severing this chain," Han Li said with an apologetic expression.

"Of course it would be impossible for you to sever this azure lightning chain with your own power alone," Liu Qi mused.

"Is there some type of external power that I can draw upon?" Han Li asked with a perplexed expression.

Chapter 756: Deal

"Any Golden Immortal can wield a third-grade immortal treasure, but a Golden Immortal possesses nowhere near enough immortal spiritual power to unleash the true power of such a formidable treasure. Hence, all of you will need to combine your immortal spiritual power into one to accomplish this," Liu Qi said.

A hesitant look appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this.

"Why are you still hesitating at a time like this, Brother Li? We've completely turned the Infernal Tribe against us just to get here. Even if we manage to eradicate ourselves of baleful qi in the Baleful Cleansing Ponds, we're completely cornered! Only by saving Patriarch Liu Qi can we possibly survive," Fox 3 hurriedly urged.

"You came all this way for the Baleful Cleansing Ponds? I suppose that makes sense. Otherwise, for what other reason would True Immortal Realm cultivators like yourself have ventured so deep into Asura City? Having said that, do you know the perils of the Baleful Cleansing Ponds?" Liu Qi asked.

"Please enlighten us, esteemed patriarch," Fox 3 implored.

"You saw the power of the azure lightning chain just now, right? That was nothing more than the power drawn out by the runes on the Lightning Entrapment Chains. The true ponds themselves are hundreds of times more inhospitable. Pardon me for being frank, but if you enter the ponds as you currently are, you'll be killed long before you can cleanse your bodies of baleful qi," Liu Qi explained.

Han Li cast a wary gaze toward the lightning ponds upon hearing this, and at the same time, he became even more wary of Patriarch Liu Qi.

It was clear that he had intentionally refrained from stopping Fox 3 in his attempt to sever the chain, and that was most likely to show Han Li's group the true power of the lightning ponds so he could use that as leverage in the negotiations.

With that in mind, Han Li intentionally feigned a distraught expression as he exclaimed, "Doesn't that mean we risked our lives to come here for nothing?"

"Don't panic. I've been trapped here for quite some time now, and during this time, I've managed to gain a good understanding of these Baleful Cleansing Ponds. If I help you withstand a part of their power, then you'll be able to successfully cleanse yourselves of baleful qi in this azure lightning pond. However, in exchange, you have to help me sever these chains, what do you think?" Liu Qi proposed.

"That would naturally be best. Once we're cleansed of baleful qi, we'll be able to maximize the power of the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber, and that would increase our chances of severing the chain too," Han Li replied with a smile.

Shi Chuankong's eyes lit up slightly upon hearing this, and a faint smile appeared on his face.

"There's no need to be so wary of me, my intention was always for you to enter the Baleful Cleansing Pond before helping me sever these chains. These ponds are extremely perilous, but not only can they cleanse you of baleful qi, they can also refine your bodies to elevate your cultivation bases by different degrees," Patriarch Liu Qi chuckled.

At this point, Fox 3 had already changed into a black robe, and he paid no heed to his own injuries as he declared, "In that case, let's not delay any longer."

"We can't rush into this too quickly. Let's all take some pills, then meditate for an hour or two before we enter the Baleful Cleansing Pond," Han Li said with a shake of his head.

Fox 3 hesitated slightly upon hearing this, but ultimately still obliged.

Thus, the three of them sat down with their legs crossed before taking some pills.

As for Weeping Soul, she didn't fear baleful qi due to her special constitution, so she naturally didn't have to enter the Baleful Cleansing Pond. Hence, she was focused on resting and recuperating while thinking to herself how she was going to answer to Yin Chengquan.

Two hours flew by in a flash.

Fox 3 was the first one to open his eyes before rising to his feet, and Shi Chuankong and Han Li quickly followed suit.

Liu Qi was laying on the wooden cross as he said, "Out of these four lightning ponds, the azure one is the least powerful, but it's sufficient for cleansing the baleful qi in your bodies, so there's no need for you to venture into any of the other ponds."

Han Li's trio nodded in response, while Weeping Soul was looking at Han Li with a hint of concern in her eyes.

The three of them strode over to the edge of the azure lightning pond, and in order to avoid disrupting each other, each of them made their way to a different corner of the pond, then peered into the azure liquid inside, but none of them immediately stepped in.

After waiting for a moment, Han Li took a deep breath, then began to step into the pond.

However, he had only just raised his foot when he stopped in his tracks, then withdrew his foot before sweeping a sleeve through the air, conjuring up a door of silver light that led to the first floor of the bamboo building in the Flower Branch domain.

Earlier, Immortal Lord Hot Flame had been restrained by Shi Chuankong and Fox 3, but he had suddenly woken up, and he called out to Han Li, "Can you let me out, Fellow Daoist Li?"

"Glad to see you're lucid again, Fellow Daoist Hot Flame," Han Li said.

"This domain of yours can keep out baleful qi, and there's plenty of world's origin qi in here to nourish me, so I was able to regain my lucidity, but it's only temporary, so I contacted you right away in order to tell you some things," Immortal Lord Hot Flame said in an urgent voice.

"What do you need to tell me?" Han Li asked.

A pained look appeared on Immortal Lord Hot Flame's face, and a burst of baleful qi flashed over his glabella as he switched to voice transmission and said, "At this point, my body is too tainted by baleful qi for me to even dream of a recovery, but I don't want to be reduced to a mindless zombie, so I want you to put me out of my misery and into the cycle of reincarnation..."

Han Li was just about to cut him off when he continued, "All of my treasures were taken by the Infernal Tribe, and all that remains is the bonded treasure in my body, which you can have. Prior to that, I also want to pass my cultivation arts onto you. Our True Mantra Sect has already fallen, but its heritage must continue."

"Fellow Daiost Hot Flame, right now, we've already arrived at the Baleful Cleansing Ponds, in which it's possible for one to eradicate the baleful qi in their body, but the process is extremely risky. Would you be willing to give it a try?" Han Li asked.

"Really? Is there really a way to eradicate baleful qi here?" Immortal Lord Hot Flame hurriedly asked.

"I wouldn't lie to you about something like this. The Baleful Cleansing Ponds are real, but the risk involved is also very real," Han Li replied.

"Of course I'm going to give it a try!" Immortal Lord Hot Flame hurriedly said as an ecstatic look appeared on his face.

"Fellow Daoist Shi, Fellow Daoist Fox 3," Han Li called out as he turned to the duo, and the two of them quickly undid the restrictions in Immortal Lord Hot Flame's body.

After Immortal Lord Hot Flame staggered out of the domain, Han Li turned to Weeping Soul and asked, "Weeping Soul, can you remove the restrictions that the Infernal Tribe planted in his body?"

"I can do that, but if I do, the baleful qi in his body could erupt and drive him insane again," Weeping Soul replied in a hesitant manner.

"Go right ahead. If I lose my sanity, then please throw me straight into the Baleful Cleansing Pond, Fellow Daiost Li. If that happens, just leave me in the hands of fate," Immortal Lord Hot Flame said with a wry smile.

"Alright, in that case, I won't try to dissuade you," Han Li said.

"Thank you, fellow daoists," Immortal Lord Hot Flame said as he cupped his fist in a salute toward Han Li and Weeping Soul.

Han Li gave Weeping Soul a slight nod, and the latter began to work on removing the restrictions in Immortal Lord Hot Flame's body.

Initially, Immortal Lord Hot Flame's expression remained largely unchanged, but it didn't take long before his face became twisted with agony, and wisps of baleful qi began surging out of his body.

At this point, Immortal Lord Hot Flame's pupils had already almost turned completely gray, and Han Li realized that he had underestimated just how heavily contaminated by baleful qi Immortal Lord Hot Flame had become.

With a flick of his wrist, an Origin Separation Law Chain slid down his arm before trailing out of his sleeve.

Right at this moment, Weeping Soul brought her palms together in a strange hand seal before clasping her hands against Immortal Lord Hot Flame's back, and he immediately gave a muffled groan as blood trickled down from the corner of his lips.

Immediately thereafter, a string of cracks and pops rang out from all of the joints in his body, and it was as if he had suddenly grown by half a foot. Furthermore, dense baleful qi began to swirl around his entire body, and he looked no different from a Gray Immortal.

Han Li's brows furrowed tightly upon seeing this, and he was just about to intervene when a terribly raspy voice rang out from between Immortal Lord Hot Flame's lips.

"It's alright, Fellow Daoist Li, I can still hold on..."

He began to make his way toward a corner of the azure lightning pond as he spoke, then leaped into the pond without any hesitation before Han Li had a chance to stop him.

As soon as he jumped into the pond, the lightning within it instantly began to churn violently, like a pot of bubbling oil that had just had a drop of water spilt into it, and countless formidable arcs of lightning surged violently toward him.

Patriarch Liu Qi feigned a concerned look upon seeing this, but in reality, he held nothing but contempt for Immortal Lord Hot Flame, who he viewed as a reckless fool.

However, he immediately sprang into action, wrapping a tail around the azure chain once again before tugging it toward himself.

The lightning pond shuddered violently as the azure light within it became even brighter, and countless arcs of lightning began to surge along the chain toward Liu Qi, diverting most of the danger away from Immortal Lord Hot Flame.

All of a sudden, Liu Qi turned and opened his mouth to release a dark green ball roughly the size of a human head, and it released a green light barrier that kept the oncoming arcs of azure lightning at bay.

The arcs of azure lightning unleashed a ferocious barrage upon the green light barrier, but were unable to get through, and even though so much of the lightning had been diverted away by Liu Qi, the lightning that remained within the Baleful Cleansing Pond was still extremely formidable.

Chapter 757: Entering the Pond

Inside the lightning pond, Immortal Lord Hot Flame's face was twisted with agony as he let loose a blood-curdling howl.

Han Li and the others turned to discover that pillars of azure lightning were converging toward Immortal Lord Hot Flame from all directions before piercing straight through his body, giving him the appearance of an azure hedgehog.

His entire body was completely enveloped by azure lightning, and his robes were in tatters, while his exposed skin was also riddled with cracks and char marks.

At the same time, all of his immortal acupoints had involuntarily opened up, and tiny arcs of lightning were burrowing their way inside to stir up the baleful qi within.

The azure lightning had no regard for whether Immortal Lord Hot Flame's acupoints could withstand the influx of power as it burrowed its way deeper and deeper, and the baleful qi rose up to contend against it.

However, the lightning in this lightning pond was Bone Rinsing Golden Lightning, which was the natural bane of baleful qi, and thus, the baleful qi stood no chance and was quickly flushed out of Immortal Lord Hot Flame's immortal acupoints.

Countless plumes of black smoke were rising up from Immortal Lord Hot Flame's body in unison, giving him the appearance of a humanoid incense burner, presenting a very intriguing contrast with the riling lightning pond.

To Han Li's relief, he could see that Liu Qi really was helping them deal with the lightning pond, and he turned to Shi Chuankong and Fox 3 as he said, "Time is of the essence, so let's begin as well."

The two of them nodded in response, and they were just about to enter the lightning pond when they suddenly heard a guttural roar.

The three of them turned to discover Immortal Lord Hot Flame with his head thrown back with his fist clenched to the heavens, roaring in an animalistic fashion. Black baleful qi was surging incessantly out of all of his orifices, concealing his entire face and giving it an indistinct appearance.

However, there was no longer any more baleful qi surging out of his body, and bright red cracks that were giving off a scorching aura began to spread over his entire body.

All of a sudden, he erupted into flames, and in no more than an instant, his legs had been completely incinerated into ashes, sending his upper body tumbling into the lightning pond.

Han Li immediately sprang into action upon seeing this, channeling his Reversal True Axis ability as he sped over to the Baleful Cleansing Pond before making a grab for Immortal Lord Hot Flame.

"Save your energy. His body is already riddled with holes, and with the baleful qi gone, there's no way he can withstand the lightning in the pond," Liu Qi said in an indifferent voice.

Han Li paid no heed to this as he thrust his arms into the lightning pond to try and grab Immortal Lord Hot Flame.

As soon as his arms entered the pond, countless arcs of azure lightning instantly converged to pulverize his sleeves.

A burst of incredibly violent lightning power surged into his body, and the baleful qi in his body almost erupted into complete chaos on the spot.

Han Li immediately let loose a loud roar as he channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique to suppress the violent urges that had arisen in his heart, and at the same time, a layer of golden scales appeared over both of his arms.

However, just this split-second of delay was too much, and Immortal Lord Hot Flame's entire body had already been completely reduced to ashes.

Han Li cast his gaze upward before attempting to make a grab for Immortal Lord Hot Flame's nascent soul, but in the instant that his body was destroyed, his exposed nascent soul also exploded after being struck by several arcs of lightning.

In the end, Han Li was only able to catch a wisp of his soul.

All of this had taken place in the span of mere seconds, and by the time Fox 3 and Shi Chuankong had reacted to what had just happened, Han Li had already returned to them, then spread open his hand with a solemn expression.

Enshrouded within a layer of azure light on the palm of his hand was a tiny figure that was flickering like a feeble candle flame.

"I'm sorry, Fellow Daoist Hot Flame. There's nothing more I can do for you," Han Li sighed.

The remaining wisp of Immortal Lord Hot Flame's soul was so feeble that it was only able to communicate to Han Li through a spiritual connection, and it consoled, "Don't blame yourself, Fellow Daoist Li. This is what fate has in store for me..."

"This soul fragment of yours is too feeble to be preserved, and it won't be long before it dissipates, so if you have any final wishes, then tell them to me now," Han Li sighed.

"At this point, we've already ascertained the cause for the fall of the True Mantra Sect, and I'm too ashamed of my master to go and see him, so I no longer have any attachments in this world. It's just a pity that I won't be able to return to Leisure Valley. I wonder if this soul fragment of mine will be able to enter the cycle of reincarnation and return to the Immortal Lord Hot Flame someday," Immortal Lord Hot Flame sighed with a wry smile.

"The Heavenly Dao works in fickle and mysterious ways, so there's always a chance," Han Li replied.

"I was going to leave my bonded treasure to you, but the lightning pond was too powerful and eradicated everything, so this is all that I have to leave to you..."

As the soul fragment's voice trailed off, its soul fluctuations also gradually faded.

In the end, the soul fragment was reduced to a tiny speck of crimson light that drifted into Han Li's glabella.

Han Li felt a burst of heat in his consciousness, and he discovered that a passage of crimson text had appeared in his mind. It was the Time Severing Flowing Fire Tome, which was none other than the fire-attribute cultivation art passed down by the Flowing Fire Palace of the True Mantra Sect.

Han Li stood in a dazed manner in the wake of Immortal Lord Hot Flame's demise, and neither Fox 3 nor Shi Chuankong said anything.

Moments later, Han Li seemed to have returned to his senses, and he rubbed his hands together, then took a glance at the wounds on his arm that had been inflicted by the azure lightning as he heaved a faint sigh.

"Let's go in," he said.

A hesitant look appeared in Shi Chuankong's eyes after witnessing what had become of Immortal Lord Hot Flame, but Han Li was already flying toward a corner of the azure lightning pond, so he didn't hesitate any longer and followed along.

Once again, Liu Qi swept up the azure chain with one of his tails to attract the majority of the azure lightning to himself, and by the time Han Li descended into the lightning pond, it was already far less hostile than before.

Upon entering the pond, Han Li was initially struck by a numb and itchy sensation, but that was immediately followed by an intense, scorching pain, as if there were countless red-hot brands pressing against his skin at once, almost setting his skin and flesh alight.

He was able to suppress his cry of agony, but a muffled groan still slipped through his lips.

However, two blood-curdling howls had rung out in unison from two of the other corners of the lightning pond, with Fox 3 screaming particularly loud.

Han Li gritted his teeth tightly as cold sweat poured down his forehead, and he had to withstand the excruciating pain while suppressing the urge to ward off the infiltration of the azure lightning.

He knew that only by allowing more of the lightning to enter his body could he eradicate the baleful qi in his immortal acupoints as soon as possible.

Just a few seconds later, his skin had already turned bright red, and countless veins were bulging beneath the surface, but unlike in the case of Immortal Lord Hot Flame, his skin was able to remain intact.

Han Li knew that this was thanks to his cultivation of the Great Universe Origin Arts, and that he was only able to fare so well against the azure lightning due to his tremendous physical constitution.

Spears of lightning were constantly crashing against his body like spears, and arcs of lightning began to pierce through his skin before burrowing their way into his immortal acupoints.

One immortal acupoint in his body was opened after another, and wisps of black baleful qi also began to rise up from his body, but at a far slower rate than what had been observed in Immortal Lord Hot Flame.

At this moment, Weeping Soul was standing near the lightning pond, looking at Han Li with a concerned look in her eyes.

"There's no need to be worried about him. The slow rate of baleful qi expulsion isn't a bad thing, it shows that he's still able to control the degree to which his acupoints are being opened, unlike the person that went before him," Liu Qi said.

Weeping Soul merely nodded silently in response.

Liu Qi then turned his gaze to Fox 3, who was sweating profusely with his teeth gritted tightly and his eyes firmly shut.

The rate of baleful qi outflow from his body was clearly far faster than Han Li's, but there was far less baleful qi surging out of his acupoints than Han Li or even Shi Chuankong.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong were both struggling with their baleful decay, so they already had a great deal of pent-up baleful qi in their bodies in addition to the infiltration of baleful qi from the outside world.

In contrast, Fox 3 was already a High Zenith Stage Jade Immortal, so all he had to expel was the external baleful qi that had infiltrated his body.

However, his physical constitution was also inferior to both Han Li's and Shi Chuankong's, which was why he was in so much agony.

On the other side of the lightning pond, baleful qi was surging out of Shi Chuankong's body in a frenzy alongside wisps of black devilish qi.

Beneath his head of curly white hair, his features had already become twisted with agony. His teeth had turned into uneven fangs, while saliva was dripping down from the corners of his mouths, and black scales had appeared over his body as he struggled to contain his true devilish form.

Chapter 758: No Making Without First Breaking

In contrast with Fox 3, Shi Chuankong's eyes remained wide open, and he was staring intently at Han Li on the other side of the Baleful Cleansing Pond.

At this point, Han Li's skin had already turned a bright red color, as had his eyes, and white steam was rising up from his body alongside black baleful qi, making him appear as if he were being cooked alive.

Black and white mist intertwined while giant arcs of azure lightning ravaged Han Li's body from all directions amid rumbling thunderclaps.

Even though the three of them had stepped into the Baleful Cleansing Pond at the same time, it was clear that Han Li had the most baleful qi in his body, so he was also most heavily affected by the lightning pond, and the lightning around him was raging with far greater ferocity than in the case of the other two.

Similarly, the scenes unfolding in his body were just as astonishing.

At this moment, every single one of his acupoints was like a border pass that was constantly being attacked by the azure lightning in the pond, and he felt as if there were gusts of fierce wind sweeping through his consciousness, striking him with a sense of disorientation and unease.

If it weren't for exceptional mental fortitude, his soul would've most likely already succumbed before his body.

Liu Qi's eyes narrowed slightly, and a hint of approval flashed through his eyes at the sight of Han Li's stellar performance.

However, right at this moment, Han Li suddenly erupted into an uncontrollable coughing fit, causing his body to tremble violently, and the rate of outflow of baleful qi from his acupoints instantly sped up significantly, like floodwaters gushing out of a broken dam.

Riled up by the increased output of baleful qi, the surrounding azure lightning instantly became even more violent, converging from all directions to quickly eradicate all of the baleful qi around Han Li.

Even though the baleful qi had been eradicated, Han Li's aura was becoming murkier by the second, while blood began to rapidly flow into his gray pupils. Bright red light was converging from all directions on his eyeballs, and it was about to take over the entirety of his pupils soon.

"Master!" Weeping Soul called out in an alarmed voice upon seeing this.

"What terrible luck... To think that his baleful decay would recur at a time like this..." Liu Qi murmured to himself with furrowed brows.

A low roar rang out from deep within Han Li's throat, and his body shuddered violently as all of his joints began to crack and pop loudly.

Golden light was flashing incessantly all over his body, and layers of golden scales were constantly appearing over his skin before fading away in a repetitive cycle.

"The baleful qi in his body is gradually gaining the upper hand, controlling him to ward off the lightning in the Baleful Cleansing Pond. If he's unable to retain his sanity and succumbs to the control of the baleful qi, then he'll be beyond saving. At this rate, there's no way he'll ever recover," Liu Qi said with a grim expression.

Weeping Soul's expression darkened even further upon hearing this, and after a brief hesitation, she rubbed a hand over her own glabella, upon which the skin and flesh there parted to reveal a dark red demonic eye.

"I suggest you stay out of this. This process is a little similar to tribulation transcendence in that external intervention can have catastrophic consequences. If you step in now, you could attract the azure lightning to yourself, and not only will you be killed, your master's baleful cleansing will also fail. Even if he somehow survives, he'll be reduced to a mindless Gray Immortal," Liu Qi harrumphed coldly.

A conflicted look appeared in Weeping Soul's eyes upon hearing this, but ultimately, she closed her demonic eye as she turned to Liu Qi and implored, "Please save my master."

"Didn't I just say that external intervention will only worsen the situation? Do you want his baleful cleansing to fail?" Liu Qi asked in a cold voice.

"But..."

"I can forcibly drag him out of the lightning pond right now, but I presume that's definitely not what he wants. Risk and reward always come hand in hand in the endeavor of cultivation, and only by directly facing adversity and having the courage to risk it all will one have any chance at reaching heights unreachable to others. Even though your master and I have only just met, I can tell that his mental fortitude far exceeds that of the average person," Liu Qi continued in a calm manner.

Weeping Soul bit down onto her own lower lip, then forced herself to sit back down onto the ground, but her eyes remained firmly fixed on Han Li.

He better not disappoint me! I've been waiting so many years for a chance to be freed, if this opportunity slips past, then I'll most likely be trapped here for the rest of eternity...

Right at this moment, a burst of dull rumbling rang out, and loose rocks began to clatter down from the surrounding rock faces.

The Baleful Cleansing Pond was relatively isolated from the outside world, but even so, bursts of rumbling could be heard ringing out incessantly from outside.

Why is it becoming louder and louder outside? Could it be that more reinforcements are arriving from the Infernal Tribe, or has that old neighbor of mine been freed? If that human brat doesn't complete his baleful cleansing a little faster, things could take a turn for the worse very soon...

With that in mind, Liu Qi opened his mouth to release a burst of black light that instantly struck the green bead.

The bead shuddered violently as the light surging out of it instantly swelled by severalfold, attracting even more of the azure lightning from the pond, thereby further alleviating the pressure on Han Li's trio.

Among the three of them, Fox 3 had the least baleful qi in his body, and his pain was instantly significantly eased. His aura also gradually became more stable, and at this rate, it was only a matter of time before all of the baleful qi in his body was expelled.

Shi Chuankong was also faring far better than before, but he didn't dare to let down his guard even in the slightest. Even though his baleful decay hadn't recurred, he was still in an extremely perilous situation.

Despite Liu Qi's best efforts, Han Li's condition was still far from optimistic.

All of a sudden, he let loose a wild roar, and streaks of light of different colors flew out of his body before forming a series of life-like true spirit projections, including the Giant Mountain Ape, the Kun Peng, the Rainbow Phoenix...

How interesting! It's incredible that he's managed to survive to this point with so many true spirit bloodlines in his body, but having such a diverse bloodline may not necessarily be a good thing...

At this moment, Han Li felt as if his consciousness had turned into a warzone, and there were enormous waves constantly battering the white mountain formed by the Imperial Peak Spirit Restriction Talisman.

The mountain was trembling violently as it released halos of gentle white light to try and sooth Han Li's chaotic mind, but these white halos were instantly destroyed by the aggressive waves upon contact.

At the same time, dark clouds were beginning to gather above his consciousness, and that was a clear indication of excessive baleful qi infiltration.

Meanwhile, more and more true spirit projections continued to appear around his body, and his muscles began to involuntarily bulge. His arms transformed into those of the Giant Mountain Ape, a Xuanwu Turtle shell was beginning to appear over his chest, and Rainbow Phoenix tail feathers were emerging behind him.

Liu Qi's expression finally changed slightly upon seeing this.

Given his vast wealth of experience as a Dao Ancestor, his current appraisal of Han Li was that he was already a spent force, and that both his body and soul were on the verge of destruction.

He was concerned that at this rate, not only did Han Li run the risk of losing his sanity, even his body could detonate on the spot.

As the owner of the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber, Han Li had to survive for Liu Qi to be freed.

Right as he was considering forcibly dragging Han Li out of the lightning pond, a burst of peculiar energy fluctuations suddenly rose up from within his body.

Inside his consciousness, a golden nascent soul was currently seated with its legs crossed and its eyes closed while making a strange hand seal.

The nascent soul didn't open its mouth to speak, but clear chanting could be heard reverberating throughout Han Li's mind. The sound of the chanting was rather faint, but also very clear, audible even over the rumbling of the ferocious waves.

The nascent soul was chanting the mantra for the fifth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique, and initially, the chanting was extremely slow and rather feeble, but as the chanting sped up, the nascent soul's voice seemed to gain strength.

Somehow, in this dire situation, Han Li had managed to break through the bottleneck of the fifth level of the Spirit Refinement Technique, and bursts of tremendous spiritual sense were surging through his mind, quelling the unrest within his consciousness.

The baleful qi in his mind was forced back by his newfound power, and the crimson coloration of his eyes began to fade, while his lucidity also returned.

Some time later, he gently exhaled, then withdrew all of the true spirit projections around him, and he felt utterly exhausted, but thankfully, he had managed to quell his baleful decay once again.

An astonished look appeared on Liu Qi's face upon seeing this.

Chapter 759: Severing the Chain

Around fifteen minutes passed by, and at this point, Han Li's trio was beginning to grow accustomed to the pain inflicted upon them by the azure lightning. However, at the same time, they discovered that the baleful qi flowing out of their acupoints wasn't as dense as before, and the rate of outflow had also slowed down significantly.

This came as quite a relief to both Fox 3 and Shi Chuankong, but Han Li wasn't encouraged by this at all.

This wasn't a sign that the baleful qi in his body was close to being fully expelled. Instead, it only showed him that the azure lightning pond was becoming less efficacious.

Right at this moment, Liu Qi suddenly declared, "Alright, that's enough. Each lightning pond has different baleful cleansing capabilities, and that's about as much as this azure pond can help you. If you keep going, you'll only be suffering more physical damage for not much gain."

"Didn't you say that this azure lightning pond would be enough to complete our baleful cleansings?" Han Li asked with slightly furrowed brows.

"How was I supposed to know that a pair of Golden Immortals like yourselves would have so much baleful qi in your bodies? You two must've claimed countless lives up to this point in your cultivation journeys!" Liu Qi scoffed.

Han Li knew that he did indeed have far more baleful qi in his body than the average Golden Immortal, so he accepted this explanation and was just about to fly out of the lightning pond, but as soon as he rose up into the air, the azure lightning latched onto him from behind and forcibly dragged him back into the pond.

Fox 3 and Shi Chuankong attempted to fly out of the pond as well, but they encountered the same problem.

The baleful qi in their bodies hadn't been completely eradicated, so the lightning in the pond was still instinctively attacking them and refusing to let them go.

Han Li immediately channeled his Reversal True Axis ability, and he shot out of the pond like an arc of golden lightning, while Shi Chuankong also emerged from the pond using a spatial secret technique.

Due to his relatively frail physical constitution, Fox 3 had sustained the most severe injuries out of the three, and even with his High Zenith Stage cultivation base, he was the last one to free himself from the pond.

After landing on the ground, all three of them stumbled slightly before sitting down with their legs crossed.

Fox 3's entire body was charred black and riddled with gashes, but there was an elated smile on his face.

He promptly devoured a fragrant High Zenith Stage pill, and the injuries all over his body began to quickly heal at a rate that was discernible even to the naked eye.

There was an elated look on Shi Chuankong's face as well, and he also took a pill, upon which a large cloud of black mist emerged to envelop his entire body.

Han Li's robes were in tatters, and the bright red coloration of his skin refused to fade. Weeping Soul approached him to enquire about his condition, in response to which he merely shook his head, indicating that he was fine.

Instead of immediately taking any pills, he closed his eyes to rest for a moment, then carefully examined his Spirit Refinement Technique to find that he really had broken through his previous bottleneck. At this point, it wouldn't take long at all for him to achieve full mastery of the fifth level.

After that, he also took a few pills, but Han Li and the others were all roused from their meditation by Liu Qi just a few minutes later.

"Pardon my interruption, but we don't have a lot of time on our hands. Yin Chengquan may be caught up at the Three Region Conference at the moment, but that doesn't mean that he won't send anyone else here, and once that happens, it'll be very difficult for you to complete your baleful cleansings," Liu Qi said.

"Indeed, there's not much time left for us," Han Li replied with a nod.

"Liu San is already at the High Zenith Stage, so he requires no further cleansing, but the remaining baleful qi in your bodies lurks even deeper in your immortal acupoints and can only be cleansed by the more powerful purple lightning pond. That's going to be quite a time-consuming process, so let's not waste any more time," Liu Qi said as he took a meaningful glance at Han Li.

Han Li was naturally aware of what that look entailed, and he said, "There's no hurry. According to our agreement, I have to free you from these chains in exchange for your help. Even though my baleful qi hasn't been completely cleansed, I should still sever one of these chains as a show of good faith."

Liu Qi nodded with a pleased expression upon seeing this.

Shi Chuankong raised no objections, and Fox 3 was naturally eager to help.

"So all that's needed is for the four of us to inject our power into the saber at once?" Han Li asked as he flipped a hand over to summon the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber.

A subtle peculiar look flashed through Liu Qi's eyes as he swept his gaze over the saber, and he replied, "An immense amount of immortal spiritual power will be required to unleash the full power of a third-grade immortal treasure, so don't hold back. Otherwise, if you fail to sever the chain in one blow, there's a very good chance that you'll be struck with backlash from the chain, which will be extremely painful for all of us."

"I'll be sure to do my best," Fox 3 promised.

"Rest assured, Senior, I'm aware that now is not the time to be holding back," Shi Chuankong also assured.

As for Han Li, he remained silent as he turned to Weeping Soul with a nod.

After taking a moment to collect themselves, Han Li grabbed onto the hilt of the sword, while everyone else positioned themselves behind him.

"Fellow Daoist Shi..."

After grabbing onto the hilt of the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber with both hands, Han Li began to attempt to communicate with Shi Qinghou.

However, he received no response, and it was as if Shi Qinghou had gone into hibernation.

"Fellow Daoist Shi, I know that there must be some history between you and Patriarch Liu Qi, but we have no choice but to help him right now, so I want you to lend me your power," Han Li urged through their spiritual connection, but once again, he received no response.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly, and he didn't waste any more time as he tightened his grip around the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber before injecting his immortal spiritual power into it.

All of the patterns on the blade began to light up, and a tremendous aura began to emanate from the saber.

Fox 3 and the others all thrust their palms toward Han Li to inject their immortal spiritual power into his body, and he acted as a central hub, transferring all of their power into the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber.

A faint buzzing sound rang out from the saber, Han Li's hands began to tremble uncontrollably as layers upon layers of crimson saber projections emerged.

The aura emanating from the saber also swelled rapidly, quickly reaching an unprecedented level.

Han Li's brows were tightly furrowed, and in the face of the saber's aura, a strange sensation was rising up within his body, as if his blood were boiling.

"The aura of this saber is quite unique, and it looks like it can stimulate one's blood and essence to drastically enhance combat prowess. There's no need to be concerned, just focus on the task at hand," Liu Qi said.

Han Li inspected his own internal condition to find that there were indeed no adverse effects taking place, and only then did he focus fully on injecting his immortal spiritual power into the saber.

With the injection of immortal spiritual power, the crimson light radiating from the saber became brighter and brighter, and crimson light appeared in the eyes of the two fox heads on the saber as well.

Han Li let loose a loud roar as he stepped forward before swinging the saber down with all his might, and countless giant saber projections erupted forth, striking the azure chain one after another.

A string of metallic clangs rang out as the azure chain trembled violently, and all of the runes engraved upon it instantly began to glow as radiantly as the sun.

The azure lightning pond instantly erupted into a frenzy, forming an enormous ball of lightning that hurtled directly toward Patriarch Liu Qi along the azure chain.

However, the ball of lightning was stopped in its tracks by the crimson saber projections, and the forces clashed with immense power.

"Sever it! Hurry!" Liu Qi roared.

Han Li and the others abruptly shuddered, and the immortal spiritual power in their bodies gushed forth in a frenzy, surging into the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber in an uncontrollable manner.

The crimson light radiating from the saber brightened even further, and the crimson saber projections that it had conjured up also seemed to have become countless times heavier as they inched toward the ball of lightning.

A hint of fear began to well up in the hearts of Han Li and the others. At this rate, they would be completely drained of immortal spiritual power before the chain could be severed.

Right at this moment, the fox heads on the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber lit up, and a giant crimson fox projection suddenly appeared, then pounced forward before fusing into the crimson saber projections, instantly bestowing upon them tremendous power.

A resounding boom rang out as the ball of lightning exploded violently, following which a streak of crimson light flashed past to sever the azure chain.

The chain tumbled to the ground, while the azure lightning retreated back into the lightning pond.

"We did it!" Fox 3 exclaimed with an ecstatic expression.

Han Li withdrew the saber, then began to examine it with tightly furrowed brows, wondering why Shi Qinghou had ultimately decided to help them at the last second.

As for Shi Chuankong, he was also observing the saber in silence with an apprehensive expression, clearly a little shaken by the forced outflow of immortal spiritual power from earlier.

"What's wrong, Master?" Weeping Soul asked.

"Nothing. How are your injuries?" Han Li asked as he stowed the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber away.

"I'm fine," Weeping Soul replied.

Right at this moment, Liu Qi raised his head to the heavens and chortled with glee at the sight of the snapped azure chain, causing the entire hall to tremble slightly.

"Thank you, everyone. Take some time to replenish your immortal spiritual power, then continue with your baleful cleansing," he said after his laughter subsided.

Chapter 760: Spiritual Sense Avatar

Asura City.

The Three Region Conference had recommenced, but due to the unexpected interlude from earlier, all of the regional monarchs were feeling rather apprehensive, so the atmosphere was a little awkward.

As the host of the conference, Yin Chengquan had to keep up appearances, even though he was feeling rather uneasy internally.

He forced a smile onto his own face, and he was just about to say something when a gray ring on his left pinky finger suddenly tightened a little.

There were four marks of different colors engraved onto the ring, namely azure, purple, silver, and gold, and in this instant, the azure mark suddenly faded.

His smile instantly stiffened, while veins began bulging on his forehead, but only for an instant before he composed himself.

Despite this, the brief change in his expression hadn't escaped anyone's notice, and Huang Fuyu raised an eyebrow as he remarked, "You don't look so good, Regional Monarch Yin. Have you been working too hard lately?"

"I'm fine. Once again, I must thank all of you for making the effort to come here," Yin Chengquan replied.

"There's no need to thank us, Regional Monarch Yin. The outcome of this conference will have a direct impact on the future of the Gray Realm, so it's only right that all of us made the effort to be in attendance," Xiao Buye said with a smile.

"Also, what happened in the Soul Cleansing Area? Why don't you tell everyone, Regional Monarch Yin?" Huang Fuyu asked.

At this point, Yin Chengquan's expression had already completely returned to normal, and he replied, "It was only a minor incident that's not worth sharing, let's get on with the conference. Today is the first day of the decision stage. After the past few days of discussion, I'm sure all of you have already made your decisions, so let's all express our ideas for everyone to hear."

Huang Fuyu took a glance at Xiao Buye, who just so happened to be looking at him as well, and the two of them exchanged a suspicious glance.

Right as Yin Chengquan's voice trailed off, a gray jade pendant concealed within his robe silently shattered.

......

Inside a certain spacious hall in Asura City.

This appeared to be a guest hall that was furnished with some refined and antiquated furniture, and the entire hall was enshrouded within a gray light barrier.

Two figures were seated across from each other at the center of the hall, one of whom was Feng Qingshui, the elderly man from the Heavenly Court, while the other was the spitting image of Yin Chengquan.

However, this Yin Chengquan was looking rather insubstantial, and it seemed like he didn't possess a substantial body.

All of a sudden, a burst of gray light flashed over Yin Chengquan's entire body, and his expression instantly darkened significantly.

"Is something wrong, Fellow Daoist Yin? I'm doing nothing but wasting time by sitting here and drinking tea anyway. If you've encountered any trouble, I'd be happy to help. This spiritual sense avatar of yours is limited in power, so it may not be able to do much," Feng Qingshui said as he set down the teacup in his hand.

"Thank you for your concern, Fellow Daoist Feng, but right now, everything is still under control, so I won't trouble you," Yin Chengquan replied.

"Fellow Daoist Yin, we are allies fighting for a common cause right now, why do you feel the need to be so wary of me?" Feng Qingshui asked as his brows furrowed slightly with displeasure.

"I'll tell you if I need your help, but before that, please remain here," Yin Chengquan replied in an indifferent manner, then abruptly vanished from the spot, immediately following which the gray light barrier around the hall instantly became several times thicker.

A cold look flashed across Feng Qingshui's face upon seeing this, and he picked up his teacup with a contemplative expression.

......

In the Baleful Cleansing Ponds, Han Li and the others were meditating on the spot after severing the azure lightning chain.

Meanwhile, Liu Qi was making a hand seal with his eyes closed while chanting an incantation on the giant cross, seemingly preparing something.

Ever since the azure lightning chain was severed, his aura had been drastically elevated.

Right at this moment, his eyes abruptly sprang open as he cast his gaze in a certain direction.

All of a sudden, a faint layer of light emerged from the rock face there, immediately followed by numerous circles of runes that began revolving rapidly.

After that, an indistinct gray figure gradually emerged, looking a little warped and insubstantial.

Han Li and the others immediately sprang to their feet upon seeing this, while Weeping Soul shuddered slightly as she exclaimed, "Master!"

Han Li's heart jolted slightly upon hearing this, and he asked in a low voice, "Weeping Soul, is this Yin Chengquan?"

Before Weeping Soul had a chance to reply, the gray figure suddenly turned his gaze to Han Li and the others.

Han Li immediately felt his vision black out momentarily as a burst of tremendous force surged into his mind, and the white mountain formed by the Imperial Peak Spirit Restriction Talisman shuddered violently before instantly shattering.

He felt as if his soul were about to fall apart at the seams, and he almost fell unconscious on the spot.

Han Li hurriedly channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique, and his spiritual sense was able to quell the unrest in his soul.

Thankfully, he had just made significant strides in the Spirit Refinement Technique, and his newfound spiritual sense was able to just barely protect his soul.

At the same time, a series of spiritual sense chains appeared in front of him, then intertwined to form a large net to ward off the burst of invisible force.

However, the oncoming force was extremely formidable, and it was able to surge into his mind through the net of spiritual sense chains.

Han Li's mind was ringing as he stumbled back in retreat, unable to steady himself.

Shi Chuankong also shuddered violently as blood came gushing out of his mouth, and his complexion instantly turned deathly pale.

All of a sudden, a small silver lock appeared above his head amid a flash of silver light, and it protected his head as he flew back in retreat.

However, the small lock then shuddered violently, and a crack appeared on its surface, while the silver light emanating from it quickly dimmed.

An alarmed look appeared on Shi Chuankong's face as he opened his mouth to expel a ball of blood essence into the lock while making a rapid string of hand seals.

The light emanating from the lock brightened slightly so that it was able to continue protecting his head, but it was flashing erratically, looking as if it could be snuffed out at any moment.

Among the three of them, Fox 3 was the one who reacted the quickest, darting back in retreat as soon as Yin Chengquan cast his gaze toward them.

At the same time, a series of white talismans flew out of his sleeves, forming layers upon layers of semi-transparent white light barriers in front of him.

In the blink of an eye, dozens of these light barriers had been erected, but they had only just taken shape before they were completely pulverized.

Fox 3's brows furrowed tightly as he continued to sweep his sleeves through the air, instantly releasing dozens more of the same white talismans.

One white light barrier appeared in front of him after another before being shattered once again, this time even faster than before, and as a result, Fox 3 was forced into retreat even faster as well.

Out of the four, Weeping Soul was the only one who wasn't being attacked, and she was standing off to the side with a conflicted expression.

Right at this moment, Liu Qi's gleeful voice suddenly rang out.

"Yin Chengquan, you've finally sent over a spiritual sense avatar of yours! However, I'm afraid you're already too late."

The soundwaves from his voices formed a barrier in front of Han Li's trio, and the space before them abrupt trembled violently, following which a series of spatial rifts emerged.

The entire hall began to sway as if an earthquake had struck, and a series of cracks appeared over the surrounding rock faces.

The tremendous pressure that Han Li's trio was being subjected to was instantly alleviated, and they stumbled back a few more steps before finally managing to steady themselves with alarmed looks on their faces.

A burst of translucent light flashed over Liu Qi's glabella, then formed a gray-robed middle-aged man with a fox fur belt around his waist.

The man was standing in front of Han Li's trio with his hands clasped behind his back, giving off an awe-inspiring aura.

"Yin Chengquan, perhaps if you had come here in person, I would be powerless to do anything with only one chain severed, but you're dreaming if you think that a mere spiritual sense avatar of yours can subdue me!" the middle-aged man chuckled coldly.

Yin Chengquan's expression darkened slightly as he turned to Weeping Soul and said in a cold voice, "Luo'er! How dare you bring these outsiders into the Soul Cleansing Area? Not only have you released the Kun Hou, you've released Liu Qi as well! Do you know how much trouble you've caused for our Infernal Tribe?"

Weeping Soul shuddered slightly upon hearing this, and a guilt-ridden look appeared in her eyes as she took a glance at Han Li and said, "I'm sorry, Master. I only wanted to bring him here to be cleansed of his baleful qi, I had no intention of harming the interests of the Infernal Tribe. He's also only here to cleanse himself of baleful qi and had no intention of opposing the Infernal Tribe."

"So you're Luo'er's former master? In that case, I can spare you for this transgression. You can go," Yin Chengquan said as he turned to Han Li before suddenly making a hand seal, and the restrictions on the hall's stone gate slowly parted, as if he really did intend to let Han Li go.

A contemplative look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he really did seem to be tempted by the offer.

Chapter 761: Master and Disciple

"Don't fall for his tricks, Fellow Daoist Li! He's trying to divide and conquer us! Right now, the entire city is in lockdown, so even if you can get away now, you'll be captured again sooner or later. The only way out right now is to rescue our patriarch and escape under his protection," Fox 3 hurriedly said.

Han Li took a glance at Fox 3, and it was unclear what he was thinking.

"You think I'm trying to trick you? I'm sure you're all aware of what the current state of Asura City is like. I don't have the time or resources to spare to hunt you down, and in my eyes, letting a couple of Golden Immortals escape is hardly of any significance.

“If you're still apprehensive, I can even grant you an infernal badge," Yin Chengquan said, and he swept a sleeve through the air as he spoke, releasing a black metal badge that descended in front of Weeping Soul.

Liu Qi's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

"Master, the restrictions littered throughout the entirety of Asura City are all connected to a super array, and infernal badges are treasures refined from that super array. There are only five such badges in total in the entire Infernal Tribe, and it'll allow you to open the majority of restrictions in Asura City," Weeping Soul said to Han Li through voice transmission as she caught the badge.

"I also played a part in destroying the seal on the Kun Hou, and you were intent on killing me just a moment ago, so why has your attitude suddenly changed so drastically?" Han Li asked as his eyes narrowed slightly.

"Under normal circumstances, I would make absolute certain that none of you leave this place alive. However, right now, my only goal is to restrain Liu Qi, and you were able to withstand an attack of mine just now, so it's clear that I won't be able to kill you while you're under Liu Qi's protection. Hence, I'm choosing to let you go to eliminate some volatile factors," Yin Chengquan explained in a cold voice.

"That's a very candid and sincere explanation, but I've already agreed to help Senior Liu Qi, so I'm afraid I must turn down your proposal," Han Li replied with a faint smile.

Fox 3 and Liu Qi were both very relieved to hear this, but the complete opposite was true for Weeping Soul.

"If you insist on opposing me, then I'll strike you down where you stand! You saw what just happened, Luo'er. I extended an olive branch to him, but he turned it down, so he leaves me no choice," Yin Chengquan said in a cold voice as he made a hand seal, and the giant array on the ground suddenly lit up, following which a burst of white light erupted forth before enveloping Weeping Soul and carrying her away.

Weeping Soul was saying something with an urgent expression, but the white light around her was too powerful, and whatever she was saying was inaudible through it.

However, right at this moment, one of Liu Qi's tails wrapped itself around Weeping Soul like lightning.

Yin Chengquan's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, and he immediately flew over to Liu Qi before throwing a punch straight at his head.

A burst of radiant gray light erupted out of his fist, and a sinister ghostly head the size of a house appeared within it, screeching and cackling incessantly.

The sounds were extremely sharp and penetrated straight into one's soul while giving off an intense aura of death, as if they were coming straight from the pits of hell.

Han Li, Fox 3, and Shi Chuankong immediately felt their heads ringing violently upon hearing this sound, and they felt as if their souls were about to fall apart.

On the ground below, Liu Qi swept both of his front paws through the air to release numerous streaks of gray light, which instantly formed a gray light barrier that encompassed Han Li's group and the four lightning ponds.

As soon as the light barrier took shape, the harrowing sounds were instantly shut out, and at the same time, the projection of the middle-aged man appeared above the light barrier in a flash, standing in Yin Chengquan's way.

"You'll have to get through me first if you want to get to them," the middle-aged man chuckled as he made a hand seal, and a burst of gray light surged out of his body, then transformed into a thick staff projection that was over a hundred feet in length.

Two serpentine projections were wrapped around either end of the staff projection, giving off incredibly formidable soul power fluctuations as it sped toward Yin Chengquan's fist.

The two clashed violently in mid-air, resulting in a blinding explosion of light that sent spiritual sense fluctuations erupting in all directions, causing the nearby space to warp and fracture like the surface of a mirror.

The gray light barrier also began to tremble violently, but it was extremely resilient and quickly managed to stabilize itself.

Following that clash, both the middle-aged man and Yin Chengquan were sent flying back.

The string of clashes had taken place in the blink of an eye, and only now did the bodies of Han Li's trio manage to react, upon which all of them threw up mouthfuls of blood before exchanging astonished looks with one another.

"Liu Qi! Do you not feel ashamed going after a junior like this?" Yin Chengquan yelled in a furious voice.

"I don't think I've ever heard such righteous words coming out of your mouth, Regional Monarch Yin. The two of us have been going at each other for countless years, do you really think I still haven't seen through your intentions?" Liu Qi chuckled coldly as he exerted more force through his tail, and the white light barrier around Weeping Soul was instantly shattered, following which she was carried back to his side.

Weeping Soul was struggling with all her might, but her struggles slowly ceased upon hearing this.

"What do you mean by that?" Yin Chengquan asked as his eyes narrowed slightly.

A hint of mockery flashed through Liu Qi's eyes, following which he turned to Weeping Soul as he asked, "You're a Xing Beast, right? I'm guessing that after Yin Chengquan took you under his wing, he did everything in his power to nurture you, even going as far as to capture beings from different tribes and killing them so that you can devour their souls, is that correct?"

"That's right, I am greatly indebted to my master," Weeping Soul replied.

"Do you know why your master was willing to do so much for you? I'm sure you're aware of what kind of person he is, are you not?" Liu Qi asked.

Weeping Soul's complexion paled slightly upon hearing this, and she opened her mouth to say something, but ultimately remained silent.

This was a question that she had asked herself on many past occasions. However, she didn't want to suspect Yin Chengquan's kindness, so whenever the question arose in her mind, she would immediately avoid it, but now that it was being directly posed to her, she was forced to finally confront it.

Han Li's heart stirred slightly upon hearing this.

Prior to coming here, he had heard that Yin Chengquan was a very bloodthirsty man who was renowned for using all types of sly and underhanded tactics to force smaller regions to bow to the Infernal Region. Hence, even his subordinates were extremely fearful of him, and he certainly didn't seem like the type of person who would accept an outsider as a disciple, much less nurture them so diligently.

However, given the constant peril that he had been in, he had never had a chance to ponder this topic, but it seemed that all was about to be revealed.

"I'm sure all of you are aware of the ability of Infernal beings to control others using Infernal Soul Bugs. Even I have to admit that this is an extremely powerful ability. Not only is the Infernal Soul Bug able to control a puppet, it can also establish a connection between puppet and master.

“If the law powers mastered by master and puppet are similar, then it can allow them to very easily integrate their law powers, and that's an important reason behind why the Infernal Tribe has always stood as one of the most powerful tribes of the Gray Realm," Liu Qi continued.

"What does this have to do with Weeping Soul, Senior Liu Qi?" Han Li asked.

"Due to some mishaps, I sustained severe injuries many years ago and fell to the Gray Realm, where I was captured by Yin Chengquan. He didn't kill me because the heavenly illusion laws that I had mastered were appealing to him.

“He cultivates the laws of ghostly enchantment, and if he could successfully refine me into a puppet, then our law powers would be able to complement one another to great effect, meaning that he would have no equal in the entire Gray Realm," Liu Qi explained with a cold sneer.

A thought seemed to have occurred to Weeping Soul here, and her complexion paled slightly.

"However, in order to control a Dao Ancestor like myself, Yin Chengquan requires an Infernal Soul Bug of an extremely high caliber, one that can't be refined using normal souls. That's why he's gone to such great lengths to nurture you.

“Xing Beasts are extremely advanced soul entities capable of devouring ghosts and spirits, making them ideal for refining premium Infernal Soul Bugs. However, your cultivation base is still quite lackluster right now, and I presume he wanted to set his plan into motion only after raising you to the Great Encompassment Stage," Liu Qi said.

Weeping Soul's complexion paled even further upon hearing this.

Han Li heaved an internal sigh upon seeing this. He had also suffered betrayal from someone that he had respected in the past, and even though it had already been many years, those events had still had a huge impact on his entire cultivation journey.

"Is he telling the truth, Master?" Weeping Soul asked as she turned to Yin Chengquan.

"It's been fun putting on the guise of a kind and benevolent master, and I originally planned to keep this act up for a while longer, but seeing as everything has already been revealed, I suppose I have no choice but to put a premature end to things," Yin Chengquan replied with a cold sneer, and the final hint of color faded from Weeping Soul's cheeks with this confirmation.

A cold gleam flashed through Han Li's eyes as he glowered at Yin Chengquan.

"Liu Qi, didn't you just say that you can see through all of my intentions? In that case, do you know why I allowed you to reveal all of that without doing anything to try and stop you?" Yin Chengquan asked as he turned to Liu Qi.

Liu Qi faltered slightly upon hearing this, following which a hint of realization appeared in his eyes as he hurriedly turned his gaze to Weeping Soul.

Chapter 762: Eternal Dream

All of a sudden, the infernal badge in Weeping Soul's hand exploded into two bursts of black qi, one of which transformed into an indistinct bug that instantly burrowed its way into her body, while the other transformed into a black dagger that shot forth toward Liu Qi's chest at an astonishing speed.

Liu Qi was bound to the cross, so he was unable to evade the dagger, and he could only raise his freed front paw to protect himself.

However, the dagger suddenly began to squirm like an agile spirit snake, slithering through a gap between Liu Qi's paws before instantly piercing into his chest.

His chest instantly exploded as blood splattered in all directions, and the dagger was able to pierce almost all the way through his body.

Liu Qi immediately threw up a large mouthful of blood that was interspersed with organ fragments, while the middle-aged man in the sky shuddered before becoming even more insubstantial in form.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and the gray light barrier encompassing Han Li and the others also dimmed significantly.

Liu Qi's tail unfurled from around Weeping Soul's body, and she tumbled to the ground, throwing her hands to her own head as she let loose a blood-curdling howl.

Black light was swirling around her body, and through the black light, one could see an indistinct bug projection in her abdomen, squirming incessantly as it rapidly devoured her energy.

Han Li and the others were stunned by this turn of events, but they immediately reacted and sprang into action, with Fox 3 flying over to Liu Qi's side, while Han Li hurriedly rushed over to Weeping Soul to support her.

He injected his spiritual sense into her body to inspect her internal condition, upon which his expression instantly darkened significantly.

"What do you think of my Immortal Devouring Dagger?" Yin Chengquan chuckled as he made a grabbing motion, and a giant gray palm projection appeared in front of him, then swooped down toward the middle-aged man.

The giant gray hand was giving off incredibly formidable soul power fluctuations, and even though Han Li and the others were currently situated in the gray light barrier, they were still instantly knocked unconscious.

The middle-aged man threw a punch in retaliation, releasing a pillar of white light to oppose the gray palm projection.

A resounding boom rang out as the two clashed, but the pillar of white light was clearly inferior in power and was instantly crushed upon contact.

The gray palm projection continued to swoop down, grasping onto the middle-aged man before crushing him with ease.

However, not only was Yin Chengquan not elated in the slightest to see this, his expression had completely darkened instead, and he let loose a low roar as he made a grabbing motion with both hands.

Four identical gray palm projections appeared around him in a flash, then swept through the air in all directions, and the surrounding space was instantly shattered, revealing the middle-aged man standing nearby in a completely unscathed condition, looking as if he were about to approach Yin Chengquan.

Within the gray light barrier down below, Liu Qi, Weeping Soul, and Han Li's group were also completely unharmed, and there was a ball of white light hovering in front of Liu Qi, releasing white halos in all directions.

A black dagger and a black bug projection were sealed inside the ball of light, unable to escape.

Yin Chengquan's expression instantly darkened even further upon seeing this.

"As expected of you to have to freed yourself from my Eternal Dream so quickly," Liu Qi chuckled with more than a hint of mockery in his voice, then opened his mouth to devour the ball of white light in front of him.

Yin Chengquan was furious to see this, and he immediately made a downward grabbing motion, upon which the four giant gray palm projections came swooping down while giving off tremendous soul power fluctuations.

Even before the four palm projections had fully descended, the gray light barrier was already trembling violently, looking as if it could shatter at any moment.

A serious look appeared on Liu Qi's face upon seeing this, and he raised his freed front paw, sending a flurry of incantation seals flying through the air, half of which surged into the gray light barrier to stabilize it, while the other half vanished into the body of the middle-aged man up above.

As a result, the middle-aged man instantly transformed into a white fox projection that was several hundred feet tall, and with a sweep of its nine tails, a wave of white light was released to clash against the four gray palm projections.

The wave of white light was instantly destroyed upon contact, while the giant fox projection was sent flying back before crashing heavily into the wall, but the four giant palm projections had also been repelled.

"He's going all out! I won't be able to last long at this rate, so you'll need to hurry up and cleanse your bodies of baleful qi, then help me sever the rest of these chains," Liu Qi said in an urgent voice.

Han Li, Shi Chuankong, and Fox 3 exchanged a glance upon hearing this, then flew toward the purple lightning pond together, while Weeping Soul remained still on the spot as she looked up at Yin Chengquan with a cold expression.

Meanwhile, the giant fox projection had already rebounded from the wall, and it didn't appear to have sustained any injuries as it pounced at Yin Chengquan.

"Let me help, Senior Liu Qi," Weeping Soul suddenly said.

"You're quite formidable for someone of your cultivation base, but you're still far from being able to play a part in a battle between Dao Ancestors," Liu Qi said as he took a glance at her.

"I'm naturally not delusional enough to think that, but just as you said earlier, I am indeed a Xing Beast, and I have a secret technique that can use my soul power to enhance the soul power of others. The secret technique is not as effective on those of higher cultivation bases than myself, but it should still work to some extent," Weeping Soul said.

A hint of surprise flashed through Liu Qi's eyes upon hearing this, and he nodded in response.

"Alright, but make sure you don't leave this light barrier. Otherwise, I won't be able to protect you."

Weeping Soul nodded in agreement, then began to chant an incantation, and four balls of black light flew out of the top of her head before descending around Liu Qi, then transformed into four instruments, namely a guqin, a waist drum, a jade flute, and a konghou.

Weeping Soul swept both hands through the air, and strands of translucent light shot out of her glabella, then fell upon the four musical instruments as incantation seals.

Music immediately began to play from the four instruments, and black ripples began to proliferate throughout the nearby space. Countless tiny runes were interspersed throughout the ripples, and they surged into Liu Qi's mind, causing his eyes to light a little.

High up in the sky, Yin Chengquan was unleashing a furious barrage of attacks, and the giant fox projection was quickly forced into a corner of the hall.

"Die!" Yin Chengquan roared as he swept both sleeves through the air, and a vast cloud of gray mist surged out of his body.

The gray mist was formed by countless spiritual sense threads, all of which fused into the four gray palm projections.

As a result, the palm projections swelled even further in size, and a series of profound patterns appeared upon them as they came crashing down with tremendous force while giving off fearsome spiritual sense fluctuations.

All of the space in their wake was filled with these formidable spiritual sense fluctuations, instantly eliminating all paths for evasion and retreat for the fox projection.

"That won't be enough to kill me!" the fox projection roared as the light emanating from its body lit brightened significantly, and it swept its nine tails through the air, releasing what seemed to be like a boundless barrage of waves of white light.

The four giant palm projections struck the waves of white light, only to be instantly devoured as if they had fallen into the sea.

A stunned look appeared on Yin Chengquan's face upon seeing this, following which he noticed what was happening inside the gray light barrier, and the astonishment in his eyes was instantly replaced with fury.

"You're a blind fool, Yin Chengquan! Let's settle our differences here once and for all!" the fox projection chortled as its nine tails abruptly straightened out, and every single strand of fur on those tails began to glow radiantly.

Immediately thereafter, countless strands of fox fur shot forth in unison like crossbow arrows before striking the four gray palm projections, instantly punching them full of tiny holes.

The four palm projections quickly exploded, following which the remaining strands of fox fur hurtled directly toward Yin Chengquan.

Yin Chengquan's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and he immediately shot back in retreat, while the fox projection sprang forward in hot pursuit.

The battle continued, with neither side able to get the better of the other.

The two began moving faster and faster until they were nothing more than a pair of untraceable blurs, and resounding booms were ringing out incessantly as they clashed over and over again.

At the same time, Han Li's trio had descended beside the purple lightning pond.

Liu Qi had already significantly lessened the power of the purple lightning pond for them, but it was still apparent from the aura emanating from the pond that it was several times more formidable than the azure lightning.

Han Li flew into the purple lightning pond without any hesitation, and Shi Chuankong immediately followed suit as well.

However, Fox 3 decided not to enter the pond.

He was already at the High Zenith Stage, and at this point, most of the baleful qi in his body had already been eradicated by the azure lightning pond. Even though there was still some left, it was only a minuscule amount, and there was no need for him to take his chances in the purple lightning pond.

In contrast, it was a much better course of action for him to take a rest and prime himself into his best possible condition so that he could assist Han Li in severing the other lightning chains.

With that in mind, Fox 3 sat down with his legs crossed beside the lightning pond, then summoned a pair of Immortal Origin Stones to help himself replenish his immortal spiritual power.

Chapter 763: Severing the Second Lightning Chain

As soon as Han Li entered the purple lightning pond, the purple lightning pond instantly converged toward him like sharks that had smelt blood, forming a corkscrew-shaped pillar of lightning around him.

Thick arcs of purple lightning sprang forth to strike his entire body amid a string of thunderous explosions, and his skin instantly turned bright red, while profusely bleeding gashes were inflicted all over his entire body.

Not only that, but as soon as the purple lightning struck his body, his glabella instantly turned pitch black, and fierce killing intent welled up in his heart, while his eyes also turned bright red.

Bursts of tremendous baleful qi fluctuations erupted out of his body, and the baleful decay that he had just forcibly suppressed was rearing its ugly head once again.

A hint of lingering fear flashed through Fox 3's eyes at the sight of Han Li's struggles, and he was very glad that he hadn't entered the purple lightning pond.

Meanwhile, Weeping Soul also cast a glance in Han Li's direction, and a hint of concern flashed through her eyes.

All of a sudden, a series of true spirit projections sprang out of Han Li's body again, and they were far clearer than before.

These lightning ponds contained both destructive power and the power of rebirth, so all of his true spirit bloodline had been strengthened somewhat from the time that he had spent in the azure lightning pond.

However, that wasn't necessarily a good thing for Han Li as the enhancements in these foreign bloodlines placed more of a strain on his body.

Han Li took a deep breath, and he remained calm and composed.

After what had just taken place in the azure lightning pond, he already had some experience when it came to dealing with these changes in his body.

After taking a moment to compose himself, he immediately channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique, using his immense spiritual sense to quell the killing intent in his mind. At the same time, he channeled his Great Universe Origin Arts to protect his internal organs, allowing the purple lightning to travel through the rest of his body.

As bursts of formidable lightning power began to infiltrate his body, more baleful qi was expelled, and plumes of black qi began to rise up from his body before instantly being eradicated by the purple lightning.

At this moment, all of his immortal acupoints had also been filled with purple lightning, forcing out the stubborn baleful qi lurking within.

As the baleful qi was cleansed, the killing intent in his mind gradually faded, and his eyes regained their former clarity as well.

This process was clearly more painful than what he had endured in the azure lightning pond, but he gritted his teeth tightly as he withstood the excruciating punishment.

Fifteen minutes passed by in the blink of an eye.

At this point, Han Li's entire body was already riddled with wounds, giving him the appearance of a torn rucksack.

However, his eyes were tightly shut, and there was a calm and placid look on his face, as if he couldn't feel any pain.

Large plumes of black baleful qi continued to surge out of his body, but all of a sudden, the outflow of baleful qi abruptly slowed down.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he opened his eyes, then immediately flew up into the air.

The surrounding purple lightning instantly followed along, forming a purple lightning net that attempted to ensnare him again.

Han Li harrumphed coldly as he channeled his Reversal True Axis ability, shooting up into the air as a golden shadow, but the purple lightning net was far more resilient than the one released by the azure lightning pond, and he was unable to break free right away.

Seemingly enraged by Han Li's provocation, the purple lightning pond released several thick arcs of lightning that hurtled directly toward him.

In contrast with the other lightning in the pond, these arcs of lightning were far brighter and had countless tiny lightning runes flashing around them, giving off tremendous lightning law powers.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and his Mantra Treasured Axis appeared behind him before rapidly revolving to send countless golden ripples surging through the air in a radius of over a hundred feet around him.

The arcs of purple lightning were instantly brought to a halt upon entering the golden ripples, but they seemed to be imbued with tremendous power, and the entire area of golden ripples was trembling slightly.

Han Li immediately swept a sleeve through the air upon seeing this, releasing a ball of green light that contained the Profound Heavenly Gourd.

He cast a string of incantation seals toward the Profound Heavenly Gourd, and a vast expanse of green light instantly surged out of its mouth before sweeping up the arcs of purple lightning, which instantly began to rapidly dim and shrink.

Immediately thereafter, the arcs of purple lightning were sucked into the Profound Heavenly Gourd in a flash.

With part of the purple lightning net sucked into the Profound Heavenly Gourd, the pressure on Han Li was lessened significantly, and he was able to fly up into the air, struggling free from the lightning net before landing near the lightning pond.

After that, the Mantra Treasured Axis vanished at his behest, and the surrounding golden ripples also faded.

The purple lightning net flashed a few times, but with no target left to restrain, it quickly descended back into the lightning pond.

After taking a moment to steady himself, Han Li took a few pills, and all of the gashes on his body began to rapidly heal, while his complexion also improved slightly.

"How are you feeling, Fellow Daoist Li? Right now, Patriarch Liu Qi is able to oppose Yin Chengquan with Fellow Daoist Weeping Soul's help, but they won't be able to keep this up for long. Our fates will be sealed if any other Infernal Tribe reinforcements arrive on the scene, so we have to make haste and sever the three remaining lightning chains as soon as possible," Fox 3 hurriedly said through voice transmission.

"Alright, I'll take some time to recover and wait for Fellow Daoist Shi to come out," Han Li replied with a nod as he turned his gaze to the purple lightning pond.

At this moment, Shi Chuankong was still in the pond, and a series of deep gashes had been sliced into his skin, some so deep that bone was visible through them.

Crimson light was flashing within his eyes, while his glabella had turned pitch black, and it was clear that he was also contending with his baleful decay.

His entire body was trembling uncontrollably from the excruciating agony, but he possessed remarkable mental fortitude, and he was gritting his teeth tightly as he endured the pain.

As plumes of black qi surged out of his body, the crimson light in his eyes gradually faded, as did the black coloration of his glabella, and his skin was beginning to take on a translucent, jade-like appearance.

Han Li knew that there wasn't anywhere near as much baleful qi in Shi Chuankong's body compared to him, and the purple lightning pond had already eradicated much of that baleful qi. At this rate, there was a very good chance that he would overcome his baleful decay to reach the semi-High Zenith Stage.

However, right at this moment, the rate of baleful qi outflow from his body suddenly abated, while the translucent quality of his skin also receded.

Han Li heaved an internal sigh upon seeing this.

It seemed that the second pond had failed to allow Shi Chuankong to overcome his baleful decay as well.

Shi Chuankong opened his eyes, then sprang up out of the lightning pond.

The arcs of purple lightning around him instantly intertwined to form a purple lightning net, and in response, a giant silver lotus flower appeared around his body amid a flash of silver light, then began to release streaks of sharp sword qi that struck the lightning net.

The purple lightning net shuddered violently as an opening was instantly sliced into it, and Shi Chuankong flew out of the opening before landing on the edge of the lightning pond.

He was already in terrible physical condition, and he had exerted himself even further by unleashing that secret technique, causing him to throw up a mouthful of blood.

As soon as he landed on the ground, he immediately summoned a vial, then tipped all of the pills inside straight into his own mouth before sitting down with his legs crossed.

A layer of dark purple light emerged over his body, and his wounds instantly began to rapidly heal.

Only after a long while did Shi Chuankong opened his eyes, following which he turned to Han Li and Fox 3 with a wry smile as he sighed, "I came within a hair's breadth of dying in there."

"It's very remarkable that you were able to survive two Baleful Cleansing Ponds in succession. I'm very thankful that I don't have to go through this. Are you alright now?" Fox 3 asked.

"I'm fine," Shi Chuankong replied.

"In that case, let's begin," Han Li said, then flew over to the silver lightning pond before sweeping a sleeve through the air, and Daoist Xie appeared beside him amid a flash of golden lightning.

"I need your help, Brother Xie," Han Li said, and Daoist Xie nodded in response.

Han Li took a deep breath as he grabbed tightly onto the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber with both hands, then injected his immortal spiritual power into it in a frenzy.

Red light flashed over the saber as all of the patterns on its surface lit up, and it began releasing a tremendous aura.

Fox 3, Shi Chuankong, and Daoist Xie thrust their palms toward Han Li in unison, injecting their immortal spiritual power into his body, following which all of their immortal spiritual power surged into the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber.

The red light emanating from the saber brightened even further, and the aura that it was releasing was also climbing steadily.

Layers upon layers of crimson saber projections emerged, and Han Li swung the saber down with all his might as he called out internally, "Lend me your power, Senior Shi!"

A giant crimson fox projection suddenly emerged from the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber, then pounced forward and vanished into the saber in a flash.

The immortal spiritual power of Han Li and the others was gushing into the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber like floodwaters through a broken dam, but none of them were all that alarmed, given their previous experience in severing the azure lightning chain.

All of the countless crimson saber projections vanished into the saber, causing it to swell to roughly twice its original size before striking the purple lightning chain, which instantly began to tremble violently, while the runes engraved upon it glowed as radiantly as the sun.

The purple lightning pond erupted into a frenzy, and all of the lightning inside rose up to form a ball of lightning that sped toward Liu Qi along the chain.

However, the ball of lightning was only able to make it halfway before the purple chain was snapped under the saber.

The ball of lightning instantly drew to an abrupt halt, then exploded to send arcs of lightning flying in all directions.

Han Li shuddered slightly as a layer of purple lightning appeared over his body, but it only appeared for an instant before fading away, as if nothing had ever happened.

A contemplative look appeared on his face, while the snapped purple chain plunged into the lightning pond.

Chapter 764: Backs Against the Wall

"Well done!" Liu Qi chortled with glee as an unmatched aura erupted out of his body, causing the entire hall to tremble violently.

Yin Chengquan's expression darkened even further as he aimed a vicious glare at Han Li's group, following which he thrust both palms through the air in unison, and a dull thump rang out as four giant gray palm projections appeared above the white fox projection's head at once.

The four giant palm projections fused as one to form an enormous palm projection that was several thousand feet in size, and it came crashing down like a massive mountain.

"Do you still think this spiritual sense avatar of yours is a match for me now that two chains have already been severed?" Liu Qi chortled as he stood up from the wooden cross, but he was still bound by the silver and golden chains.

A burst of bright translucent light emerged over his glabella, and the white fox projection swelled drastically in size, then rose up onto its hind legs before sweeping both of its front paws through the air.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as the giant gray palm projection exploded, and Yin Chengquan shuddered violently as he stumbled back several steps in retreat.

The fox projection was also sent tumbling down from the sky as the white light emanating from its body flickered in a slightly unsteady fashion, but it then instantly righted itself before pouncing at Yin Chengquan.

......

At the conference venue in the Fallen Lake Area.

All of the regional monarchs had begun expressing their opinions, and the former lively and bustling atmosphere of the conference had been restored.

Yin Chengquan was seated with a smile on his face, occasionally communicating with the regional monarchs around him, and Huang Fuyu was a little disappointed to see him looking so calm and composed.

Right at this moment, Wyrm 3's voice suddenly rang out in his mind.

"Palace Master Huang, our people have learned that something has indeed happened in the Soul Cleansing Area, but it's not some incident concerning their treasure refinement facilities, as Yin Chengquan proclaimed. Instead, some people have snuck deep into Asura City and caused a great deal of trouble there. Right now, all of the forces within Asura City are converging there."

"Oh? To think that someone would sneak into Asura City at a time like this," Huang Fuyu mused as he raised an eyebrow.

"Should I instruct our people to keep gathering more information, Palace Master Huang?" Wyrm 3 asked.

"Yes, and while they're at it, get them to cause some trouble as well, but make sure they don't get caught by any of the Infernal Region's forces," Huang Fuyu immediately replied.

Wyrm 3's eyes immediately lit up slightly upon hearing this, and she gave an affirmative response.

Yin Chengquan was discussing something with a regional monarch next to him when he shot a glance in Huang Fuyu's direction, and a peculiar look flashed through his eyes.

Right at this moment, his finger tightened once again as the purple mark on his ring also faded, and his smile instantly stiffened slightly.

......

Inside the restricted area.

Han Li's complexion was looking a little pale, and he stowed the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber before taking a pill.

Fox 3 and Shi Chuankong also took some pills to replenish their immortal spiritual power, while the light emanating from Daoist Xie's body had dimmed significantly.

Almost all of the immortal spiritual power in the Immortal Origin Stones in Daoist Xie's body had been sucked dry just now, rendering it barely even able to move.

Han Li took a glance at Daoist Xie, then swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of azure light that drew it into the Flower Branch domain.

He had left a large supply of Immortal Origin Stones in the Flower Branch space, and that would be enough for Daoist Xie to replenish its energy.

Fox 3 was ecstatic to see that the fox projection up above was beginning to gain the upper hand over Yin Chengquan, and he turned to Han Li and Shi Chuankong with an elated expression as he said, "Please take a quick rest, then we'll sever the remaining two chains. Once Patriarch Liu Qi is freed, he'll be able to lend you his protection so you can enter the third lightning pond."

"We can't do that," Han Li refused with a shake of his head.

"Why not? We're currently in a very perilous situation right now. Enemy reinforcements could come at any second, and without Patriarch Liu Qi's protection, there's no way you'll be able to enter the third lightning pond!" Fox 3 said with a slightly displeased expression.

"Please don't misunderstand, Fellow Daoist Fox 3. These Lightning Entrapment Chains are no ordinary restrictions, and Senior Liu Qi already spoke of the potential of suffering backlash from these chains earlier. The two of you haven't ever been in direct contact with these chains, so you wouldn't have felt it, but with each chain that was severed, both Senior Liu Qi and I were struck by backlash from the power that they contained.

“The lightning power imbued within these chains is extremely fearsome, and if I hadn't been baptized in the corresponding lightning ponds, thereby injecting a hint of their essential aura into my own body, there's no way I would've been able to withstand the backlash.

“Senior Liu Qi must've already been aware of this in advance, and that must be why he wanted us to enter the Baleful Cleansing Ponds before severing the chains," Han Li said as he lifted a hand, and a layer of purple light re-emerged over his body to demonstrate his point.

An enlightened look appeared on Fox 3's face upon hearing this, and he said, "I see, but right now, Patriarch Liu Qi won't be able to offer you his protection, so how will you be able to endure the remaining two lightning ponds?"

"Just as you said earlier, we're still in an extremely perilous situation right now, and life-threatening danger could descend upon us at any time. If I don't take a risk now, then perhaps I won't even get a chance to later. I must hold my fate in my own hands."

He flew over to the silver lightning pond as he spoke, then peered into it to discover that the arcs of lightning in this pond were far thinner than the ones in the previous two ponds, and they were giving off a forbidding sound that resembled the high-pitched calls of countless birds.

He took a deep breath, then gritted his teeth tightly as he jumped into the pond, upon which countless arcs of silver lightning instantly converged upon him in all directions.

The arcs of silver lightning were able to slice through his body with ease, and every single one of them was like a silver flying sword.

Han Li couldn't help but give a muffled groan as a hint of astonishment flashed through his eyes.

The silver lightning was several times more fearsome than the purple lightning, and his tremendous physical constitution was almost unable to protect him at all.

In the blink of an eye, his body had been shredded into ribbons.

At the same time, the silver lightning surged through his entire body, tearing his flesh and meridians into shreds, and blood was gushing out of all parts of his body, presenting a harrowing sight to behold.

The true spirit projections reappeared around him, having become significantly clearer once again, and they began to revolve around his body.

His muscles involuntarily bulged as he began to take on physical traits from all of the true spirit beings, and his true spirit bloodlines in his body were threatening to tear their way out, thereby further exacerbating his injuries.

An urgent look appeared in his eyes upon seeing this, and he knew that his body wouldn't be able to last at this rate.

However, if he wanted his baleful qi to be cleansed, then he couldn't keep out the silver lightning.

He gritted his teeth as he channeled his Great Universe Origin Arts once again, protecting only his internal organs as he allowed the arcs of silver lightning to wreak havoc throughout the rest of his body.

His baleful decay was also activated once again, but at this point, the impact that the baleful decay had on him was rather minimal, and the only real cause for concern was whether his body would be able to last.

The arcs of silver lightning were actively burrowing into the immortal acupoints that were contaminated by baleful qi as if they had a mind of their own, and more plumes of dense black qi began to rise up out of Han Li's body.

The rate of outflow of baleful qi was far faster than in the previous two lightning ponds, and with the expulsion of this baleful qi, Han Li felt as if his body were being liberated from a heavy load.

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to him, and he flipped a hand over to summon a silver pill.

It was none other than his final High Zenith Pill, and he swallowed it before immediately closing his eyes.

Meanwhile, Shi Chuankong was also staring into the silver lightning pond with tightly furrowed brows.

"Are you considering entering the pond as well, Brother Shi? Fellow Daoist Li has no choice, but you can wait until our patriarch is freed before you enter the pond," Fox 3 said.

"That may be true, but who knows if I can afford to wait that long? I've already taken so many risks to get here, how can I back down at the last second?" Shi Chuankong asked as a faint smile appeared on his face.

Fox 3 was just about to say something further when a black array suddenly appeared at the edge of the hall without any warning, following which a figure emerged within the array.

"Yin Gua!" Shi Chuankong exclaimed as he swung around with an alarmed expression.

Indeed, the person who had just arrived was none other than Yin Gua, the Great Encompassment Stage Gray Immortal from the Hundred Treasure Area.

As soon as Yin Gua appeared, he took a glance at Shi Chuankong and Fox 3, then immediately looked up into the air, where Yin Chengquan's spiritual sense avatar and the giant fox projection were facing each other from several thousand feet away.

Liu Qi took a glance at Yin Gua, then looked back at Yin Chengquan's spiritual sense avatar, and a cold sneer appeared on his face.

A hint of fear flashed through Yin Gua's eyes at the sight of Yin Chengquan, who turned to him before asking in a cold voice, "What are you doing here, Elder Yin Gua? Do you not know what this place is?"

"Please forgive me, Regional Monarch. You Luo betrayed our Infernal Tribe and freed those outsiders from the infernal prison, then led them here to free the Kun Hou. I had no choice but to pursue them to this point," Yin Gua hurriedly explained in a trembling voice as he extended an apologetic bow.

Chapter 765: Opposing a Great Encompassment Cultivator

A cold look flashed through Yin Chengquan's eyes, but he then said in a calm voice, "Given the urgency of the situation, your actions are understandable. However, it's still true that you've broken a sacred law of our tribe, but if you can kill these scoundrels, I'm willing to spare you of punishment."

"Thank you, Regional Monarch! Your generosity is truly unmatched!" Yin Gua hurriedly replied in an elated manner.

"Your ability to tell lies without even so much as batting an eyelid is truly impressive, Yin Chengquan. I've seen three people who've come here without your permission. One of them was a man named Yin Duo, right? He was also a Great Encompassment Stage Gray Immortal, but you still sucked him dry and threw him into the lightning pond," Liu Qi chuckled.

Yin Gua's expression changed slightly upon hearing this.

Elder Yin Duo's disappearance had always been extremely suspicious, and the circumstances behind his disappearance had never been confirmed. Everyone in the Infernal Tribe had thought that he was killed by people from the Reincarnation Region during an outing, but for some reason, Yin Chengquan hadn't seemed overly bothered by his disappearance.

With that in mind, it was all the more plausible that Yin Duo could've been killed by Yin Chengquan.

"Stop trying to drive a wedge between us, you sly old fox! I am the master of the Infernal Region, I wouldn't stoop as low as to say one thing, only to do another!" Yin Chengquan declared in a cold voice.

"Rest assured, Regional Monarch, I'll wipe out these pesky rats right away," Yin Gua vowed as he cupped his fist in a salute toward Yin Chengquan.

Yin Chengquan nodded in response, then turned his attention back to Liu Qi before charging straight at him.

"You got away once, but this time, I'll make sure to get the job done!" Yin Gua spat through gritted teeth as he turned Shi Chuankong and Fox 3.

Shi Chuankong took a glance at Han Li, who was still in the silver lightning pond, then turned back to face Yin Gua with a grim expression.

"We're in trouble now, Fellow Daoist Shi," Fox 3 said with a wry smile.

"Don't give up yet! If you have any more trump cards up your sleeves, then don't hide them any longer. He may be a Great Encompassment cultivator, but I can sense that his aura is still rather unstable after creating all those Infernal Soul Bugs. If we can last until Fellow Daoist Li comes out of the lightning pond, we'll still have a chance!" Shi Chuankong said.

"To think that a Golden Immortal and a Jade Immortal would dare to oppose me! How ludicrous!" Yin Gua harrumphed coldly as he removed a black seal from his waist before tossing it forward.

A streak of black light shot out of his hand, then instantly transformed into a millstone-sized black seal that hurtled directly toward Shi Chuankong, who immediately made a hand seal while rushing back in retreat.

However, the black seal abruptly sped up significantly, striking Shi Chuankong in the blink of an eye to send him flying before crashing into the wall behind him.

"Brother Shi!" Fox 3 cried out in alarm, but right at this moment, a ball of crimson light emerged over his body, and he exploded on the spot.

"Pathetic!" Yin Gua scoffed with a disdainful expression.

He then cast his gaze toward Han Li, who was still in the silver lightning pond, and a hint of fear flashed through his eyes at the sight of the raging silver lightning.

Right at this moment, his brows suddenly furrowed slightly as he turned his gaze to the black seal.

A burst of cracking was ringing out from behind the black seal, and a series of spatial rifts branched out around it, making the entire space appear rather warped and fractured.

Behind the seal, Shi Chuankong's hands were clasped in a strange seal, and in front of them was a walnut-sized white jade pendant that was giving off formidable spatial fluctuations, forming a barrier between him and the seal.

"I forgot that you had some spatial law powers up your sleeve," Yin Gua harrumphed coldly, then thrust a palm forward, and a resounding boom rang out as a burst of tremendous force erupted out of the black seal, instantly destroying the spatial barrier in its path.

The white jade pendant in front of Shi Chuankong's also exploded, while the black seal crashed into him with immense power, causing him to throw up a mouthful of blood as the wall behind him fractured into countless pieces.

All of a sudden, his body began to swell drastically in size, while large black scales emerged over his skin, and a layer of complex silver patterns appeared over his chest and limbs. His hair also grew rapidly, while his handsome features devolved into a monstrous visage, and in the blink of an eye, he had transformed into a giant demonic being that was over a thousand feet tall.

At the same time, four more arms had grown out of his back and his ribs, and they were also riddled with silver patterns.

Shi Chuankong thrust all six palms forward, releasing waves of silver light that struck the black seal, which had swelled to the size of a small mountain at this point.

A resounding boom rang out, and not only was the seal stopped cold in its tracks, it was even sent flying back to Yin Gua, who raised an eyebrow as he casually swept a sleeve through the air, upon which the seal flew back up his sleeve as a streak of black light.

"Is that all you've got? In that case, you can die now," Yin Gua scoffed with undisguised contempt, and he spread open the fingers of his other hand, upon which a ball of radiant black light emerged from the palm of his hand.

Right at this moment, Yin Gua felt a blur flash before his eyes, following which his flesh was instantly peeled back as a series of extremely vibrant crimson flowers sprouted out of his body.

The flower had extremely voluptuous petals that resembled luscious lips, and they were dotted with droplets of blood that resembled morning dew, presenting a harrowing sight to behold.

Yin Gua looked down to discover that his body seemed to be acting as sustenance for these crimson flowers, and his blood and energy were being rapidly sucked away.

A cold sneer appeared on his face as he remarked, "It's not every day that I get to see such beautiful flowers in the Gray Realm. If I wasn't in such a hurry, I'd perhaps stay in your little illusion for a while longer."

He was speaking in a very casual and nonchalant fashion, but internally, he was quite perplexed, wondering when he had fallen into this illusion.

As soon as his voice trailed off, he let loose a loud roar that caused the entire hall to tremble violently.

A burst of incredibly powerful energy fluctuations erupted out of his body, and the surrounding illusion was instantly eradicated.

Right at this moment, Fox 3's voice suddenly rang out.

"Now, Brother Shi!"

In the same instant that the illusion was destroyed, the sound of lute music rang out, and Yin Gua was greeted by the sight of Shi Chuankong charging directly at him, strumming the strings of a silver lute with his bloodstained fingers.

As the lute was played with more and more urgency, all of the patterns on it began to light up, following which a streak of radiant silver light appeared over the strings of a lute, resembling an arrow that was about to be fired.

A sense of instinctive foreboding welled up in Yin Gua's heart, and to his astonishment, he discovered that the streak of silver light really did seem to be able to pose a threat to him.

At this moment, Shi Chuankong was still in mid-air, and almost all of his immortal spiritual power had been sucked dry by the Virata Lute. His entire body was trembling uncontrollably, but his hands remained firm.

Right on the verge of completely exhausting his immortal spiritual power reserves, he released the strings of the lute, and the streak of silver light instantly shot forth.

The streak of light was fired at almost point blank range, and it instantly struck Yin Gua in the chest.

A faint crack rang out as the black seal appeared in front of Yin Gua's chest at the last second to block the streak of silver light.

However, the black seal was instantly split in half, and the streak of silver light continued onward without pause.

One half of the black seal fell to the ground, while the other half vanished into thin air.

Taking advantage of the split-second of time that the seal had bought for him, Yin Gua sped away to the side as an arc of black lightning, moving as quickly as Han Li when enhanced by his Reversal True Axis ability.

Even so, the arc of black lightning still wasn't able to completely evade the streak of silver light, and just like that half of the black seal, the section of the arc of lightning that was struck instantly disappeared without a trace.

The remaining arc of black lightning sped over to one side of the hall, following which Yin Gua emerged within it with an alarmed and furious look on his face.

He turned to discover that his entire left arm had disappeared along with his left shoulder, and there were still residual spatial law fluctuations lingering on his wound, preventing the flesh there from regenerating.

Chapter 766: Untitled

Yin Gua took a moment to compose himself, then cast his gaze forward to find Shi Chuankong crouching on the ground, trembling uncontrollably. His hands were a bloody mess, but he was still clutching onto the silver lute with all his might.

"That's an exceptional spatial immortal treasure you have there. If you were also a Great Encompassment cultivator, then I would be no match for you, it's just a pity that you're only a Golden Immortal," Yin Gua chuckled.

As soon as his voice trailed off, he spread open one of his hands, and balls of black baleful lightning erupted out of the palm of his hand in all directions, then rained down upon Shi Chuankong.

At this moment, Shi Chuankong was completely drained, and he didn't even have sufficient immortal spiritual power left to conjure up a layer of protective spiritual light.

In this dire situation, Fox 3 darted onto the scene, positioning himself in front of Shi Chuankong as nine thick and strong white fox tails appeared behind him before sweeping through the air toward the balls of black baleful lightning.

A string of violent explosions rang out as black lightning erupted in all directions.

Fox 3 let loose an agonized cry as lightning surged over his fox tails, and a numb sensation shot through his entire body, significantly hampering his immortal spiritual power circulation.

Before he had a chance to shake off the numb sensation, another thunderclap rang out as a vast expanse of black lightning descended upon him.

Yin Gua shot out of the black lightning, then stomped down onto Fox 3's shoulders with mountainous force.

Two bursts of black lightning shot out of the soles of his feet before piercing into Fox 3's shoulders, instantly pulverizing the bones in both shoulders, while half of his body sank into the ground from the force of the stomp.

"You clearly have a death wish, so I'll send you on your way first!"

A cold look flashed through Yin Gua's eyes as he curled the fingers of his right hand into claws, and black baleful lightning began to converge over the palm of his hand, following which he reached down toward the top of Fox 3's head.

In this instant, Fox 3 was completely immobilized, and he was plunged into the depths of despair.

Right at this moment, a rumbling thunderclap rang out as a streak of bright silver lightning shot out of the lightning pond, then flew onto the scene like a silver arrow, causing the nearby space to warp and twist.

Yin Gua immediately turned his attention to the streak of silver lightning, conjuring up five longan-sized black lightning beads on the tips of the fingers on his right hand before releasing them to clash against the streak of silver lightning.

A string of explosions rang out as the beads of baleful lightning exploded one after another, but the arcs of black lightning quickly dissipated, while the silver arrow continued to hurtle directly toward Yin Gua's chest, looking largely unharmed.

Yin Gua's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, and he hurriedly twisted around to protect his vital regions, but the streak of silver lightning was still able to tear a huge gash into his left side as it glanced past him.

A resounding boom rang out as Yin Gua was sent flying by the explosion of lightning, crashing heavily into the nearest wall.

From there, he looked down at the large gash on his left side with an incredulous expression.

Countless arcs of silver lightning continued to linger over the wound, devouring the baleful qi that was slowly seeping out of his body while constantly burrowing into his body like invasive insects.

Yin Gua extricated himself out of the wall before slowly descending to the ground, and the wall behind him instantly shattered into countless pieces that clattered to the ground.

He cast his gaze toward the lightning pond, and the fury in his eyes gradually faded, replaced by his usual cold expression.

At this moment, pillars of silver lightning were erupting out of the lightning pond, and Han Li was hovering above the lightning, making his way out of the pond.

At this moment, large sections of his skin had been charred black, and his robes were in tatters. Furthermore, his body was riddled with bright red cracks, seeping out of which were wisps of black baleful qi.

However, his eyes were extremely bright, and the gray coloration within them had completely faded, indicating that he barely had any baleful qi in his body left.

At this point, Fox 3 had already pulled himself out of the ground, and he hurriedly retreated to the edge of the lightning pond with Shi Chuankong, gritting his teeth through the pain as he fed a pill each to Shi Chuankong and himself. He then struggled up into a standing position as he cast a wary gaze toward Yin Gua, but at the same time, he couldn't help but glance at Han Li out of the corner of his eye.

He could sense that Han Li's aura was a little strange, and he asked through voice transmission, "How are you feeling, Brother Li?"

"Most of my baleful qi has already been cleansed, and my body and spiritual sense have also been refined. Now that I'm no longer burdened by baleful qi, I feel as if I've been reborn anew," Han Li replied.

However, he wasn't telling Fox 3 the entire truth. At this moment, his aura had reached the semi-High Zenith Stage, but it was different from back when Baili Yan had been on the cusp of the High Zenith Stage.

Due to the fact that he had taken that premium High Zenith Pill, both his body and mind had undergone some transformations, and some type of profound connection had been established between himself and the silver lightning pond, allowing him to break through that final bottleneck.

In fact, he had a feeling that as soon as he returned to the Immortal Realm, he would immediately attract an influx of the world's origin qi, allowing him to reach the High Zenith Stage.

Han Li took a glance at Weeping Soul and Liu Qi, who were still locked in a fierce battle against Yin Chengquan.

Even though this was only a spiritual sense avatar, it was definitely not to be looked down on, and it was able to hold its own just fine against the combined powers of Liu Qi and Weeping Soul.

"If I recall correctly, you've mastered the laws of time, so how are you able to wield the lightning in the Baleful Cleansing Pond?" Yin Gua asked.

Han Li offered no response as he gripped tightly onto a pair of mid-grade Immortal Origin Stones, rapidly absorbing the immortal spiritual power within them.

Nine Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were hovering around him, emanating azure light and arcs of golden lightning, while the Profound Heavenly Gourd was hanging from his waist.

Yin Gua swept his gaze over Han Li's trio, and he was feeling quite frustrated.

The residual spatial law power fluctuations lingering on the wound on his left shoulder weren't showing any signs of abating. By his estimates, it would most likely be several centuries before he could regrow that arm. Furthermore, the gash on his left side also wasn't going to be healing anytime soon with the residual silver lightning continuing to wreak havoc.

He had thought that he would be able to crush these three with ease, but things had certainly not gone according to plan.

Of course, this could also be attributed to the fact that he was still yet to completely consolidate his own cultivation base after his recent breakthrough to the Great Encompassment Stage, as well as the five Infernal Soul Bugs that he had conjured up earlier.

However, as a Great Encompassment cultivator, there were still more tricks up his sleeve, and he immediately sprang into action, sweeping his only remaining arm through the air to release a cloud of black mist, within which arcs of black lightning were crackling incessantly.

Several hundred spears formed by black baleful lightning quickly took shape, then hurtled directly toward Han Li's trio.

In response, all of Han Li's profound acupoints lit up, while a layer of golden scales emerged over his skin, and his suit of Xuanwu armor appeared over his body. After that, he stepped forward directly toward Yin Gua, making no attempt to take evasive measures.

In the face of the oncoming baleful lightning spears, the nine Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords hovering around Han Li shot forth to oppose them, and deafening explosions rang out as black baleful lightning and golden Divine Devilbane Lightning exploded incessantly.

With each explosion that rang out, an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword would be slowed down further, while the spiritual light emanating from them grew dimmer and dimmer.

Han Li had a very strong connection with his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, and each time a sword was struck, his immortal spiritual power and internal organs would tremble violently, causing blood to trickle down from the corners of his lips.

Even so, he still continued onward without pause.

Before long, all nine Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords had been struck down, and Han Li didn't even get a chance to retrieve them before more baleful lightning spears struck his suit of Xuanwu armor.

Blood came spewing out of Han Li's mouth as his suit of Xuanwu armor was instantly riddled with cracks, looking as if it could shatter at any moment, but he had gotten a lot closer to Yin Gua.

Right as the distance between them was closed down to less than a thousand feet, Han Li channeled his Reversal True Axis ability, shooting through the gaps between the black spears to reach Yin Gua in the blink of an eye, following which he began to summon his Mantra Treasured Axis.

If he were to release his Mantra Treasured Axis at such close quarters, even the Great Encompassment Stage Yin Gua would be sure to be severely affected, thereby allowing Han Li a chance to deal a grievous blow.

However, before Han Li had a chance to summon his Mantra Treasured Axis, a cold sneer appeared on Yin Gua's face, and a rumbling thunderclap suddenly rang out around Han Li as thick arcs of black baleful lightning appeared, then wrapped themselves around his limbs and torso to immobilize him in mid-air.

Immediately thereafter, Yin Gua made a grabbing motion, and a ball of black lightning instantly elongated into a black spear in the palm of his hand.

He didn't waste any more time as he plunged the baleful lightning spear directly toward Han Li's glabella, while Fox 3 and Shi Chuankong looked on with alarmed expressions.

Chapter 767: Baleful Domain

Right as Yin Gua's baleful lightning spear was about to pierce into Han Li's head, the nearby space suddenly began to ripple, following which several translucent chains emerged without any warning before piercing into Yin Gua's mind, completely unimpeded by the protective light barrier around him.

As a result, Yin Gua was instantly immobilized on the spot, and even his expression had completely stiffened.

At the same time, a layer of golden scales appeared over Han Li's arms, and he clenched his fists tightly while rushing forward with all his might, stretching the arcs of black baleful lightning around him, but they refused to snap.

Furthermore, they were constantly sending jolts of numbing force into his body, thereby further thwarting his efforts.

Fox 3 hesitated momentarily upon seeing this, then arrived behind Yin Gua in a flash before making a grabbing motion to summon the silver longsword from before.

Bursts of sword qi were surging out of the sword as he pierced it toward Yin Gua's chest from behind, but right as the tip of the sword was about to pierce into Yin Gua's body, Han Li's pupils suddenly contracted slightly as he hurriedly yelled, "Get back!"

Fox 3 immediately shot back in retreat without any hesitation upon hearing this, right as a black bead emerged on Yin Gua's glabella before exploding to release a burst of black light that snapped the spiritual sense chains in his mind.

Immediately thereafter, a fearsome aura erupted out of his body, and eight baleful lightning spears that resembled spider legs shot out of his back without any warning.

If Fox 3 hadn't retreated in time, he would've been impaled on the spot.

Yin Gua's body shuddered slightly, but he didn't do anything else. It seemed that his spiritual sense was still a little sluggish and disoriented after being freed from the Spiritual Sense Cage, and those eight baleful lightning spider spears had only been released out of self-preservation instincts.

Right at this moment, a burst of green light flashed from the mouth of Han Li's Profound Heavenly Gourd at his behest, immediately following which a vast expanse of silver lightning erupted out from within, forming a silver lightning net that enshrouded his entire body.

He had collected this silver lightning from the silver lightning pond, but the Profound Heavenly Gourd only had a limited tolerance for the lightning in the Baleful Cleansing Pond.

Filling the gourd with silver lightning was already potentially harmful to the gourd's spiritual nature, so Han Li didn't dare to try and draw any golden lightning into the gourd.

The silver lightning net clashed against the black baleful lightning, and the arcs of black lightning wrapped around his body instantly dissipated to free him.

At this point, retreat was no longer an option, and he sped directly toward Yin Gua as quickly as he could.

Meanwhile, Yin Gua had also returned to his senses, and upon sensing the approaching Han Li, he lashed out with all eight of his spider spears at once, bringing them together to conjure up a ball of black lightning the size of a human head, which hurtled directly toward Han Li.

The ball of black lightning didn't appear to be all that fearsome, but there were dozens of miniature lightning dragons circling around within it, waiting to be freed as soon as the ball of lightning was detonated.

A sense of foreboding welled up in Han Li's heart in the face of the ball of lightning, but he continued onward without pause, summoning the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber before swinging it down upon Yin Gua with both hands.

His immortal spiritual power surged rapidly into the saber, and all of the crimson patterns on its surface instantly lit up, conjuring up a giant saber projection that struck the ball of black lightning.

On the edge of the Baleful Cleansing Pond, Shi Chuankong had already recovered somewhat, and a peculiar look flashed through his eyes as he sat with his legs crossed, absorbing immortal spiritual power from a pair of Immortal Origin Stones.

After emerging from the silver lightning pond, Han Li had clearly become significantly more powerful, and this saber strike was already not inferior to the one that they had collectively unleashed to sever the azure lightning chain.

The saber projection struck the ball of lightning, and a deafening explosion instantly rang out, causing the entire hall to shudder violently.

Even Yin Chengquan and Liu Qi had their attention drawn to the commotion, while Weeping Soul was desperately praying for Han Li's welfare.

The miniature lightning dragons were struggling with all their might, but they were firmly suppressed and contained by the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber, while only some residual arcs of lightning managed to slip through the cracks to lash out at Han Li.

Han Li's hands were trembling incessantly as arcs of baleful lightning ravaged his entire body, sending plumes of smoke rising up into the air, while blood trickled out of his mouth and nostrils.

Even so, he gritted his teeth tightly and persevered with all his might as he forced the saber down bit by bit, slowly overwhelming the eight opposing spider spears.

A sinister look appeared in Yin Gua's eyes as he chanted a brief incantation, following which an indistinct insect projection suddenly appeared deep within his eyes.

At the exact same moment, a strange rune suddenly appeared on the body of the dormant slug-like Infernal Soul Bug in Han Li's mind, and it began to move again.

A cold sneer appeared on Yin Gua's face as he reached out with his only remaining hand, and five streaks of black light shot out of his fingertips, piercing through the black baleful lighting up ahead as it surged toward Han Li.

Han Li's brows furrowed tightly as he let loose a loud roar while channeling his Spirit Refinement Technique, and the spiritual sense chains around the Infernal Soul Bug instantly constricted, while several more chains emerged before piercing through its body, pinning it firmly to the spot.

These chains were giving off formidable spiritual sense that was manifested in the form of countless tiny runes, and the Infernal Soul Bug was immobilized once again.

As for the five streaks of black light that were hurtling toward Han Li's head, they had been scattered by the tremendous spiritual sense fluctuations erupting out of Han Li's mind.

"Impossible!"

Yin Gua was astonished to see this.

He was more aware than anyone of just how formidable Infernal Soul Bugs were, yet Han Li's spiritual sense had been enhanced to such an extent through his baptisms in the three lightning ponds that he was now able to dominate the Infernal Soul Bug.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged as he injected even more immortal spiritual power into the saber in his hands, and the ball of black lightning was finally sliced into two, while the eight spider spears also caved.

The Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber plunged straight down, slicing Yin Gua cleanly in half from the top of his head down through his chest and abdomen, but the two halves of his body remained hovering in mid-air as he sneered, "It's extremely impressive that a semi-High Zenith cultivator like yourself was able to force me to use my baleful spirit as a substitution to take that lethal blow, but this is as far as you go!"

Immediately thereafter, his body exploded violently, sending a vast expanse of black lightning spreading in all directions.

At the same time, the ball of black lightning also exploded, and the lightning dragon projections within it instantly crashed straight into Han Li's chest.

The suit of Xuanwu armor re-emerged over his body, only to instantly shatter upon contact with the lightning dragon projections, and before Han Li even had a chance to cry out, his saber had slipped out of his grasp, while his body was severely ravaged and came drifting down like a raft in a turbulent sea.

A sense of despair welled up in Fox 3's heart as he looked on from afar, while Weeping Soul hurriedly attempted to rush over to Han Li's side, only to be instantly stopped in her tracks by Yin Chengquan's spiritual sense avatar.

In the next instant, the arcs of baleful lightning that had scattered through the air converged to form a spherical black light barrier that encompassed Han Li's entire body.

The black light barrier was extremely dense and virtually completely opaque, and incredibly thick arcs of black lightning emerged within it, stretching out Han Li's limbs so that he was forced to hover in mid-air in a spreadeagled fashion.

Immediately thereafter, a ball of black baleful lightning appeared in front of him before taking on the form of Yin Gua.

"You've got quite a few true spirit bloodlines in your body, and your physical constitution is also exceptional. Once I refine you with my baleful lightning, that should be enough to replenish the energy I've exerted in this battle, and I may even be able to further consolidate my cultivation base," Yin Gua mused, and he was looking rather pale from overexertion.

His body swelled to over a hundred feet tall as he spoke, and a giant mouth-like opening abruptly split open from his lower abdomen before sucking Han Li into his belly.

"You have to fight back, Master! He's using his baleful domain!" Weeping Soul called out frantically, and in her moment of distraction, she was sent flying by a swat from Yin Chengquan before crashing into the wall, where she was embedded into the rock face.

Several seconds later, the spherical black light barrier faded, and Yin Gua emerged from within it.

With Han Li nowhere to be seen, Shi Chuankong heaved an internal sigh as a hint of despair flashed through his eyes.

Meanwhile, Yin Gua made a beckoning motion, and all of the arcs of surrounding baleful lightning converged toward the palm of his hand.

Chapter 768: Come From Behind

Yin Gua took a glance at the spot where his arm had been severed, then turned to Shi Chuankong with a sinister grin as he chuckled, "I'm terribly sorry to have kept you waiting for so long."

He then began to slowly make his way toward Shi Chuankong, who was looking on with tightly furrowed brows.

At this point, he had already released the Immortal Origin Stones in his hands and was making a strange hand seal. He could feel a burning pain on his back as a sealed rune began to appear on his skin.

Activating the rune would incur an extremely heavy cost, so it was only ever to be used as a last resort, and this was truly his final trump card.

Right as Shi Chuankong was steeling himself to make a final stand, Yin Gua's expression suddenly changed drastically as a rumbling thunderclap rang out from within his lower abdomen, following which a burst of silver light that was as radiant as the sun appeared.

Immediately thereafter, countless arcs of silver lightning erupted forth, tearing a huge gash open on his lower abdomen, following which waves of scorching silver flames surged out into the open.

A sharp cry rang out as a giant silver fire raven flew out of Yin Gua's abdomen, then circled around in mid-air before pouncing at his chest.

Standing on the fire raven's back was none other than Han Li, although he was looking very much worse for wear.

Everyone was completely astonished by this incredible turn of events, while Weeping Soul struggled out of the rock face, paying no heed to her own injuries as she stared intently at Han Li with an anxious expression.

Yin Chengquan's expression darkened significantly upon seeing this, while Liu Qi was looking on with a combination of surprise and elation in his eyes, with the former far outweighing the latter.

A resounding boom rang out as the silver fire raven crashed into Yin Gua's chest, instantly setting his entire body alight with silver flames.

"What the hell is this thing?!" Yin Gua yelled in a horrified voice, and baleful lightning was surging incessantly over his body, but he was unable to struggle free from the silver flames.

Just like the silver lightning from the Baleful Cleansing Pond, these silver flames were extremely potent against him.

Unbeknownst to him, after devouring the three balls of Rainbow Fire Pill Sand, the power of the Essence Fire Raven's flames had already reached the High Zenith Stage. If Han Li hadn't forcibly awoken it prematurely, the power of its flames would've been able to reach at least the late-High Zenith Stage.

Furthermore, the Essence Fire Raven was a natural bane of baleful qi, and it had erupted from within Yin Gua's body, so it was naturally particularly potent.

Shi Chuankong and Fox 3 were naturally ecstatic to see this, while Yin Chengquan's expression darkened even further, and Liu Qi was observing Han Li with a thoughtful look in his eyes.

Despite Yin Gua's desperate struggles, the silver flames refused to be extinguished.

Right at this moment, a streak of black light suddenly shot out of the fire, and a miniature black figure appeared within it, then vanished into thin air amid a flash of lightning before Han Li and the others could intervene.

Meanwhile, Yin Gua's body crashed to the ground, having already been reduced to a charred corpse.

Han Li jumped down from the Essence Fire Raven's back, then made a beckoning motion to retrieve the scattered Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords on the ground, but they were rather reluctant to return to him.

His brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and only after placing more focus on his spiritual connection with the swords was he able to just barely draw them back into his body.

After that, he also drew the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber into his grasp before flying over to Yin Gua's body.

Following a brief examination, he discovered a white bone badge hanging from his waist, and he removed it before stowing it away.

Meanwhile, the Essence Fire Raven reverted back into a miniature silver figure before landing on Han Li's shoulder, still looking very sleepy.

"Are you alright, Master?" Weeping Soul hurriedly asked as she flew over to his side.

"I'm fine. How about you?" Han Li asked.

"I'm alright. He still seems to want to use me, so he held back against me, and my injuries aren't very severe," Weeping Soul replied with a sullen expression.

Right at this moment, Fox 3 hurriedly approached them with a concerned expression, then urged, "I'm sorry to call upon you right after such a grueling battle, Brother Li, but Patriarch Liu Qi still needs our help."

Han Li turned to discover that without Weeping Soul's assistance, the tables had been completely turned, and Yin Chengquan had gained a clear upper hand.

"I'll go help him, Master," Weeping Soul immediately volunteered.

"There's no hurry. Senior Liu Qi will be able to last some time on his own, so let's take this time to replenish our immortal spiritual power, then sever the third chain. If we can do that, Senior Liu Qi's powers will be drastically enhanced, and he'll be able to defeat Yin Chengquan even without our help," Han Li replied.

"Each successive chain seems to be more powerful than the previous one, are you sure you'll be able to sever this third chain, Brother Li?" Fox 3 asked with slightly furrowed brows.

"Rest assured, I'm 70% confident that I'll be able to sever the silver chain, but prior to that, I'll need to recover as much immortal spiritual power as possible," Han Li replied.

With that, everyone quickly sat down with their legs crossed and began to focus on rest and recuperation.

......

At the conference venue.

The atmosphere was still as tense as ever, and things were beginning to get a little awkward.

Huang Fuyu's brows furrowed slightly as he proposed, "Regional Monarch Yin, at this point, there's no reason to delay things any further, so let's get to the vote."

However, Yin Chengquan didn't seem to have heard him at all, and he was sitting in silence with a thoughtful look on his face while playing with the gray ring on his left pinky finger.

"Palace Master Huang is right, Regional Monarch Yin. Everything that needs to be discussed has already been discussed, so let's commence the vote," Xiao Buye echoed in a slightly louder voice.

Only then did Yin Chengquan suddenly snap back to his senses, and a slightly stiff smile appeared on his face as he said, "According to the conference schedule, it's still not time to vote yet, so let's wait a while longer."

As soon as his voice trailed off, his right hand suddenly shot back into his sleeve as if he had been stung, and an incredulous look flashed through his eyes as he looked down at the ring on his left hand, where the silver mark had suddenly began flashing slightly.

He had done well to conceal this sequence of actions, but it hadn't escaped Huang Fuyu's notice.

At this point, Huang Fuyu was beginning to feel a little bewildered. He had come into this conference feeling very apprehensive, thinking that the Infernal Tribe was up to no good, but at this point, Yin Chengquan was currently the one looking the most uneasy out of three leading figures at the conference, and it seemed like the Infernal Tribe was truly dealing with a lot of trouble.

Yin Chengquan was just about to rise to his feet when his expression changed once again, and this time, he was so shocked that he had even forgotten to conceal his own astonishment.

"What's wrong, Regional Monarch Yin? Has there been a turn in the situation over at the Soul Cleansing Area? If you require assistance, I'm sure all of the regional monarchs present would be willing to lend you a hand," Huang Fuyu said with a smile.

"That won't be necessary. This is an internal affair of our Infernal Tribe, so I won't bother all of you. I was only thinking about the proposition that you had just raised," Yin Chengquan replied as his expression returned to normal.

Huang Fuyu raised an eyebrow upon seeing this, then suddenly asked through voice transmission, "Wyrm 3, have our spies in Asura City unearthed any more information?"

"There have been some further updates, but we still don't know exactly what's happening. All I've been told is that there's been a major crisis in the Soul Cleansing Area, and the nearby Tarmin Area, Hundred Treasure Area, and Bitter Lake Area have all been placed under lockdown.

“The Great Encompassment cultivator stationed in the Bitter Lake Area, Yin Lin, has also traveled to the Soul Cleansing Area, but it seems like the situation over there is only continuing to escalate," Wyrm 3 replied.

"Judging from Yin Chengquan's reaction, things must really have taken a drastic turn for the worse," Huang Fuyu mused with a faint smile.

"Are you considering following Palace Master Huang's proposal to commence the vote now?" Xiao Buye asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"There are still a lot of conflicting opinions, so I don't think this is the best time to be holding a vote. How about we temporarily adjourn the conference, then continue our discussion some other day? After all, this conference concerns the future direction of our Gray Realm, so a decision should not be made lightly," Yin Chengquan replied with a smile.

Xiao Buye immediately shook his head vigorously upon hearing this.

"Asura City is not a readily accessible place for us all, and many of us have had to make very long journeys to get here. In light of that, it would be far too unreasonable to adjourn the conference and expect everyone to make the same journey again some other time."

"That was never my intention, Regional Monarch Xiao. The next time the conference recommences, I suggest holding it in your Black Rope Region," Yin Chengquan replied.

"That would still be far too inconvenient for everyone, Regional Monarch Yin. It's not like we're in a hurry to reach a decision, we could easily just extend the conference. As long as we can arrive at a decision that satisfies the majority, I'm sure everyone would be willing to wait a few more days," Huang Fuyu said, and all of a sudden, it seemed that he was no longer in a hurry.

A subtle hint of displeasure flashed through Yin Chengquan's eyes upon hearing this, then turned to Xiao Buye asked as he asked, "What do you think, Regional Monarch Xiao?"

The drastic turns in the attitudes of Yin Chengquan and Huang Fuyu had tipped Xiao Buye off to the situation at hand, and he pretended to consider the question for a moment, then gave a response that he had already prepared in his mind.

"Both proposals have their merits, but our Gray Realm has already been fractured for a very long time, and the lack of consensus on what course of action should be taken against the Immortal Realm has long been a source of unease and contention.

“My concern is that if we keep delaying things, our Gray Realm will only continue to become more fractured and divided, to the point that things could become untenable. Hence, I think we should make a decision right away and not postpone the decision to another day."

Chapter 769: Postponing the Debate

"Regional Monarch Xiao, I'm afraid that our Infernal Region cannot support the Reincarnation Region's stance. Our Infernal Region has no problem with resisting Immortal Realm invasions, but establishing a passageway between our two realms to attack the Immortal Realm is a step too far.

“Setting aside how costly it would be to maintain such a passageway over long periods of time, if a spiritual qi influx from the Immortal Realm is triggered, that would spell disaster for our entire realm!" Yin Chengquan said.

"You can rest assured on that front, Regional Monarch Yin. Our Reincarnation Region already has a complete plan prepared with regard to an interrealm passageway, and if we can all reach a consensus, then our Reincarnation Region would be happy to reveal this plan for all to see," Huang Fuyu replied.

"If you already have a plan prepared, then why not reveal it now? Once Regional Monarch Xiao and I have seen it, our qualms will be eased, and we'll be more open and receptive to your Reincarnation Region's stance on this matter," Yin Chengquan sneered.

"This is a closely guarded secret of our Reincarnation Region, and there aren't many people aware of this even in our region. Hence, before our three regions can reach a consensus, I won't be leaking any information," Huang Fuyu replied in a stoic fashion.

"If you keep arguing like this, the debate could go on for centuries without reaching a decisive outcome! I think that our top priority should be to address the division currently in our Gray Realm. As for our stance against the Immortal Realm, that's a subject that I think can be set aside to be discussed another time," Xiao Buye proposed with a smile.

"I think that's a good suggestion, Regional Monarch Xiao," Yin Chengquan replied without any hesitation. "What do you think, Palace Master Huang?"

"I think by doing this, we'll only be avoiding the true topic of contention, and the outcome will be that our three regions will be united on the surface, but in reality, we've only smoothed over the cracks instead of actually filling them," Huang Fuyu countered with slightly furrowed brows.

"In the past, there have been many conflicts between the regions, and even though none have resulted in severe casualties, it's still a form of infighting that should be eliminated. If our three regions can agree to unite as one, then no one will attack the others for fear of retaliation from both of the other two regions," Xiao Buye said with a smile.

"That may be true, but even if an alliance is to be formed, someone must lead the alliance. I'm sure Fellow Daoist Huang wouldn't agree to let me serve as alliance leader, and similarly, I'm not willing to allow the role to fall into the hands of the Incarnation Region.

“With that in mind, I think it would be best for Regional Monarch Xiao to serve as alliance leader for now. As for whether that's subject to change in the future, that'll depend on the outcome of the next conference," Yin Chengquan said.

Huang Fuyu heaved an internal sigh upon seeing this. Ultimately, it was Xiao Buye who was the main beneficiary of this conflict.

Even so, at the very least, a relatively stable environment had been created. Without any foul play from the Infernal Region, the Reincarnation Region would be able to better focus on its plans. Furthermore, judging from the reactions of the monarchs present, it seemed that many regions were in support of the Reincarnation Region's stance.

With more time for the Reincarnation Region to win over smaller regions, Huang Fuyu was confident that he would be able to secure a crushing victory in the next conference.

With that in mind, Huang Fuyu nodded as he said, "Our Reincarnation Region has no objections to this proposal."

Xiao Buye didn't try to contest this outcome, and he smiled as he said, "I am truly honored to be receiving such a prestigious role, and I'll be sure to step down once an outcome is reached in the next conference."

In light of this outcome, no vote was required for now, and Yin Chengquan proposed, "In that case, let's decide a time for the next conference..."

......

Shortly thereafter, the conference drew to a conclusion, and the tribes from the Reincarnation and Black Rope Regions departed from the Fallen Lake Area, traveling toward the city gates of Asura City.

Among the long convoy of carriages, the carriage of the San Miao Tribe was rather nondescript, and Miao Xiu and Miao Gao were seated within it.

"Father, do you think those three were responsible for what happened in Asura City?" Miao Xiu suddenly asked in a quiet voice.

Miao Gao immediately made a quieting gesture upon hearing this, then replied through voice transmission, "Regardless of whether they had anything to do with it, don't ever mention those three to anyone. We've never met them, and we don't know of their existence, do you understand?"

Miao Xiu nodded in response, then turned to look out the window of the carriage with a thoughtful expression.

Meanwhile, Wyrm 3 was standing behind the railing of a giant octagonal carriage, and she was looking out at the Soul Cleansing Area with a peculiar look on her face.

Right at this moment, Huang Fuyu emerged from the carriage, then asked, "What's wrong, Jiuzhen?"

"I can't help but feel like that entire conference was very strange, Uncle Huang. What could've possibly happened to trigger such a drastic change in the Infernal Tribe's attitude?" Wyrm 3 asked with slightly furrowed brows.

"I don't know the answer to that, but in any case, the outcome was a positive one for us," Huang Fuyu replied with a smile.

"We had all those measures prepared in case Yin Chengquan tried any funny business, but I'm glad things ended as peacefully as they did," Wyrm 3 said with a smile of her own.

......

In the Baleful Cleansing Ponds, the white fox projection was hovering proudly in the sky while panting slightly.

Not far in front of it stood Yin Chengquan's spiritual sense avatar, and a massive hole had been blasted into its chest, almost splitting its body into two, while its eyes were completely dull and devoid of luster.

The fox projection harrumphed coldly before flying back into Liu Qi's glabella, while the remains of Yin Chengquan's spiritual sense avatar dissipated into specks of translucent light.

Standing beside Liu Qi, Weeping Soul's complexion was deathly pale, and she was barely able to remain standing.

The four musical instruments around Liu Qi reverted back into four balls of black light that flew back into her body, following which she began to fall to the ground, unable to hold herself upright any longer.

A streak of azure light flew over to catch her, following which Han Li appeared beside her with his brows tightly furrowed with concern.

"I'm fine, Master, it's just that I've overexerted my soul power from playing the Crying Soul Melody for so long," Weeping Soul assured with a forced smile.

However, Han Li's concern wasn't assuaged at all upon hearing this.

At this moment, Weeping Soul was in terrible condition. Her face was completely devoid of color, and her aura had become extremely feeble.

Even though the Crying Soul Melody had ceased, her aura was still growing feebler by the second.

Han Li raised a hand to summon several black pills, all of which flew into Weeping Soul's mouth, and at the same time, he cast a string of incantation seals into her body to help her digest the pills faster.

A layer of black light emerged over Weeping Soul's body, but it wasn't having much of an effect at all.

Han Li's expression darkened even further upon seeing this, and he was at a temporary loss for what to do.

Right at this moment, Liu Qi turned to Weeping Soul, and a burst of translucent light shot out of his glabella before vanishing into her body.

A layer of translucent light instantly appeared around her, and a hint of color quickly returned to her cheeks, while her aura was also immediately stabilized.

With Han Li's help, she was able to get into a seated position, and her aura quickly began to recover, much to Han Li's relief.

As expected, a Dao Ancestor's powers were far beyond those of a semi-High Zenith cultivator like himself.

Fox 3 flew over to Liu Qi's side with an excited expression, but before he had a chance to say anything, Liu Qi turned to Han Li with an urgent expression as he said, "Now's not the time to be celebrating. Yin Chengquan is most likely already on the way here! Now that you've overcome your baleful decay and attained a Jade Immortal Physique, the lightning in these Baleful Cleansing Ponds won't pose much of a threat to you anymore.

“Enter the final golden lightning pond right away so you can absorb its aura, then sever the final Lightning Entrapment Chain."

Han Li turned to the golden lightning pond upon hearing this, and he discovered that it was filled with incredibly thin arcs of golden lightning that were better described as strands.

These strands of golden lightning were extremely bright, and they occasionally converged to take on all types of different forms, such as balls, rings, or mountains, presenting a profound sight to behold.

Furthermore, every single strand of lightning was giving off formidable lightning law power fluctuations that caused the nearby space to tremble incessantly.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this. The golden lightning pond was clearly far more powerful than the silver lightning pond, and even though he was on the cusp of the High Zenith Stage, he still wasn't confident in his ability to withstand such a stern test.

However, just as Liu Qi had said, Yin Chengquan was sure to react to the demise of his spiritual sense avatar, and there was no telling when the enemy would be arriving, so they had to free Liu Qi as soon as possible.

A concerned look appeared on Shi Chuankong's face as he said, "Fellow Daoist Li, the lightning in the golden lightning pond is extremely formidable. Are you sure..."

Before he had a chance to finish, Han Li interjected, "Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Shi. I'll be in your care then, Senior Liu Qi."

After that, he sprang into the golden lightning pond without any hesitation.

Chapter 770: Evolution

As soon as Han Li entered the golden lightning pond, all of the lightning inside instantly began to churn violently amid bursts of thunderous rumbling, and countless balls of golden lightning took shape before converging toward him from all directions in a frenzy.

Han Li naturally wasn't just going to resign himself to his fate. In the instant that he entered the lightning pond, his body instantly swelled drastically in size, while a layer of golden scales appeared over his skin.

Immediately thereafter, his entire body was inundated by golden lightning, filling the entire hall with blinding golden radiance.

Liu Qi's eyes narrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he chanted a rapid incantation, then grabbed onto the golden chain with one of his tails before giving it a strong tug.

The light emanating from the golden chain instantly brightened significantly as arcs of lightning emerged over its surface, drawing the majority of lightning from the pond to alleviate the pressure on Han Li.

At the same time, he opened his mouth to release a ball of white light, which then instantly exploded into dozens of streaks of white light that shot forth in all directions before vanishing into all parts of the hall.

The patterns in the giant array on the ground quickly turned white, and the stone gate at the entrance slammed shut with a resounding boom.

In the blink of an eye, all of the array patterns in every corner of the entire hall had lit up, and all of a sudden, it was as if the hall had become completely isolated from the outside world, forming a separate space of its own.

"This is a Xumi Domain!" Shi Chuankong exclaimed.

Liu Qi had just unleashed a type of spatial secret technique capable of completely severing a place from the outside world, and if an outsider wished to enter the space, their only option would be to completely destroy it.

Shi Chuankong took a long glance at Liu Qi, then suddenly flew over to the silver lightning pond.

"What are you doing, Brother Shi?" Fox 3 hurriedly asked.

"The baleful qi in my body is still yet to be fully eradicated, so I'm going to continue my baleful cleansing," Shi Chuankong replied with a smile.

"You've witnessed the power of the silver lightning array, even Fellow Daoist Li only just barely managed to survive it. As opposed to taking such a huge risk now, you should wait until Patriarch Liu Qi is completely freed," Fox 3 advised with slightly furrowed brows.

"Right now, the situation outside is constantly changing, and enemies could arrive at any moment, so I can't afford to delay any longer. Thank you for your concern, Brother Fox, but I must enter this lightning pond, even if I am to die in there!" Shi Chuankong replied with a determined expression, then leaped into the silver lightning pond before Fox 3 had a chance to say anything else.

Fox 3 could only shake his head before turning his gaze to the golden lightning pond.

As time passed, the golden lightning within the pond had begun to conjure up different objects such as lightning beads and lightning rings, all of which were bombarding Han Li relentlessly.

Even though Han Li's physical body had already reached the High Zenith Stage, he was struggling to withstand the assault, and his skin had turned bright red, while his entire body was riddled with countless tiny bleeding gashes that were healing just as quickly as they appeared.

Han Li's eyes were tightly shut as he remained completely still in the golden lightning pond, but veins were bulging on his forehead, and all of his muscles were squirming incessantly. It was clear that he was enduring indescribable agony, but at the same time, he was also channeling his Great Universe Origin Arts to protect his own internal organs.

Having endured the three previous lightning ponds, he had already gleaned many secrets about them, and that allowed him to absorb the aura of the lightning pond faster than before.

At the moment, time was of the essence, and he had to absorb the aura of the golden lightning pond as quickly as possible, then sever the golden chain.

Before long, the arcs of golden lightning had managed to break through the defenses of his skin, and they immediately burrowed their way into his body, severing all of the flesh and meridians in their wake.

The lightning law powers imbued within the arcs of lightning also rapidly spread through his body, striking him with a numb sensation that completely immobilized him while also rendering him unable to control his own immortal spiritual power circulation.

Han Li was naturally greatly alarmed by this development. With both his body and his immortal spiritual power in an immobile state, he had lost the ability to leave the lightning pond.

A hint of anger quickly welled up in his heart, and he was furious that Liu Qi hadn't warned him about this beforehand.

Having already been trapped here for so long, Han Li was certain that Liu Qi would've been aware that this would happen.

However, this wasn't the time to be pointing fingers, and Han Li was forced to focus all of his efforts on resisting the influx of lightning law powers.

However, these lightning law powers were extremely formidable, and they were surging into his body in waves, exacerbating the numb sensation.

A burst of lightning law powers also surged into his mind and wrapped itself around his soul, causing his spiritual sense to become stagnant as well.

Following Yin Gua's demise, the Infernal Soul Bug in his soul had remained completely still, as if it had perished, but in the face of this influx of lightning law powers, it suddenly began to struggle violently while screeching in an agonized fashion.

At the same time, it was desperately trying to burrow deeper into Han Li's soul in order to escape from the lightning law powers, but it was already too late, and golden lightning runes had already begun surging in its body.

The Infernal Soul Bug abruptly began to swell rapidly in size, following which it exploded into a cloud of black qi amid a dull thump.

Han Li's soul shuddered violently, causing his vision to black out for a moment, but the disturbance wasn't that severe, and with his tremendous spiritual sense, he was able to quickly recover.

The Infernal Soul Bug in his soul had always been a concern of his. Perhaps it wouldn't be able to do anything now that Yin Gua was dead, but ultimately, it was certainly not a good thing to have such a potential threat lurking in his soul, and his eradication came as quite a relief.

However, his relief quickly turned to concern once again as the power of his Great Universe Origin Arts was quickly stripped away by the influx of lightning law powers, following which the lightning law powers began to infiltrate his internal organs.

Han Li gave a muffled groan as blood began to trickle down from the corner of his lips, and right as he was considering taking some drastic measures, the seventy-two Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords in his dantian suddenly stirred slightly, then began devouring all of the incoming lightning law powers.

Han Li faltered slightly upon seeing this, following which a hint of elation appeared in his eyes.

He didn't know why this was happening, but the lightning law powers in his dantian had faded, allowing him to regain control over the immortal spiritual power there.

He was just about to channel his immortal spiritual power to try and keep out the surrounding lightning when the seventy-two Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords suddenly flew out of his dantian altogether, then began to circle through the air around him.

As they did so, they began to rapidly devour the lightning law powers within the lightning pond, doing so with a great deal of eagerness and urgency.

Countless tiny golden lightning runes began to appear around the swords, and they were giving off lightning law power fluctuations that caused the nearby space to buzz and tremble incessantly.

Meanwhile, the lightning law powers in Han Li's body were quickly fading away, as was the numb sensation that had immobilized him this entire time.

The elation on his face became even more pronounced upon seeing this, and it was intermingled with a hint of excitement.

The Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were his bonded treasure, so he had an extremely close spiritual connection with them, and at this moment, he could sense that the swords were undergoing a process of evolution from devouring the lightning law powers in this lightning pond.

Having devoured so much sword essence in the Infernal Frost Immortal Manor, the set of swords had been imbued with tremendous spiritual power, and each of them was comparable in power to most immortal treasures.

However, they contained no law powers, so they were made to look rather inferior in the face of some graded immortal treasures, but it seemed that they were finally about to make the leap to become graded immortal treasures themselves.

Han Li suppressed the excitement in his heart as he channeled his Great Universe Origin Arts once again to protect his own body, warding off the surrounding golden lightning while carefully observing his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

These were his bonded treasures, and he had to make absolute certain that no harm befell them.

A hint of surprise appeared on Fox 3's face as he saw what was happening in the golden lightning pond, and Liu Qi also turned his gaze to Han Li with an intrigued expression.

The seventy-two Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were circling rapidly around Han Li, and the lightning law runes around them were rapidly expanding in size, while the lightning law powers that they were giving off were also becoming steadily more formidable.

The flying swords themselves were also rapidly swelling in size, having already become several dozen feet in size, and they resembled seventy-two sharks that were swimming joyfully through the lightning pond while devouring the lightning law powers within like seventy-two bottomless pits.

Han Li wasn't surprised at all to see this.

He knew that the law powers imbued within an immortal treasure was related to the materials used to refine it, the spiritual power that it contained, and the degree to which it had been nurtured. If an immortal treasure had been refined from inferior materials or was of an unsuitable attribute, then there was a very good chance that it could break during an injection of law powers.

Exceptional materials had been used to refine these Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, and they also contained immense spiritual power. On top of that, they had either been nurtured in Han Li's body or within the Profound Heavenly Gourd this entire time, and with such a strong foundation, it naturally stood to reason that they could contain an immense amount of law powers.

He had refrained from elevating this set of flying swords into true immortal treasures this entire time as he hadn't been able to find a source of law powers of sufficient volume to support this process, but the opportunity had suddenly presented itself to him.

Chapter 771: Utmost Urgency

Han Li could see that the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were continuing to devour the lightning law powers within the lightning pond without any adverse side-effects, so he began to focus on himself, closing his eyes to inspect his own internal condition.

It was naturally a good thing that the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were evolving, but his top priority at the moment was to absorb the aura of the lightning pond as soon as possible.

All of a sudden, various true spirit projections appeared around his body once again, and they were far clearer than before, with every single one of them giving off formidable true spirit bloodline auras.

Han Li's body was rapidly swelling and morphing, but with his physical body greatly enhanced, the true spirit bloodlines weren't having anywhere near as potent an effect on him as they were earlier.

Aside from these true spirit projections, arcs of golden lightning had also surfaced over his body, and they began to fuse together, forming a radiant cloak of golden lightning.

In the next instant, Han Li's eyes abruptly sprang open, following which he shot up into the air as a golden shadow.

Just like in the three previous lightning ponds, the golden lightning in the pond immediately set off in pursuit of Han Li, forming a giant golden lightning net that wrapped itself around him.

The net of golden lightning was extremely dense, and it was further bolstered by countless lightning law runes, stopping Han Li cold in his tracks.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, but before he had a chance to do anything, huge streaks of azure sword qi suddenly erupted out of the lightning pond in all directions, slicing through the surrounding space with ease.

The golden lightning net was instantly shredded into countless pieces, and the sword qi seemed to have a mind of its own, making sure to skirt around Han Li to ensure that he remained unharmed.

Fox 3's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, and he hurriedly shot back in retreat.

He had reacted very quickly, but the eruption of sword qi had been far too abrupt, and a deep gash had still been sliced into his arm, one that was bleeding profusely.

Specks of green light emerged over the gash on his arm, and the injury quickly began to heal, while Fox 3 cast his gaze toward the sword qi in the golden lightning pond with a hint of wariness in his eyes.

The sword qi was extremely formidable, and he was extremely fortunate that he had been standing quite far away to begin with and had reacted very quickly. Otherwise, if he had been swept up in the midst of the sword qi, then the consequences would've been catastrophic.

Right at this moment, Han Li flew out of the sword qi before landing beside the lightning pond, then promptly took a pill.

Bursts of green light emerged over the wounds on his body as well, and the gashes quickly healed within a matter of seconds.

The boundless sword qi within the lightning pond also quickly faded away, while the rifts that they had sliced into the nearby space were sealed again.

Immediately thereafter, the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords came flying out of the lightning pond one after another, and their outward appearance had changed drastically.

All of the swords had become such a bright green color that they were virtually transparent, and they were riddled with golden lightning-shaped patterns, while arcs of thick golden lighting were flashing around them.

In the blink of an eye, all seventy-two flying swords had flown out of the lightning pond, and every single one of them was giving off tremendous sword qi fluctuations that were several times more powerful than before, placing them at least on par with the few graded immortal treasures in Han Li's possession.

The seventy-two Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords circled around Han Li momentarily as a series of golden shadows, then returned to his dantian.

Han Li could sense the tremendous power within the seventy-two Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, and a faint smile of elation crept onto his face.

Right at this moment, Fox 3 flew over to him, then cupped his fist in a congratulatory salute as he said, "Congratulations, Fellow Daoist Li. Have you managed to absorb the aura of the golden lightning pond?"

"Rest assured, Brother Fox, I wouldn't have come out of the lightning pond if I hadn't absorbed its aura," Han Li replied with a smile, and a layer of golden lightning flashed over his body as he spoke.

A hint of elation and excitement flashed through Liu Qi's eyes upon seeing this, while Weeping Soul was roused from her meditation by the sound of Han Li's voice.

"Master!" she called out as she rose to her feet before approaching Han Li.

At this point, her complexion had already improved significantly, while her aura was also mostly recovered. It was unclear what type of secret technique she had used, but her recovery had been remarkably fast.

Han Li gave Weeping Soul a nod, and he was just about to say something when Shi Chuankong suddenly flew out of the silver lightning pond amid a deafening thunderclap.

At this moment, he was in an extremely sorry state. An entire layer of flesh and skin had been peeled away from his body, revealing a series of ribs on his lower abdomen, while the skin and flesh on his arms had almost been completely stripped away to reveal the bones underneath.

Despite the terrible physical condition that he was in, there was a layer of jade-like translucent light over his body, clearly indicating that he had already overcome his baleful decay.

Right at his moment, arcs of silver lightning shot out of the lightning pond before wrapping themselves around his body in a flash.

His expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, and he made a hand seal to summon his Virata Lute.

Shi Chuankong strummed his fingers over the strings of the lute, instantly releasing a series of silver soundwaves that eradicated the arcs of silver lightning clinging to his body upon contact.

He pounced on the opportunity to fly out of the lightning pond, and he was barely able to remain upright as he gasped for air while hurriedly flipping a hand over to summon a few pills.

Despite the terrible physical condition he was in, his face was glowing with elation.

Finally, he had overcome his baleful decay.

Lights of different colors emerged all over his body, and his wounds quickly began to heal. Before long, his body had largely returned to normal.

"Congratulations on overcoming your baleful decay, Brother Shi. Looks like we made the right decision to come here, after all," Fox 3 said with a smile as he cupped his fist in a salute.

"I just barely survived that by the skin of my teeth," Shi Chuankong chuckled.

All of a sudden, Liu Qi interjected in an urgent voice, "I hate to interrupt, but we don't have time to be chatting right now! I can sense that someone is quickly approaching this place, so we have to sever the golden chain right away!"

Everyone's expressions changed slightly upon hearing this, and they immediately sprang into action without delay.

The Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber appeared in Han Li's grasp amid a flash of red light, and he took a deep breath before gripping tightly onto the saber's hilt with both hands, then injected his immortal spiritual power into it in a frenzy.

Fox 3 and the others appeared behind Han Li in an instant, then thrust their palms forward in unison to inject their immortal spiritual power into his body.

Daoist Xie also appeared beside Han Li amid a flash of golden lightning.

The Immortal Origin Stones in Daoist Xie's body had already been replaced with new ones, so its aura had returned to its peak, and it was also injecting two beams of golden light into Han Li's body out of the palms of its hands.

This time, the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber was glowing even more radiantly than on the previous three occasions, and it released countless crimson saber projections that filled half of the entire hall.

A giant crimson fox projection suddenly emerged from the twin fox heads on the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber, then immediately pounced forward and vanished into the blade of the saber, immediately followed by all of the countless surrounding saber projections.

The Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber instantly swelled to several times its original size, and its shape also changed drastically as it transformed into a giant crescent-shaped scimitar.

Furthermore, dozens of crimson eyes had appeared all over the entire saber, giving it a harrowing sight to behold.

The Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber shuddered as an animalistic roar rang out from within it, following which crimson light that was as viscous as blood erupted out of its blade.

As the wielder of the saber, Han Li was struck head-on by an immense wave of baleful qi that caused his ears to ring loudly, while his internal organs were also churning violently.

A sense of feebleness spread through his entire body, almost causing him to lose his grip on the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber.

Pained looks appeared on the faces of Fox 3 and the others as well, but they were far less severely impacted than Han Li.

Han Li gritted his teeth as he channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique with all his might to stabilize his spiritual sense, and at the same time, he tightened his grip around the hilt of the saber.

However, right as he was about to swing the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber down onto the golden chain, it suddenly flew out of his grasp, then crashed heavily down onto the golden chain on its own.

The golden chain trembled violently as the runes engraved on its surface lit up with blinding golden radiance.

The entire golden lightning pond erupted into a frenzy, and waves of golden light that were thousands of feet tall rose up from its surface before threatening to spread in all directions, but ultimately, they seemed to be restricted by some type of invisible force, confining them to the lightning pond down below.

Countless arcs of golden lightning were intertwining incessantly within the golden light, presenting an awe-inspiring sight to behold.

The Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber sliced into the golden chain with great difficulty, but it only managed to slice halfway into the chain before stopping cold in its tracks, unable to advance even an inch further.

A burst of fearsome shockwaves erupted from the point where the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber and the golden chain were connected, and Han Li and the others were instantly sent flying before crashing heavily into a wall.

Right at this moment, a resounding boom rang out, and the entire hall swayed violently as if it had been dealt some type of heavy blow.

Chapter 772: Peril at Every Turn

"I suppose this was always unavoidable," Liu Qi murmured to himself as his expression darkened slightly.

At this moment, all of the surrounding white array patterns were glowing radiantly while releasing tremendous power that encompassed the entire hall, attempting to stabilize the violent tremors.

However, whatever was attacking the hall from the outside was doing so with tremendous power, and a series of cracks immediately appeared over its walls.

"There's no time left! Sever the chain!" Liu Qi urged as he made a hand seal, and bright white radiance erupted out of his body as he pointed a finger forward, releasing streaks of white light that vanished into the surrounding array patterns in a flash to stabilize the array.

However, before Han Li and the others even had a chance to steady themselves, an even more fearsome burst of power descended upon the hall.

This time, the hall swayed even more violently than before, and the surrounding white array patterns were trembling incessantly, looking as if they could collapse at any moment.

Liu Qi shuddered as he gave a muffled groan, seemingly having been indirectly affected by the heavy blow.

Immediately thereafter, a third blow arrived, and this time, the restrictions in the hall weren't able to hold themselves together any longer.

The stone gate exploded violently, leaving a huge hole in its wake, following which Yin Chengquan and Feng Qingshui flew into the hall.

Liu Qi gave another muffled groan as his body trembled incessantly, and blood began to trickle down from the corner of his lips, but his expression remained completely unchanged as he observed Yin Chengquan and Feng Qingshui with a cold expression.

"Your Infernal Tribe certainly is harboring many secrets, Regional Monarch Yin. We've just dealt with the Kun Hou outside, yet there's another Dao Ancestor in here! My eyes have truly been opened," Feng Qingshui mused as he observed Liu Qi from afar.

"Cut the chit-chat! Just do what we agreed upon prior to coming here. Otherwise, I'm scrapping our prior agreement!" Yin Chengquan harrumphed coldly.

Feng Qingshui remained completely unbothered by this as a faint smile appeared on his face.

Even though Han Li and the others had been sent flying from the shockwaves of the exploding stone gate, none of them had sustained any substantial injuries, but Han Li's heart immediately sank at the sight of Yin Chengquan and Feng Qingshui, both of whom had comparable auras, thereby indicating that the latter had to be a Dao Ancestor as well.

Fox 3 and Shi Chuankong's expressions also darkened significantly as this reality dawned on them as well.

Meanwhile, Weeping Soul was glowering at Yin Chengquan with a cold expression and her fists tightly clenched.

Yin Chengquan swept his gaze over Han Li and the other, then turned his attention to Liu Qi as he chuckled coldly, "Did you have all of this planned out, Liu Qi? You certainly chose a good time to strike, but there's no way that these ants could possibly sever these Lightning Entrapment Chains. I already told you that you were going to be trapped here for all of eternity!"

He threw a punch as he spoke, and as soon as he did so, Han Li immediately felt the surrounding space swell rapidly like a balloon, expanding the space within the hall by a hundredfold.

In this instant, Yin Chengquan's body became enormous, and he truly resembled an omnipotent deity.

In contrast, Han Li and the others were made to feel like a group of tiny ants that had strayed from the colony, and a sense of powerlessness welled up in their hearts.

A gray fist projection that resembled a massive mountain took shape before crashing down upon Liu Qi, and the surrounding space was also warping drastically as it compressed toward Liu Qi from all directions.

Furthermore, the gray fist projection was giving off a tremendous aura that instantly struck Han Li and the others with a numb sensation, and their legs plunged involuntarily into the ground all the way up to their knees.

Han Li's complexion instantly paled significantly as blood began to trickle down from the corner of his lips, while Fox 3 and the others fared even worse, throwing up mouthfuls of blood as their faces turned as pale as a sheet.

The Immortal Origin Stones in Daoist Xie's body had already been exhausted of their immortal spiritual power once again, and in the face of this crushing aura, it toppled straight to the ground, where it laid in a completely still fashion.

"If I hadn't been wounded by cultivators from the Heavenly Court all those years ago, there's no way you would've been able to restrain me! Now that I've already been freed from most of the restrictions, you won't capture me again!" Liu Qi sneered as he grabbed onto the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber with one of his front paws.

The saber immediately began to radiate dazzling crimson light that filled the entire hall, glowing countless times brighter than when it had been wielded by Han Li and the others.

With a swing of the saber, Liu Qi unleashed an enormous crimson saber projection, and the space in its wake exploded in layers like sheets of fragile paper.

Yin Chengquan's eyes narrowed slightly at the sight of the Heavenly Fox Bloodform Saber, while the giant saber projection crossed over a distance of several hundred feet in a flash before striking the gray fist projection with an earth-shattering boom.

Gray and crimson light intertwined as the nearby space trembled violently, and the bizarre phenomenon of enlarged space abruptly faded as everything returned to normal.

Countless white storms emerged, and countless more spatial rifts appeared within the storms before spreading in all directions.

At this moment, Han Li and the others were completely immobilized, and they could only look on helplessly as the spatial rifts spread toward them while releasing devastating forces that would tear their bodies to shreds upon contact.

"What are you standing there for? Don't let those people die! Capture them!" Yin Chengquan suddenly yelled.

Feng Qingshui turned his gaze to Han Li and the others upon hearing this, and rays of watery blue light began to radiate from his body.

The blue light wasn't particularly bright, but it was able to seep into the nearby rock face with ease, quickly giving the wall and the floor of the hall the appearance of translucent blue jade.

Enshrouded within the blue light, the spatial rifts were instantly slowed down significantly, while Feng Qingshui reached out to make a grabbing motion, and a giant blue palm projection instantly appeared around Han Li and the others.

Even before the palm projection had closed around them, Han Li and the others were already being subjected to a burst of tremendous force that instantly pressed them flat against the ground.

In their current state, they couldn't even lift a single finger, nor could they circulate their immortal spiritual power at all, and they could only look on helplessly as the giant palm projection descended upon them.

Despite his best efforts, Han Li wasn't able to move at all, and for the first time in a long time, a hint of panic welled up in his heart.

In the face of a true Dao Ancestor, he was truly nothing more than a powerless ant.

If it weren't for the fact that Yin Chengquan wanted them captured alive, they would've most likely already been killed on the spot.

Right at this moment, a cold harrumph rang out, and the crimson saber projection grew even brighter, while a series of crimson patterns appeared on its surface, and the gray fist projection was instantly sliced into two, following which the saber projection sped directly toward Yin Chengquan with tremendous power.

At the same time, the ground beside Han Li and the others suddenly exploded, following which a pair of thick fox tails emerged from underground.

One of the tails rose up into the air, and countless white runes emerged over its surface as it struck the oncoming blue palm projection with fearsome power.

A resounding boom rang out as the nearby space shuddered violently, and the blue palm projection was instantly slowed down significantly in its descent.

Meanwhile, the other fox tail wrapped itself around Fox 3 like lightning, following which both tails descended back into the ground.

Han Li's expression darkened significantly upon seeing this.

It was clear that Liu Qi had never truly viewed them as allies, but then again, that wasn't particularly surprising.

Their collaboration had been one that was forged solely on the promise of mutual benefit, and now that Han Li and the others had outlived their usefulness, they were naturally going to be abandoned.

If it weren't for the special set of circumstances that they were in, there was no way that a Dao Ancestor like Liu Qi would've been willing to help them to begin with.

Despite the fact that Fox 3 had been taken right before his eyes, Feng Qingshui's expression remained completely unchanged as he made a hand seal, and the blue palm projection swelled to roughly twice its original size, then split up into two, forming two identical giant palm projections.

One of the palm projections continued to descend toward Han Li's trio, while the other one vanished into the ground in a flash.

Right as the palm projection was no more than a hundred feet away from Han Li's trio, Shi Chuankong's body abruptly shuddered as a ball of radiant silver light flew out of his body without any warning, and the ball of silver light contained none other than the Virata Lute.

The lute was revolving rapidly while releasing countless rays of silver light, and not only was it able to stop the blue palm projection in its tracks, its strings also began to move on their own, releasing a series of silver runes that vanished into the nearby space.

All of a sudden, the space parted to create a spatial passageway that led to an undetermined destination.

A burst of tremendous suction force surged out of the spatial passageway, encompassing Han Li's trio before sucking them.

The pressure on Han Li's trio was instantly lifted, restoring their mobility and immortal spiritual power circulation, and they were naturally ecstatic to sense this.

"Stop them! If you have to kill them, then so be it!" Yin Chengquan yelled in an urgent voice.

An enraged look had also appeared on Feng Qingshui's face, and he immediately made another hand seal, upon which the nearby space trembled violently.

Immediately thereafter, countless rays of blue light surged out of the surrounding space, fusing forth like a celestial waterfall before filling the entire area in the blink of an eye.

The spatial passageway was also inundated by the boundless blue light, while a burst of tremendous force emerged around Han Li's trio, compressing toward them from all directions to stop them in their tracks right at the entrance of the spatial passageway.

Despite the tremendous suction force surging out of the passageway, they remained completely immobilized just a single, tantalizing step away.

Chapter 773: Surviving a Major Ordeal

"Come back!" Feng Qingshui roared in an authoritative voice as he reached out to make a grabbing motion, and countless translucent blue threads emerged around Han Li's trio, ensnaring them before dragging them away from the spatial passageway.

However, right at this moment, the nearby space shuddered once again, and bursts of dark red light emerged, forming a projection of a mountainous red wheel.

There were six dark holes on the wheel that were arranged in a hexagonal formation, and within every single one of these holes was a swirling vortex of black light.

As soon as the giant wheel projection appeared, it immediately began to revolve, giving off a burst of indescribably immense power.

The translucent blue threads around Han Li's trio were instantly severed, and they began flying toward the spatial passageway once again along with the Virata Lute.

However, right at this moment, Weeping Soul suddenly fell unconscious, and countless bursts of black qi surged out of the pores of her entire body.

Countless human and beastly faces could be seen within the bursts of black qi, and all of them were flying into the giant wheel projection.

At the same time, Weeping Soul's aura was rapidly diminishing, while her body was also taking on a transparent appearance.

Han Li hurriedly grabbed onto her upon seeing this, then stowed both her and Daoist Xie away into his Flower Branch domain, and he did so just in the nick of time as in the next instant, he was sucked into the spatial passageway.

A furious roar from Yin Chengquan rang out in the distance, and at the same time, two completely different bursts of law powers came surging toward them in unison.

Immediately thereafter, all of the sounds behind them abruptly faded, and it seemed that the spatial passageway had closed. The two bursts of law powers were also severed, but much of it had followed Han Li and the others through the spatial passageway.

Swept up by the two bursts of law powers, Han Li's body instantly became extremely slow and sluggish, and even the circulation of his spiritual sense and immortal spiritual power had slowed down significantly.

Through his blurry vision, he could just barely make out the Virata Lute releasing a series of silver halos that sucked away the two bursts of law powers, one gray and one blue, thereby freeing Han Li from their influence.

After taking a moment to compose himself, Han Li cast his gaze forward, and he discovered that there were two bursts of light, one blue and one gray, circling around the Virata Lute.

Several streaks of silver light were released by the strings of the lute, and they wrapped themselves around Han Li and Shi Chuankong's waists like streamers before pulling them along.

At this moment, Han Li's entire body was throbbing with pain, but he could still clearly sense bursts of incredibly formidable spatial power compressing toward him from all directions. He wanted to raise a hand to put up some resistance, but once again, he wasn't able to lift even a single finger.

Shi Chuankong wasn't far away from him, and he also appeared to be in the same situation, drifting along behind the Virata Lute with a pained grimace on his face.

Han Li gritted his teeth tightly as he peered deep into the spatial passageway with his Infernal Devilish Eyes, but all he saw was a seemingly endless expanse of empty space. It seemed that there was some type of powerful spatial force drawing the Virata Lute forward, and even though it was unclear whether the situation had taken a turn for the better, at the very least, they had managed to escape from Yin Chengquan and the other Dao Ancestor.

Right at this moment, the streaks of gray and blue light circling around the Virata Lute suddenly began to speed up, and a sense of foreboding immediately welled up in Han Li's heart upon seeing this, but in his current state, he wasn't able to do anything but watch.

The two streaks of light continued to pick up speed, and no more than twenty seconds later, they abruptly exploded without any warning, sending waves of blue and gray light surging through the air in all directions.

The surrounding spatial passageway instantly began to warp in the face of the immense explosive force, and countless specks of silver light began to dissipate in all directions.

Bursts of warped power glided past Han Li, further exacerbating the compressional force exerted by the surrounding spatial power, all of which ultimately acted upon the silver lute.

Shi Chuankong had clearly also sensed that something wasn't quite right, but just like Han Li, he was also completely immobilized, drifting along like a helpless raft in a turbulent sea, unable to do anything.

All of a sudden, a faint crack rang out, and the Virata Lute flying up ahead suddenly shuddered violently, and it was unable to continue to maintain a stable flight path.

After teetering around momentarily in an unstable fashion, it shuddered once again before tumbling violently through the air.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong were being dragged along behind it, and they also began to tumble through space, causing the world to spin around them. At the same time, in the face of the tremendous pressure exerted upon them by the surrounding spatial power, they were struggling to remain conscious.

......

After what seemed like an eternity, a glimmer of light finally appeared on the dim horizon.

A streak of silver light shot out of the glimmer of light, then reverted back into a silver lute that descended out of the sky.

Immediately after it came Han Li and Shi Chuankong, both of whom began to plummet out of the sky.

They had been jostled around quite severely within the spatial passageway, and even though they had managed to remain conscious, both of them were feeling very disoriented, so they were only able to gradually regain their vision after a brief process of acclimation.

Han Li cast his gaze forward to discover that the sky was a little dim, and gusts of fierce wind were howling past his ears. At this moment, he was situated in the air above a dark azure mountain range, plummeting rapidly toward the ground.

He hurriedly channeled his immortal spiritual power to stabilize himself in mid-air, then inspected his surroundings to discover that Shi Chuankong was also plummeting out of the sky not too far away.

Right at this moment, Shi Chuankong seemed to have also returned to his senses, and after stabilizing himself, he immediately flew over to the Virata Lute.

Holding the lute in his arms, he began to inspect it with a pained expression, upon which he discovered that there was a clear crack on its head, and the silver light radiating from it had also dimmed significantly.

Han Li was just about to call out to him when his entire body abruptly stiffened, following which a string of cracks and pops rang out from within his body as his immortal acupoints lit up one after another.

Wisps of the world's origin qi began to appear in the surrounding space, and they were rapidly becoming denser and denser as they converged toward him from all directions.

At this point, Shi Chuankong had also noticed what was happening, and he turned to Han Li with a bewildered expression.

"I was already about to make a breakthrough back in the Baleful Cleansing Ponds, and I only failed to do so due to the lack of the world's origin qi in the Gray Realm. Now that we're back, the breakthrough is commencing on its own," Han Li explained with a wry smile.

Shi Chuankong took a glance down at the mountain range below, which was filled with mist and miasma, and his brows began to furrow tightly with concern.

"But this is not the right place..."

Before he had a chance to finish, Han Li interjected, "My breakthrough is no longer being impeded by my baleful decay, so I won't be able to suppress it, and I have no time to choose a spot to enter seclusion. Hence, I'll have to trouble you and Brother Xie to protect me."

As soon as his voice trailed off, he flew down into a valley below as a streak of light.

Shortly thereafter, a door of silver light appeared in mid-air, and Daoist Xie also appeared before descending into the valley with him.

Thick pillars of silver lightning erupted out of Han Li's body before blasting into the valley amid a string of resounding thunderclaps that caused the entire valley to tremble incessantly, and amid the chaos, countless beasts and birds fled the valley in a blind panic.

All of the vegetation within a radius of dozens of kilometers around the spot that was struck in the valley was reduced to ashes, presenting a very jarring sight to behold.

Han Li sat down in that artificial clearing, and the dense world's origin qi that had gathered around him had already formed a series of white vortexes that were filled with glittering specks of light.

Outside the clearing, Daoist Xie was hovering three feet above the ground, wielding Thunderslash in its left hand and Heavenslash in its right, serving as Han Li's guardian.

Meanwhile, Shi Chuankong inspected his surroundings with a grim expression, and his expression only darkened even further at what he saw.

"You've really picked out a terrible place, Fellow Daoist Li! If you knew where we are right now...""

His voice trailed off as he shook his head with a wry smile, then also landed outside the clearing.

Daoist Xie cast its gaze toward him from afar, and there was a clear hint of wariness in its eyes.

"You take the north, I'll take the south. We're going to be very busy soon," Shi Chuankong coordinated.

A hesitant look flashed through Daoist Xie's eyes upon hearing this.

Right at this moment, a chorus of strange roars rang out from both within and outside of the valley, causing the entire valley to tremble incessantly.

"Here they come!" Shi Chuankong yelled.

As soon as his voice trailed off, the sound of snapping trees rang out from deep within the valley, and one enormous tree was felled after another, sending wood chips and clumps of soil flying in all directions.

A giant black ape, an azure serpent that was over a thousand feet in length, and a massive purple spider rushed out of the destroyed forest in unison, charging directly toward Han Li.

The black ape had a pair of crimson eyes, and its body was completely devoid of fur. Its skin resembled black steel that was giving off a faint sheen, and it launched a huge tree and a giant rock at Shi Chuankong from afar.

Meanwhile, the azure serpent opened its mouth to release a cloud of five-colored venomous smoke that surged through the air, interspersed throughout which were countless smaller azure serpents and purple spiders.

Furthermore, there were even more formidable beasty figures to come, and it was only a matter of time before they emerged from the forest as well.

Chapter 774: Immaculate Jade Physique

At the same time, countless beasts of different shapes, forms, and sizes were rushing in through the entrance of the valley before charging straight at Shi Chuankong and Daoist Xie.

All of the weaker beasts that they encountered that were still fleeing out of the valley were instantly trampled to death or devoured on the spot, and a horrific massacre ensued.

Judging from their auras, it seems like we're not dealing with any of the truly troublesome creatures yet, but that could easily change if this drags on for too long, Shi Chuankong thought to himself with a grim expression.

With that in mind, he rose up into the air before swooping down from above while sweeping his sleeves through the air to release a string of array tools, all of which descended onto the ground in the path of the oncoming beasts.

As the wave of ferocious beasts drew closer and closer, Shi Chuankong abruptly made a hand seal, and a burst of silver light rose up from the ground, forming a giant spatial barrier that was thousands of feet wide, spanning all the way from one end of the valley to the other.

A resounding boom rang out as the giant black ape crashed into the silver light barrier, which shuddered violently upon impact, but it remained completely unmoved.

The black ape's aura indicated that it was at the early-True Immortal Stage, and a furious look appeared in its eyes as it began raining blows down upon the silver light barrier with its incredibly thick and strong fists.

Immediately thereafter, the azure serpent and the purple spider also began ramming into the light barrier, but despite their best efforts, the light barrier remained as resilient as ever.

Shi Chuankong heaved a faint sigh of relief upon seeing this, then sat down with his legs crossed.

Now that they were finally out of the Gray Realm, he wouldn't have to rely on Immortal Origin Stones for energy replenishment any longer.

On the other side, the wary look on Daoist Xie's face eased slightly as it observed Shi Chuankong from afar, and it stowed Thunderslash away before removing a gourd from its waist.

It tipped the gourd upside-down as it chanted a brief incantation, then patted the underside of the gourd, and a vortex of spiritual light instantly emerged from the mouth of the gourd, following which a series of dark yellow beans emerged before raining down onto the ground.

As soon as they landed on the ground, each bean instantly transformed into a Dao Warrior that was around ten feet tall.

All of the Dao Warriors were clad in suits of antiquated armor that were riddled with lightning patterns, and they formed around a dozen uniform units, with each unit consisting of hundreds of Dao Warriors, then began to charge out of the valley in a stable formation.

The sound of their thundering footsteps echoed throughout the valley in a resounding fashion, and they were quickly surrounded by the oncoming waves of ferocious beasts.

Individually, these Dao Warriors were slightly inferior in power to these beasts, but thanks to their flawless teamwork, they were quickly able to gain the upper hand, and they began tearing through the enemy ranks.

Meanwhile, Daoist Xie was hovering high up in the sky, looking out into the distance with tightly furrowed brows.

There were massive clouds of smoke rising up in that direction, and it seemed like there were many more ferocious beasts on their way.

It then looked up at the sky as a reminiscent look flashed through its eyes, following which it turned its gaze back to Han Li.

At this moment, Han Li's eyes were tightly shut, and it seemed that he was completely oblivious to everything happening around him. The surrounding world's origin qi had formed an enormous white vortex around him, and it stretched all the way up to the dark clouds in the sky like a giant pillar.

Situated at the very center of the vortex, Han Li's body was lifted up into the air by the world's origin qi, and his immortal acupoints were glowing brightly, while his skin had taken on a pristine, jade-like appearance.

All of his bones and meridians were visible through his near-transparent skin and flesh, and they were all giving off a faint golden sheen.

Right at this moment, his eyes suddenly sprang open as he exhaled to release a plume of black mist, and the surrounding white light was instantly set alight.

Countless white flames emerged within the vortex of spiritual qi, constantly roasting Han Li's body to make it even more immaculate and transparent.

The dark clouds above the white flames had also begun to light up, and specks of five-colored light emerged within them, presenting a breathtaking sight to behold.

The ultimate pursuit for a Jade Immortal was to attain an immaculate immortal physique that was as unblemished as jade, and their physical constitutions were naturally far superior to those of Golden Immortals, while their spiritual sense would also be elevated to a different level.

On top of that, Jade Immortals also became more in sync with heaven and earth, the Great Dao, and the laws of heaven and earth, thereby allowing them to better understand and harness law powers.

It could be said that the degree of purity of a Jade Immortal's physique determined how far they would be able to go on the path of cultivation, and the astonishing phenomena that Han Li was triggering now naturally had much to do with the four Baleful Cleansing Ponds that he had endured.

Shi Chuankong was roused from his meditation by these incredible phenomena, and he turned to Han Li with an awestruck expression as he murmured to himself, "As expected, Fellow Daoist Li really is always full of surprises."

As soon as his voice trailed off, he turned his gaze to the silver light barrier, upon which his brows immediately furrowed slightly.

At this moment, all of the purple spiders were shooting five-colored webs onto the silver light barrier, thereby giving themselves the purchase required to climb up the light barrier.

A ferocious roar rang out as the giant black ape climbed its way up the light barrier using the cobwebs, then vaulted itself over the light barrier entirely before pouncing at Han Li with fierce bloodlust in its eyes.

However, before it could reach Han Li, a streak of silver light flashed past to pulverize its head.

Unfortunately, its demise did nothing to intimidate all of the other beasts, and they continued to rush toward the silver light barrier without any regard for their own safety.

Meanwhile, some of the massive figures within the dense mist up ahead were also gradually becoming clearer and clearer.

"I should refer to you as Fellow Daoist Xie, right?" Shi Chuankong asked as he approached Daoist Xie, and the latter turned to face him, but remained silent.

"It doesn't look like Brother Li will be coming out of seclusion anytime soon, and there will only be more and more beasts drawn to this place by the vast abundance of the world's origin qi here. Hence, we have to work together to protect him. There's no need to be so wary of me, I bear no ill will toward Brother Li," Shi Chuankong assured with a smile.

Daoist Xie merely nodded in response, and Shi Chuankong could only shake his head in a resigned manner upon seeing this.

After that, he flew onto the silver light barrier, then flipped a hand over to produce a palm-sized silver mirror, which immediately released numerous strands of silver light at his behest. The strands of silver light shot forth through the air to strike the azure serpents and purple spiders climbing up the silver light barrier, tearing their bodies to shreds.

Meanwhile, Daoist Xie withdrew its gaze as it began wielding both Thunderslash and Heavenslah again, and all of a sudden, it burrowed into the ground, disappearing out of sight.

Shortly thereafter, hundreds of pillars of lightning erupted out of the ground amid a burst of violent rumbling, completely destroying the ground at the entrance of the valley, and all of the demon beast that had just rushed to the entrance of the valley were instantly eradicated by the pillars of lightning.

All of a sudden, a giant rift appeared in the ground, and a white centipede that was over a thousand feet in length emerged before flying up into the air, then crashed heavily down onto the ground with all of its joints shattered.

Standing atop its head was Daoist Xie, who was slowly pulling Thunderslash out of its body in an expressionless manner.

The Dao Warriors had already eradicated all of the demon beasts in the valley, and they hadn't suffered many casualties in the process. All of the formations were still relatively intact, and under Daoist Xie's instructions, they began to gather at the entrance of the valley to form a dense defensive line.

......

Over three months flew by in a flash.

Lightning was flashing incessantly above the valley as a giant winged serpent snaked its way through the dark clouds while releasing streaks of black light out of its mouth in all directions.

Behind it was a figure that was enveloped in arcs of golden lightning, and they were constantly moving while wielding a pair of antiquated blades, with which they had already been able to inflict a series of huge gashes onto the serpent's body.

The serpent's eyes were filled with resentment, but it was hindered by its own enormous frame, and its assailant was far too fast for it to catch.

Right at this moment, the figure abruptly appeared on the winged serpent's back amid a flash of lightning, then lashed out with both blades at once, striking viciously down upon the points where the serpent's wings were connected to its body.

Chapter 775: Reaching the High Zenith Stage

Blood sprayed in all directions as the serpent's wings were severed, and it let loose an anguished cry as it plummeted straight into the valley.

At this moment, the entire valley was already filled with demon beast carcasses, and blood was flowing everywhere. Many deep puddles of blood had already accumulated next to some of the more massive demon beasts, while some of the smaller demon beasts were floating in the puddles of blood, presenting a hellish sight to behold.

The winged serpent crashed heavily down into one of these enormous pools of blood, and it began struggling violently, sending putrid black blood splashing in all directions.

All of a sudden, a bolt of golden lightning descended out of the sky before crashing down onto its head, and only then did its struggles gradually subside as it fell limp to the ground.

The golden figure was none other than Daoist Xie, and it pulled its blade out of the serpent's body, then looked up into the sky with a cold expression.

At this point, two massive mountains of carcasses had already built up in the valley, and they stretched on as far as the eyes could see. Currently, there were very few demon beasts attacking over land, and only the most powerful terrestrial demon beasts were able to climb over the mountains of carcasses to launch their attacks.

A putrid lake of blood that was close to fifty kilometers in radius had taken shape in the valley, and there were countless carcasses floating on top of it, but hovering above the center of the lake was a white lotus bud formed by pure immortal spiritual power.

The flower bud seemed set to bloom at any moment, and Han Li was currently inside it.

What was very remarkable was that the blood around the lotus bud seemed to have been affected by its immortal spiritual power, and it retained its original bright red color. There wasn't any putrid odor emanating from it, nor did any of the floating carcasses approach the flower bud.

High up in the sky above the lotus bud, Shi Chuankong's entire body was drenched in blood as he fought against three enormous demon beasts while wielding a silver spear.

He and Daoist Xie had already lost count of how many times these demon beasts had attacked over the past few months. All they knew was that all of the Dao Warriors nurtured by Han Li had been eradicated half a month ago, while Shi Chuankong had also exhausted his supply of talismans and array plates, and even quite a few of his treasures had been completely destroyed in battle.

What was most concerning of all was that there were several formidable demon beasts that were even more powerful than the winged serpent laying in wait around the valley, waiting for them to be worn down before they stormed into the valley.

At this moment, Daoist Xie was observing Shi Chuankong with a contemplative look on its face.

Initially, it had no trust at all for Shi Chuankong, and their relationship only improved slightly over time, but it wasn't sure if Shi Chuankong would remain committed to the cause if things were to continue in this fashion.

Right at this moment, a resounding boom rang out, and an enormous white toad suddenly sprang up into the sky from one of the mountains of carcasses, then opened its mouth to release a corkscrew-shaped glacial storm that surged directly toward Shi Chuankong.

Shi Chuankong had only just withstood the attacks from the three powerful demon beasts that he was locked in battle against, and he was unable to adopt any defensive measures before he was swept up by the storm.

A layer of white ice crystals instantly appeared over his body, and he began to plummet out of the sky.

A grim look appeared in Daoist Xie's eyes as it hurriedly flew toward Shi Chuankong.

These demon beasts had launched their attack a little earlier than it had anticipated.

A series of enormous demon beasts began to emerge on the two mountains of carcasses in the valley, and all of them were at or above the early-Golden Immortal Stage, with the most powerful one among them, a Hundred-eyed Centipede, giving off a late-Golden Immortal Stage aura.

Under normal circumstances, Shi Chuankong and Daoist Xie would have nothing to fear, but at this point, they had already been severely drained by the constant battles they had been forced to endure over the past few months.

It wouldn't be difficult for them to escape, but if they had to continue directly opposing these demon beasts, then the situation was looking far from optimistic.

Right at this moment, the sound of a yawn rang out from within the white lotus bud.

It was only a very faint sound, but it was transmitted in all directions by the spiritual power fluctuations emanating from the lotus bud, and it rang out as clear as day within Daoist Xie's mind.

As for Shi Chuankong, even though he was still encased in a layer of ice crystals, he heaved a long sigh of relief as he murmured to himself, "You're finally awake, Brother Li."

In the next instant, the dark clouds up above abruptly parted, and a ray of radiant light rose up from the lake of blood.

Immediately thereafter, a figure shot out of the white lotus bud, only stopping in its tracks after ascending to incredible heights.

The figure was enshrouded within a layer of blinding white light, and Daoist Xie immediately stopped in its tracks upon seeing this.

All of the demon beasts in the valley were also intimidated by the figure's formidable aura, and all of them stopped in unison before looking up into the sky.

High up in the sky, the white light gradually faded, and Han Li was revealed.

At this moment, he was dressed in a white robe, and he had put on his Reincarnation Palace mask. His skin was as immaculate and translucent as jade, giving him the appearance of an elegant immortal.

This change in his physical appearance wasn't one that he had artificially manufactured. Instead, it was the result of newfound disposition, which was indescribably pure, as if he had been reborn anew.

However, Han Li wasn't a fan of this appearance himself, and he reverted back to his original appearance amid a flash of azure light, but due to the fact that he had only just completed his breakthrough, he was unable to suppress his High Zenith Stage immortal spiritual power fluctuations for now.

He took a glance at his surroundings, following which three Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords appeared around him at his behest.

The swords were trembling slightly, and tiny arcs of golden lightning were constantly dancing over them. It seemed that the swords were barely able to contain the lightning law powers within them.

Han Li gently swept a sleeve through the air, and the three swords instantly shot forth at his behest, vanishing from the spot in the blink of an eye.

In the next instant, three of the demon beasts in the sky cried out in unison as their heads exploded into countless pieces amid eruptions of golden lightning, following which their charred bodies came plummeting down from above.

The white toad immediately turned to flee as quickly as it could upon seeing this, and the other demon beasts also followed suit.

Han Li raised an eyebrow as he threw a punch in both directions, sending two enormous azure fist projections hurtling through the air.

Both of the mountains of carcasses were struck by a burst of tremendous force in unison, and the white toad was pulverized by one of the fist projections without being able to put up any resistance, and the other demon beasts also quickly suffered the same fate.

Even the late-Golden Immortal Stage centipede was only able to just barely launch a few fireballs at the fist projection, but they had no effect whatsoever.

Shi Chuankong and Daoist Xie had already received advance warning from Han Li, so they had flown up into the sky to avoid being caught in the crossfire.

With just two simple punches, the two mountains of carcasses that had been built up over the course of three months in the valley had been instantly razed to the ground. Even the valley itself had caved in significantly and been completely transformed into a giant lake of blood.

In the wake of the demise of all of the Golden Immortal Stage demon beasts, all of the other demon beasts that had previously been impeded by the mountains of carcasses quickly fled the scene.

Han Li flew down from above to join Shi Chuankong and Daoist Xie, and the former cupped his fist in a salute as he said, "Congratulations on reaching the High Zenith Stage, Brother Li."

"It really was quite the ordeal overcoming my baleful decay. If I recall correctly, you were also able to cleanse all of the baleful qi from your body, so why is it that our return to the Immortal Realm hasn't triggered a breakthrough in you?" Han Li asked.

"The circumstances required for beings like myself to make breakthroughs are a little different from yours," Shi Chuankong explained in an ambiguous fashion.

Han Li didn't know whether he was referring to the entire Devil Race or just his bloodline in particular, but he didn't pry into the subject, merely nodding in response.

"By the way, how do you know that this is the Immortal Realm, Brother Li?" Shi Chuankong suddenly asked with a faint smile.

"Is that not the case?" Han Li asked with a surprised expression.

"It is, but it's also not," Shi Chuankong replied in a mysterious fashion.

"Could it be that we're in the Devil Realm?" Han Li asked.

"That's what people from the Immortal Realm like to call it, but we prefer to refer to it as the Holy Realm," Shi Chuankong confirmed with a nod.

"I had heard that the Devil Realm was inside the Immortal Realm, but existed as a standalone entity, but I certainly wasn't expecting to visit it so soon," Han Li mused with a faint smile.

"I'm not exactly sure why we've suddenly appeared here, but I have a rough idea," Shi Chuankong said.

"Didn't you channel the power of that lute of yours to get us out of the Gray Realm?" Han Li asked with a puzzled expression.

"I'm not capable of such a miraculous feat. There's only one person I can think of who can channel the power of the Virata Lute to rescue us from the Gray Realm, and that's my father, the one that you would refer to as the Devilish Monarch," Shi Chuankong replied with a wry smile.

Han Li was astonished to hear this.

The Devilish Monarch was the one who had lent Patriarch Miro that spatial treasure, and there were legends told of him resisting many Dao Ancestors at only the Great Encompassment Stage to seize control over the Devil Realm.

It was said that his powers were comparable to those of the Heavenly Court's Time Dao Ancestor, and Shi Chuankong was referring to this man as his father!

Chapter 776: Search for a Soul Mate

A whole host of questions had arisen in Han Li's heart, but he chose not to articulate any of them, and after taking a moment to compose himself, he couldn't help but wonder why Shi Chuankong had revealed this to him.

"I'm guessing that my father sensed it when I used the secret technique passed down in our clan to refine the Virata Lute, and by using the lute as a medium, he was able to bring us back to the Devil Realm using his spatial powers," Shi Chuankong explained.

"I see," Han Li replied with a nod, and he was just about to say something else when a thought suddenly occurred to him, and he swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up a door of silver light before stepping into it.

Shi Chuankong was rather perplexed to see this, but he still followed along, as did Daoist Xie.

After stepping through the door of light, the trio arrived in the bamboo building in the Flower Branch domain, where Weeping Soul was laying on the ground, and Han Li hurriedly rushed over to her before picking her up.

He then began to inspect her condition with his spiritual sense, and moments later, he flipped a hand over to summon a golden pill that she fed into her mouth.

However, the pill seemed to have had no effect, and Weeping Soul remained unconscious.

"What's wrong with her, Brother Li?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"I don't know," Han Li replied with tightly furrowed brows. "Her injuries aren't very severe, nor has she sustained much damage to her soul, so she shouldn't be unconscious."

"Have you checked to see if there are any abnormalities in her dantian?" Shi Chuankong asked.

An enlightened look appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this, and he hurriedly did as Shi Chuankong suggested, upon which a perplexed look appeared on his face as he mused, "I can't detect any essential power in her dantian..."

"That's most likely the cause of the problem then," Shi Chuankong said.

Thinking back to the events that had transpired before they entered the spatial passageway, Han Li couldn't help but feel as if Weeping Soul's current condition had something to do with the wheel projection from before, but at the same time, he couldn't be certain whether this was actually the case.

"Thank you for the reminder, Brother Shi. Otherwise, I would've been completely stumped," Han Li said.

"It's fine. What do you plan to do about her condition, Brother Li?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"I've never seen anything like this before, so I don't really know what to do. Do you have any ideas, Brother Shi?" Han Li asked with a wry smile.

"I'm afraid not, but if you return to our holy capital with me, perhaps our grand priest would be able to offer a solution," Shi Chuankong replied.

A contemplative look appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this.

"Pardon me for prying, but if you're not going to come with me, then what are your plans going forward from here?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"I thought we had returned to the Immortal Realm, but that's clearly not the case, so I'll have to have a good think about what I do from here," Han Li sighed.

"Right now, we're currently in a place known as the Ten Hazards Mountain Range, and it derives its name from the presence of ten Great Encompassment Stage demon beasts in the mountain range. Hence, this is an extremely dangerous place, so regardless of what you decide to do, it would be in your best interest to leave this place first," Shi Chuankong advised.

Han Li was quite startled to hear this, and after some contemplation, he said, "Truth be told, I know next to nothing about the Devil Realm. What do you suggest that I do from here, Fellow Daoist Shi?"

"The demon beasts in this area are extremely xenophobic, so we'll be in a great deal of danger if any of the Ten Hazards become aware of our existence. Hence, I think we should travel northward and leave this place as soon as possible.

“At the northernmost point of the Ten Hazards Mountain Range is a city that was constructed to ward off demon beast invasions, and there are Great Encompassment cultivators stationed in the city, so we'll be safe once we get there. From there, we can travel to the capital, Night Sun City, either through the city lord's manor or the Vast Origin House branch in the city," Shi Chuankong replied.

Han Li mulled over his options for a moment, then decided to accept Shi Chuankong's proposal.

Shi Chuankong was ecstatic to hear that Han Li was willing to come with him, and he immediately said, "In that case, let's set off right away. Those demon beasts have retreated for now, but there's no telling when they could be back, so this definitely isn't a safe place to stay."

"Hold on a second, Fellow Daoist Shi. Before we set off, there's something I want to ask you," Han Li suddenly said.

"Please go ahead, Fellow Daoist Li," Shi Chuankong prompted.

"Firstly, I must thank you for protecting me during my breakthrough, but at the same time, I can't help but wonder why you went to such great lengths to help me. If you need something from me, then feel free to tell me," Han Li said.

Having spent so much time with Shi Chuankong, he had developed a rough idea of Shi Chuankong's personality, and he knew that Shi Chuankong wasn't the type of person to take such a huge risk for nothing.

"You really are a smart man, Fellow Daoist Li. I do indeed have something to ask of you. The Ten Hazards Mountain Range is an extremely perilous place, and I'm not confident in my ability to get out of here on my own, so I was hoping that you would accompany me," Shi Chuankong admitted in a slightly embarrassed fashion.

"Of course. It's only right that we help each other out in such a perilous place," Han Li replied with a nod.

Now that he had reached the High Zenith Stage, his powers had been significantly enhanced, and he was fairly confident in his ability to ensure self-preservation, even in the face of the average Great Encompassment cultivator. If worse came to worst, he would just have to send Shi Chuankong into the Flower Branch domain so that he wouldn't be a hindrance.

"You have my thanks, Fellow Daoist Li. The headquarters of the Vast Origin House just so happens to be in Night Sun City, and there are spatial gates there leading to various immortal regions. As soon as we return to Night Sun City, I'll immediately arrange for you to be sent back to the Black Soil Immortal Region," Shi Chuankong promised.

"I'm not in a hurry to get back to the Black Soil Immortal Region, and I have a favor to ask of you once we get to the Vast Origin House headquarters," Han Li said.

The world's origin qi in the Devil Realm was quite abundant, and it was far away from the Heavenly Court's sphere of influence, so he would actually rather stay and cultivate here for now than return to the True Immortal Realm right away.

"What is it, Fellow Daoist Li? Is it the matter that you spoke to me about back in the Gray Realm?" Shi Chuankong asked.

"That's right. I would like you to draw upon the resources of the Vast Origin House to help me find an ascended cultivator. Here's what she looks like," Han Li said as he offered a blue jade badge to Shi Chuankong, and hovering above the badge was a visage of none other than Violet Spirit.

Shi Chuankong's eyes lit up as he accepted the jade badge, and he asked, "Is this your dao partner, Fellow Daoist Li? Her beauty is truly unmatched!"

"Her name is Violet Spirit, and she's a devilish cultivator from a lower realm. She may or may not have ascended at this point, and I'm hoping that you can find her for me, Fellow Daoist Shi," Han Li replied.

"If she's a devilish cultivator, then that makes things far easier. All devilish cultivators from the lower realm will ascend to our Holy Realm, and the ascension platform of our Holy Realm has always been overseen by one of my brothers, whom I'm very close to. Hence, as long as she's ascended, I'll definitely be able to track her down," Shi Chuankong assured with a confident smile.

"In that case, I'll be counting on you," Han Li replied with a smile of his own.

"I already agreed to this back in the Gray Realm, and now, I need your protection to leave this Ten Hazards Mountain Range, so I'm the one who'll be counting on you," Shi Chuankong chuckled.

With that, the two of them didn't delay any longer, and they left the Flower Branch domain before heading northward.

……

Countless kilometers away from where Han Li's duo was situated was an enormous mountain range, most of which was golden in color, perhaps due to the presence of some type of special ore in the area.

At the center of the mountain range was a huge mountain that was entirely golden in color and was giving off dazzling golden radiance that was clearly visible even from hundreds of kilometers away.

A cluster of giant palaces was situated on the mountain summit, all of which were extremely grand and spectacular. Everything in this cluster of palaces was also golden in color and enshrouded in golden light.

The Ten Hazards each had their own territory in the Ten Hazards Mountain Range, and they had countless powerful demon beasts under their command, so even the devil race was unable to do anything about them.

The cave abode of one of the Ten Hazards, the Golden Rhinoceros King, was situated here, and all of the guards and servants in the palace were also dressed in golden attire.

Stationed at the entrance of a large palace on the very outskirts of the cluster of palaces were two guards clad in suits of golden armor, and only half of their faces were visible through their golden visors.

"This armor is so heavy that I can barely breathe in it, but if I don't wear it, I'll immediately be harmed by the golden radiance here. No wonder no one wants to stand on guard duty on this Golden Peak Mountain," the guard on the left complained.

"It's definitely particularly uncomfortable when you first get here, but you'll get used to it over time. It's a grueling job, but we get far better compensation than everyone else, so just bear with it, Brother Ba," the other guard replied.

"Of course. There's no way I'd be willing to come here if not for the compensation! What a strange man the Golden Rhinoceros King must be to enjoy staying in an environment like this," the guard with the Ba surname scoffed.

"Shush!" the other guard hurriedly scolded through voice transmission.

"What's wrong?" the guard with the Ba surname asked.

"The Golden Rhinoceros King hates it when other people comment on his likes and dislikes. One of his new concubines recently made a similar comment, and she was immediately executed by sun exposure, strapped to the Scorching Sun Pole until she burned to a crisp, so make sure you don't ever say anything like that again!" the other guard warned in a solemn manner.

"I'll be sure to keep that in mind," the guard with the Ba surname hurriedly replied as he took a fearful glance at his surroundings, and he only heaved a sigh of relief after some time passed with no incident.

Chapter 777: Eldest Prince

Deep within the cluster of palaces was a particularly lavish palace, within which a man that resembled a mountain of flesh was laying lazily on a golden reclining chair.

The man had a pair of long and narrow eyes coupled with a flat nose and an enormous mouth, presenting a hideous sight to behold. His skin was dark golden in color and riddled with barely visible golden patterns.

Two golden-robed maidservants were knelt down beside him, massaging his body.

Both of the women had serpentine lower bodies, and they were wearing golden gloves on their slender hands.

These golden gloves were immortal treasures, and they released bursts of golden light to help the two women massage the giant man's body.

Both of the women were sweating profusely, indicating that they were massaging with all their might.

"That's good, that's the spot... Go a bit harder..." the massive man murmured in a blissful manner with his eyes half-closed, and the two women immediately redoubled their efforts upon hearing this.

Right at this moment, the man suddenly raised an eyebrow as he got up into a seated position, and the two women immediately stopped what they were doing upon seeing this.

"You two can go for now," the man instructed with a dismissive wave of his hand.

Despite his enormous frame, his voice was very sharp and high-pitched, presenting a rather comical contrast, but the two women didn't dare to display any amusement as they backed away with their heads lowered.

The man swept a hand through the air, releasing a purple plate that hovered in mid-air in front of him.

The plate released a burst of radiant purple light, which formed a purple array, and a purple-robed middle-aged man appeared within the array.

The man appeared to be around thirty-seven to thirty-eight years of age, and he had a set of handsome and refined facial features.

There was a faint purple mark on his glabella that was imprinted deep into his skin, and it seemed to be an ancient rune that was giving off a faint purple glow.

"Well, well, well, to what do I owe this honor, Your Highness? Isn't this a very busy time for you? How do you have the time to be contacting a lowly nobody like me?" the giant man asked.

"You're far too modest, Fellow Daoist Golden Rhinoceros. I've always admired you for your power, but I didn't want to disturb you as I heard that you were recovering from the injuries that you sustained from your recent battle against that black weasel. I'm very glad to see that you appear to have made a full recovery," the purple-robed man replied with a warm smile.

The giant man was none other than the Golden Rhinoceros King, and a cold look instantly appeared on his face upon hearing this.

"Have you come here just to mock me, Your Highness?"

"Please don't misunderstand, Fellow Daoist Golden Rhinoceros. The only reason why you lost that battle is because you're yet to attain your Devilish Vajra Physique. I just so happen to have come into possession of a few Golden Origin Dao Fruits recently, and I'm sure they'll be able to help you in that department," the purple-robed man replied.

The Golden Rhinoceros King immediately sprang to his feet with a fervent look in his eyes upon hearing this, and he hurriedly asked, "Is that true?"

The purple-robed man merely smiled and offered no response.

The Golden Rhinoceros King took a moment to compose himself, then said, "If you have something to ask of me, then please go ahead, Your Highness."

"I do indeed have something to ask of you, Fellow Daoist Golden Rhinoceros, and if you can complete my request, then the Golden Origin Dao Fruits will be yours," the purple-robed man said as a hint of killing intent flashed through his eyes.

"Go ahead, Your Highness," the Golden Rhinoceros King prompted.

"I want you to take someone out of the picture for me, permanently," the purple-robed man replied.

The Golden Rhinoceros King didn't seem surprised at all to hear this, and he asked, "Who is it?"

Instead of giving a reply, the purple-robed swept a sleeve through the air to release a streak of purple light, which transformed into a screen of purple light that depicted two figures, namely Shi Chuankong and Han Li.

The Golden Rhinoceros King's gaze immediately settled on Shi Chuankong as a hint of recognition flashed through his eyes, while Han Li was ignored entirely.

"That man is the thirteenth prince, Shi Chuankong. Right now, these two are in the Ten Hazards Mountain Range, and by my estimates, they should be in your territory. If you can bring me his head and the silver lute in his possession, then I'll give you two Golden Origin Dao Fruits," the purple-robed man said.

A hint of greed flashed through the Golden Rhinoceros King's eyes upon hearing this, but that was then replaced with a conflicted expression.

"I'll admit that this is a very tempting offer, but I've heard that Shi Chuankong is a very beloved son of the Holy Monarch. The wrath of the Holy Monarch is not something that I can bear, so I'm afraid you'll have to turn to someone else, Your Highness," the Golden Rhinoceros King said with a shake of his head.

"Right now, Father is currently in seclusion, and prior to going into seclusion, he instructed my brothers and I to settle the matter of deciding an heir on our own. Do you understand what I'm saying, Fellow Daoist Golden Rhinoceros?" the purple-robed man asked.

"In that case, I can consider it, but Shi Chuankong is affiliated with some very formidable powers, so killing him will make me a lot of enemies," the Golden Rhinoceros King mused.

"The mighty Golden Rhinoceros King is afraid of making enemies?" the purple-robed man chuckled.

"There's no need to try and goad me, Your Highness. If you want my help in this matter, then I want two Golden Origin Dao Fruits as a deposit, and once I get the job done, you need to give me two more Golden Origin Dao Fruits," the Golden Rhinoceros King said.

The purple-robed man's expression remained unchanged, but a hint of displeasure crept into his voice as he asked, "Do you not think you're asking for too much, Fellow Daoist Golden Rhinoceros?"

"Asking for too much? I think not! Golden Origin Dao Fruits are indeed very precious, but they're nothing compared with what you're trying to accomplish! According to my knowledge, even though you're the eldest prince, Shi Chuankong has always been a major threat to your claim to the throne, so getting rid of him for the price of just four Golden Origin Dao Fruits is an absolute bargain for you!" the Golden Rhinoceros King countered with a sly grin.

"At the very most, I'll only give you three fruits, and they'll only be given to you after the job is done," the purple-robed man negotiated.

"That won't do. I want one fruit as a deposit. I won't do anything unless I receive a deposit," the Golden Rhinoceros King replied in a firm manner.

"Alright, but if you're unable to do what I ask, not only will you have to return the Golden Origin Dao Fruit, you'll have to do so with interest. By the way, that man who's accompanying Shi Chuankong should already be at the early-High Zenith Stage," the purple-robed man said.

The Golden Rhinoceros King immediately burst into laughter as if he had just been told a hilarious joke, and he chortled, "Isn't Shi Chuankong only a Golden Immortal? Even with an early-High Zenith cultivator by his side, there's no way they'll be a match for me!"

"In that case, I look forward to hearing from you, Fellow Daoist Golden Rhinoceros," the purple-robed man said before vanishing from the spot.

However, the purple array remained in his place, and not only did it not fade away, it grew even brighter as countless silver runes surged out of it to form a separate silver array.

Immediately thereafter, a fist-sized golden fruit appeared at the center of the array amid a flash of silver light.

The fruit was riddled with small golden spots that were giving off a golden gleam, and it was giving off formidable metal-attribute law power fluctuations.

The Golden Rhinoceros King's eyes immediately lit up as he picked up the golden fruit before conducting a close examination, following which he carefully stowed the fruit away into a jade box.

After applying several talismans to the box, he stowed it away, then called out, "Get Tie Yu to come and see me."

A golden-robed servant immediately appeared outside the palace, then gave an affirmative response before flying away into the distance.

Shortly thereafter, a streak of green light shot forth from afar, then landed outside the hall before fading to reveal a short green-robed man.

The man's skin was entirely green in color, and he stood at only five feet tall with a childlike face. However, his body was extremely muscular and well-developed, presenting a jarring contrast.

A hint of fear flashed through the eyes of the guards outside the palace at the sight of the short man, and they immediately extended respectful salutes.

"Master Tie Yu!"

Tie Yu paid no heed to the guards as he strode into the palace, then knelt down onto the ground before kowtowing as he said, "Tie Yu pays his respects to the Golden Rhinoceros King."

"No need for formalities, Tie Yu. I've already told you that Tong Yu, Yin Yu, and you do not need to observe such formalities in my presence," the Golden Rhinoceros King said in a warm voice as he stood up and personally helped Tie Yu to his feet.

"You are the king, while we are your subordinates, so it's only right that such formalities be observed," Tie Yu countered in a respectful manner.

"Fine, do as you please then," the Golden Rhinoceros King sighed.

"May I ask why I have been summoned here?" Tie Yu asked.

"Take some people to scour our territory for this man, and bring back his head and all of his possessions," the Golden Rhinoceros King instructed as he flicked a finger through the air to conjure up a screen of light that depicted both Shi Chuankong and Han Li, and he pointed a finger straight at the former.

"There are outsiders in our territory?" Tie Yu asked in a cold voice.

"That's right. I know how much you detest outsiders, but make sure that you bring this man's head back to me completely unharmed," the Golden Rhinoceros King instructed.

"I'll be sure to do so," Tie Yu replied as a hint of killing intent flashed through his eyes.

"Your target is at the pinnacle of the Golden Immortal Stage, while the man accompanying him is at the early-High Zenith Stage. Make sure to hunt them down as soon as possible, and I give you permission to take anyone you want with you," the Golden Rhinoceros King continued, but refrained from revealing Shi Chuankong's identity to Tie Yu.

"Rest assured, my king, I'll bring his head back to you within a month," Tie Yu replied in a proud manner.

"Alright, you can go now," the Golden Rhinoceros King said, and Tie Yu promptly departed, flying out of the palace as a streak of green light.

Chapter 778: Intercepted

Han Li and Shi Chuankong were flying along at a low altitude through a dim forest somewhere within the Ten Hazards Mountain Range.

The forest was already quite dim to begin with, and visibility certainly wasn't helped by the fact that all of the trees were black in color.

Furthermore, the forest was also giving off a very peculiar aura that wasn't the world's origin qi or devilish qi. Instead, it was some type of special dark power, and there were many strange beasts residing in the forest that were also giving off the same aura.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong were able to blend almost perfectly into this environment thanks to their concealment techniques, and even though they were flying very quickly, they weren't giving off any aura fluctuations.

"This is quite a remarkable environment," Han Li commented as he inspected his surroundings.

At this point, they had already been traveling for around half a month, and they had been attacked by some demon beasts along the way, but all of the attacks had been easily dealt with, so they were feeling a little more relaxed.

"Compared with the True Immortal Realm, the underground energy veins in our Holy Realm are a bit more chaotic, and that's even more true for the Ten Hazards Mountain Range. There are all types of energies present in these mountains, forming many special environments, but you'll get used to this over time," Shi Chuankong replied with a smile.

Han Li nodded in response, and he was just about to say something when he abruptly stopped cold in his tracks, then peered deep into the forest up ahead.

Shi Chuankong also stopped in his tracks upon seeing this, but he couldn't see anything up ahead, and he asked, "What's wrong, Fellow Daoist Li?"

"Nothing. Perhaps it was just a figment of my imagination," Han Li replied as a hint of befuddlement flashed through his eyes.

He peered carefully into the forest for a moment longer, but was still unable to see anything, so he ushered Shi Chuankong to continue onward, and the two of them quickly vanished into the distance.

Shortly after their departure, a black fruit on a certain tree suddenly began to glow with faint black light. The tree's fruits were vaguely humanoid in shape, presenting a rather disturbing sight to behold, and the fruit that was glowing began to slowly warp as a set of facial features appeared on it, following which it slowly opened it eyes and turned its gaze to the direction that Han Li and Shi Chuankong had just departed in.

A series of black ripples were flashing incessantly within its black eyes, and at the same time, there was an enormous black cloud that was dozens of acres in size traveling rapidly through the air countless kilometers away.

Standing atop the black cloud were close to a hundred half-human, half-beast beings, and they were led by none other than Tie Yu, who had a furious look on his face.

All of his subordinates were making sure to stand far away from him for fear of falling prey to his wrath.

Many of them were seated with their legs crossed all over the black cloud, seemingly unleashing some type of secret technique.

"Have there still not been any leads?" Tie Yu suddenly asked.

He had promised to bring Shi Chuankong's head back to the Golden Rhinoceros King within a month, yet half that time had already elapsed, and he hadn't even tracked down his targets yet.

A golden-robed man strode forward with tightly gritted teeth, then reported, "We're trying our best, Master Tie Yu, but there's too much ground to cover, and those two haven't left any traces behind, so we haven't been able to track them down yet."

"Useless piece of trash!" Tie Yu roared as a layer or green light emerged over his body, then formed a series of green snake projections that glowered intently at the golden-robed man.

The man seemed to be extremely fearful of these snake projections, and he began trembling uncontrollably as he fell to his knees before kowtowing over and over again.

"Please forgive me, Master Tie Yu, I'll be sure to redouble my efforts..."

"Get down there and keep searching! I'll give you three more days. If you still can't find them by then, I'll take your head to the Golden Rhinoceros King too!" Tie Yu roared.

The golden-robed man immediately scurried away, and right at this moment, a dark-skinned man who was seated on the black cloud suddenly rose to his feet as he declared with an elated expression, "Master Tie Yu, we've found them!"

The man was holding a black wooden figure, and at this moment, its eyes were open, and there were black ripples flashing within them.

Tie Yu's eyes immediately lit up upon hearing this, and he hurriedly asked, "Where are they?"

"They're in the Black Scale Forest, and they're currently traveling northward," the dark-skinned man hurriedly repiled.

"Northward? It looks like they're planning to leave the Ten Hazards Mountain Range. We'll just have to intercept them!" Tie Ye mused with a cold sneer, and he immediately made a hand seal, upon which the black cloud underfoot changed directions and diverged away from its original trajectory.

……

Han Li and Shi Chuankong continued onward, and close to a day passed by in the blink of an eye.

The black forest up ahead gradually became sparser and sparser, and a lush, green mountain range appeared up ahead.

The warm sunlight was able to filter through the sparser vegetation, making the air much warmer, and a warm breeze was gently caressing their cheeks.

The field of view widened up ahead, revealing a mountain range that stretched as far as the eyes could see, presenting a breathtaking sight to behold.

Shi Chuankong spread open his arms as he took a deep breath in a blissful manner.

The black forest that they had just emerged from was very cold and forbidding, making for a very unappealing environment even for a devilish cultivator like himself.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged, but it was clear that he was also glad to be out of the forest.

Shi Chuankong turned to Han Li, and he was just about to say something when the latter suddenly grabbed him by the collar before darting back in retreat.

Shi Chuankong had just been dragged away from the spot where he was standing when a thick green arrow pierced through the ground there.

The arrow was thirty to forty feet in length and as thick as an arm. There were countless green patterns engraved onto the arrow's shaft, giving off rays of warped green light that formed a series of black snake projections that were hissing incessantly.

The arrow had arrived at an astonishing speed, and even though Shi Chuankong was able to just barely evade it thanks to Han Li, a sickly sweet aroma still managed to worm its way up his nostrils, upon which he was instantly struck by a feeble and numb sensation.

There's poison at work!

As soon as this thought sprang into his mind, Shi Chuankong immediately flipped a hand over to produce a pair of longan-sized white pills that he promptly swallowed, and a layer of white light emerged over his body, while the green light on his face and the feeble sensation in his body faded away.

"Are you alright?" Han Li asked.

He had also inhaled some of the poison, but having cultivated the Chaotic Myriad Poison Body, he had become extremely resistant to all poisons, and that, coupled with his tremendous physical constitution, ensured that he remained completely unaffected. [1]

"I'm fine," Shi Chuankong replied.

"Who's there?" Han Li called out as he turned to a certain direction.

A black cloud slowly emerged up ahead amid a flash of black light, and standing atop the cloud were none other than Tie Yu and his subordinates.

At this moment, Tie Yu was observing Han Li with a hint of surprise on his face as he remarked, "It's quite impressive that you were able to evade my Divine Poison Arrow."

He raised a hand to make a beckoning motion as he spoke, and the arrow immediately swung around, then shrank down significantly before vanishing up his sleeve.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong's expressions changed slightly at the sight of the formidable lineup before them, and the latter stepped forward as he cupped his fist in a salute and said, "May I ask which one of the ten kings you serve?

“The two of us inadvertently stumbled into the Ten Hazards Mountain Range, and we were just planning to leave. We harbor no ill will toward any of the ten kings, and we're willing to offer up two hundred thousand Devilish Origin Stones if you let us go."

"You don't even know who's territory this is?"

"Is that supposed to be a joke? He wants to bribe us with just two hundred thousand Devilish Origin Stones!"

"Ptui!"

"We can let you go, but you have to leave your heads behind!"

All of Tie Yu's subordinates immediately burst into laughter upon hearing Shi Chuankong's offer, and Han Li and Shi Chuankong's expressions both darkened slightly upon seeing this.

Tie Yu raised a hand, and all of his subordinates instantly fell silent.

"Are you from outside the mountain range?" Tie Yu asked in a cold voice.

"That's right. May I ask..."

Before Shi Chuankong had a chance to finish his sentence, a look of fierce resentment flashed through Tie Yu's eyes as he declared in a cold voice, "All outsiders deserve to die! Kill them, but don't be too rough. Make sure to keep their heads intact, in particular."

All of his subordinates instantly gave a collective affirmative response, then charged toward Han Li and Shi Chuankong in unison with their weapons brandished.

His subordinates were all quite formidable, and there were over ten Golden Immortals among them.

They were led by a trio that consisted of a man silver hair, green eyes, and a horn on his head, a red-haired elderly man with skin as coarse as tree bark, and a golden-haired young woman with a pair of wings on her back, all three of whom were at the early-High Zenith Stage.

Theoretically speaking, such a formidable lineup was more than sufficient to deal with an early-High Zenith Stage human and a peak-Golden Immortal Stage devilish being.

The horned man made a hand seal, and radiant green light erupted out of his body before forming a ball, following which the ball of green light flew through the air and transformed into a green cloud.

The green cloud was instantly set alight, and a burst of law power fluctuations erupted out of it to encompass both Han Li and Shi Chuankong.

At the same time, the red-haired elderly man began to chant an incantation, and three huge tiger head projections appeared above his head in a flash, all three of which then abruptly vanished into thin air.

In the next instant, the three tiger head projections appeared directly in front of Han Li and Shi Chuankong, then opened their mouths to bite down viciously upon them.

Even before the three tiger heads had fully descended, they were giving off a harrowing aura that struck a sense of involuntary fear into the heart of the beholder.

At the same time, the golden-haired young woman spread her wings, and they began to glow as brightly as the sun.

With a flap of her wings, countless beams of golden light were released, raining down upon Han Li and Shi Chuankong in a torrential barrage.

Every single beam of golden light was a golden feather that was giving off extremely formidable law powers, and with three High Zenith cultivators attacking at once, all of the devilish qi within a radius of dozens of kilometers instantly began to churn violently, while the surrounding space also began to tremble and buzz.

A grim look appeared on Shi Chuankong's face at the sight of the barrage of oncoming attacks, and he was just about to spring into action when Han Li stepped forward and declared, "Leave it to me!"

Eighteen streaks of azure light shot out of his sleeves in rapid succession as he spoke, and each streak of light contained an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword.

After reaching the High Zenith Stage, Han Li's immortal spiritual power reserves had been significantly enhanced, thereby allowing him to control eighteen Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords at once.

[1]. For more information on the Chaotic Myriad Poison Body, please refer to RMJI Chapter 1846: Chaotic Myriad Poison Body.

[Back]

Chapter 779: Slaying the Enemies

Han Li wore a solemn expression as he made a rapid string of hand seals, and the eighteen Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords split up into two batches, with six of them circling around him, while the remaining twelve shot forth through the air.

In the blink of an eye, over a thousand azure sword projections appeared, forming a vast sea of sword qi that was several acres in size before sweeping toward the oncoming enemies.

Tie Yu raised an eyebrow upon seeing this, but he didn't appear concerned at all. The sword array appeared to be quite formidable, but it didn't contain much law power, so it didn't pose any threat in his eyes.

His subordinates clearly also thought the same thing, and the fiery green cloud, the crimson tiger head projections, and the barrage of golden feathers lit up even further before striking the azure sword array with tremendous power, immediately followed by the attacks from all of the other Golden Immortals and True Immortals.

A string of resounding booms rang out, and the azure sword array shuddered violently as close to half of the azure sword qi within it was eradicated in the blink of an eye.

However, instead of displaying any concern, a faint smile appeared on Han Li's face, and he abruptly switched to a different hand seal.

The streaks of azure sword qi instantly transformed into even thicker streaks of golden sword qi, all of which had arcs of golden lightning dancing over them, giving off formidable lightning law power fluctuations.

The entire sea of sword qi was instantly restored to its former state, while a peculiar dragon design appeared deep within it.

Incredibly formidable sword qi fluctuations erupted out of the sea of golden sword qi, and they were several times more powerful than the energy fluctuations released by the azure sword qi.

All of the attacks that had plunged into the sea of golden sword qi were instantly destroyed. Not only was the sword array itself extremely formidable, the arcs of golden lightning within it were particularly potent when it came to eradicating baleful qi, so it was able to destroy all of the oncoming attacks with ease.

The sword array continued to descend right before the astonished eyes of the High Zenith Stage trio, and they immediately began to retreat, but it was already too late.

The sea of golden sword qi crashed down upon the trio, completely encompassing them before they were able to get away, and Tie Yu immediately began rushing into the fray upon seeing this.

The three High Zenith cultivators were all precious subordinates of the Golden Rhinoceros King, and if they were to be slain here, even if he could capture the heads of Han Li and Shi Chuankong, it would be far too heavy a loss to incur.

As Tie Yu flew through the air, a giant green bow appeared above his head amid a flash of green light. There were nine Divine Poison Arrows nocked on the bowstring, and all of them were let loose at once.

The nine arrows hurtled directly toward the sea of golden sword qi, leaving nine long, black trails in their wake.

The nine arrows were extremely fast, and they reached the sea of golden sword qi in an instant, but right at this moment, six golden flying swords appeared in their path, radiating dazzling golden light as they quickly crossed over one another to form a giant sword lotus flower.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as a series of spatial rifts appeared in the nearby area, and the golden sword lotus flower exploded as the six flying swords were sent flying in all directions, but the nine Divine Poison Arrows were also stopped in their tracks.

Right at this moment, the space in front of Tie Yu suddenly began to tremble violently, and countless silver runes surged forth before converging toward him from all directions.

All of a sudden, Tie Yu felt as if there were an invisible hand closing around him from all directions, forcing him to stop.

Shi Chuankong was standing in mid-air not far away from him, holding a silver lute as he observed Tie Yu with a cold smile.

Right at this moment, the sea of golden sword qi began to descend upon the devilish beings trapped within it, and the horned man's expression changed drastically as he swept a sleeve through the air to release a pair of large azure flags, both of which were burning with azure flames that were giving off formidable glacial fire law power fluctuations.

The two flags unfurled at his behest, forming a thick azure fire barrier around his entire body.

At the same time, the red-haired elderly man opened his mouth to release a crimson pagoda, and as it revolved on the spot in mid-air, rays of crimson light cascaded down from the pagoda to envelop his entire body.

As for the golden-haired young woman, a suit of heavy golden armor quickly appeared over her body amid an eruption of radiant golden light, and countless golden runes were dancing over the suit of armor, giving off bursts of law power fluctuations and an indestructible appearance.

The three of them were very quick to react, immediately summoning their devilish treasures, but the other devilish beings were not so fortunate, and a chorus of blood-curdling howls instantly rang out as most of them were torn to shreds in the blink of an eye.

Some of them were able to adopt some protective measures, but they were still sliced into ribbons, nonetheless, and in the blink of an eye, all that remained in the sword array were the three early-High Zenith cultivators and four or five Golden Immortals.

All of them were gathered in a circle with their backs facing each other, and devilish treasures were flying all around them, forming a colorful protective barrier to keep the surrounding sword qi at bay.

Han Li harrumphed coldly as he switched to a different hand seal, and the dragon design at the center of the sword array instantly began to glow radiantly.

An earth-shattering draconic roar rang out as twelve giant golden dragons flew out of the center of the sword array at once, and every single one of them was several thousand feet in length, while their bodies were formed entirely by golden lightning and streaks of sword qi.

In the next instant, the twelve golden dragons pounced onto the colorful protective barrier, wrapping themselves around the barrier before constricting with all their might.

The protective barrier was instantly destroyed, and at the same time, countless streaks of sword qi erupted out of the bodies of the twelve golden dragons to inundate the horned man and the others.

A few of them had their bodies torn to shreds before they even had a chance to cry out, and before Tie Yu had a chance to intervene, everyone in the sword array had already perished.

Tie Yu was furious to see this, while all of the other devilish beings on the dark cloud in the distance were looking on with astonished expressions.

Even Shi Chuankong was staring at Han Li with a stunned look in his eyes.

Han Li exhaled as he made a hand seal, and the golden sword array instantly began to shrink down before vanishing altogether, reverting back into twelve Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

However, the lightning runes on the swords had become far dimmer than before, while the lightning law powers emanating from them had also become quite feeble, as if the lightning law powers inside them had been exhausted.

The twelve flying swords flew back into Han Li's dantian at his behest, and having just had so much of their lightning law powers exhausted, it was going to take a nurturing period for them to recover.

The sword array that he had just unleashed was the Horned Dragon Sword Array that he had learned from Jin Hai, and it was a secret sword array of the Boundless Sword Sect, one that was rather similar to his Azure Coil Sword Array.

However, in contrast with the Azure Coil Sword Array, which required seventy-two flying swords to unleash, the Horned Dragon Sword Array only required twelve flying swords, but it was extremely taxing on the swords used and could only be unleashed using flying swords of an extremely high caliber.

Even the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords most likely wouldn't have been able to withstand the strain if it wasn't for their recent evolution in the golden lightning pond.

Flames of fury were burning in Tie Yu's eyes at the sight of the shredded remains of his subordinates, but in the next instant, he took a deep breath, and his enraged expression quickly faded.

His subordinates were already dead, so there was nothing that he could do. On the bright side, without those people getting in the way, he would be able to fight without any qualms.

"Impressive! It appears I underestimated you. You've earned the right for me to personally put an end to your life!" Tie Yu declared as fierce killing intent rose up from his entire body alongside a tremendous and violent aura that instantly filled the entire area.

Everyone standing atop the dark cloud was instantly swept away like falling leaves in a gust of wind in the face of his aura, and Shi Chuankong was also forced to stagger back over a thousand feet before just barely managing to steady himself with a stunned look on his face.

He turned to take a glance at Han Li, then flew back even further, exiting the battlefield altogether.

Out of everyone present, Han Li was the only one who was able to remain completely unmoved, but his brows also furrowed slightly as he raised a hand to make a beckoning motion, summoning the six Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords from before back to himself.

However, at this moment, there were many streaks of mist-like green light wrapped around the six flying swords, and they were burrowing into the swords like living creatures while giving off vicious law power fluctuations.

The golden light emanating from the six flying swords was quickly fading, as if they had been corroded somehow, and green spots appeared on their surfaces before quickly spreading.

Han Li's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and arcs of golden lightning instantly erupted out of the six flying swords at his behest, attempting to eradicate the streaks of green light around them.

However, the green light continued to cling firmly to the flying swords, refusing to be dispelled.

"Nothing can escape from my Green Cloud Miasma!" Tie Yu chortled as he reached out to make a grabbing motion, and nine arrows appeared above his head amid a flash of green light.

All nine arrows were nocked on the bowstring of the green bow, which had been drawn back in full.

The nine arrows were then fired and reached Han Li in the blink of an eye, traveling over twice as fast as before!

Chapter 780: Eradicating the Enemy

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as arcs of golden lightning sprang out of his body, and he dodged to the side while flipping a hand over to stow the six flying swords into his Profound Heavenly Gourd.

The poisonous green light clinging to the six flying swords was instantly sucked away by the green light within the Profound Heavenly Gourd, and the green spots on their surfaces also faded, much to Han Li's relief.

"You're not getting away!" Tie Yu yelled as he switched to a different hand seal, and the nine arrows immediately swerved mid-flight to continue pursuing Han Li.

All of a sudden, the nine arrows connected as one, causing them to speed up even further, yet right as Han Li was on the verge of being caught, he took a glance behind him while sweeping a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of green light that swept up the nine arrows.

The poisonous green light emanating from the arrows quickly faded until there was only a thin layer left, and Tie Yu could sense that his spiritual connection with them was also diminishing.

His expression instantly darkened slightly as he opened his mouth to release a ball of green light, then plunged a hand into it before pulling out a green whip that was lined with extremely sharp hooked spikes.

With a flick of his wrist, the whip elongated rapidly, instantly crossing over a distance of several thousand feet before wrapping itself around the nine arrows and giving them a firm tug.

A dull thump rang out as the whip was able to wrench the nine arrows out of the surrounding green light, and Han Li raised an eyebrow upon seeing this, then withdrew the burst of green light before suddenly flying directly toward Tie Yu.

At the same time, he began to chant a rapid incantation, and his body split up into around a dozen identical arcs of golden lightning, all of which split up before converging toward Tie Yu from different directions.

All of the arcs of lightning were also giving of identical auras, making it impossible to determine which one was Han Li.

Tie Yu's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and he raised a hand to grab onto the bow above his head, following which nine more arrows appeared on its bowstring before being fired through the air.

As soon as the nine arrows were fired, they immediately split up into countless green arrow projections that rained down from the heavens.

Every single one of the arrow projections was giving off fierce poison law power fluctuations, causing all of the nearby devilish qi to churn violently.

The volley of arrows instantly pierced through all of the arcs of golden lightning, causing them to explode, and one of them reverted back into Han Li.

At this moment, his entire body was clad in a suit of armor formed entirely by arcs of golden lightning, and he remained completely unscathed.

As soon as the true Han Li was revealed, Tie Yu immediately made a hand seal, redirecting all of the arrow projections in the sky toward Han Li.

In response, Han Li raised both hands to release a series of thick arcs of golden lightning, all of which were giving off formidable lightning law powers.

With a sweep of his sleeve, the arcs of golden lightning erupted forth in a relentless torrent, forming a dense net of golden lightning in front of him.

The volley of arrows descended upon the net of golden lightning amid a string of resounding booms, but the net of lightning was able to withstand the assault without displaying any signs of caving.

Han Li gave a cold harrumph as he made a grabbing motion, and eighteen Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords instantly appeared at his behest before releasing countless streaks of golden sword qi that formed a golden mountain, which crashed straight into the volley of arrow projections.

The golden mountain was able to barge its way straight through the arrow projections without encountering any resistance, and it appeared right in front of Tie Yu at an astonishing speed.

Tie Yu's expression changed slightly as he opened his mouth to release a black shield, which instantly transformed into a protective black light barrier while he dodged to the side as quickly as he could.

The mountain of golden sword projections came crashing down, and despite the black light barrier's unremarkable appearance, it was able to keep most of the streaks of golden sword qi at bay.

However, some of the sword qi was still able to pierce through the light barrier, and even though Tie Yu was taking evasive measures to the best of his abilities, several streaks of sword qi were still able to catch up to him, slicing several deep gashes into his body.

A furious look appeared in his eyes as he let loose a thunderous roar, and plumes of mist-like green light began to surge out of his body in a frenzy, forming a green spirit domain that was close to fifty kilometers in size around him.

The spirit domain contained incredibly dense poisonous green mist, and all of the trees in the mountain range below that came into contact with the green mist were instantly reduced to puddles of green goo.

At this point, Tie Yu's subordinates had already fled into the distance, so they weren't caught within the spirit domain.

However, the same couldn't be said about Shi Chuankong, and the protective spiritual light around his body was being rapidly whittled down by the surrounding poisonous mist.

He hurriedly summoned several protective spiritual treasures, which formed several layers of light barriers around him, but those light barriers were also being rapidly eaten away.

However, those light barriers had bought him some time, and he began rapidly strumming the strings of his Virata Lute, releasing a stream of silver runes that formed a silver array around him.

In the next instant, Shi Chuankong vanished from within the green spirit domain, then reappeared dozens of kilometers away immediately thereafter.

Tie Yu paid no heed to Shi Chuankong, continuing to glower intently at Han Li.

All of the poisonous green mist within the spirit domain surged toward Han Li from all directions at his behest, forming a series of giant green dragons that swooped down upon him.

All of the green dragons were giving off incredibly formidable poison law power fluctuations, causing the space in their wake to tremble violently.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged upon seeing this, and he made a string of rapid hand seals, releasing a spirit domain of his own.

Now that he was at the High Zenith Stage, the golden ripples in his time spirit domain had become far denser than before, and as soon as the spirit domain was unleashed, the surrounding poisonous mist and green dragons were instantly slowed down significantly.

An astonished look appeared in Tie Yu's eyes upon seeing this, and he immediately tried to do something, but his movements had also become extremely slow and sluggish.

Han Li made a hand seal, and arcs of golden lightning sprang out of his body before forming a lightning array around him.

The arcs of golden lightning were far dimmer than usual within Tie Yu's poison spirit domain, but they were still able to form a functional lightning array, and in the next instant, Han Li vanished from the spot before reappearing behind Tie Yu, then opened his mouth to release a bolt of radiant golden lightning toward Tie Yu's head.

Tie Yu was extremely alarmed by this turn of events, and he wasn't in time to turn around, so he could only channel his poison law powers with all his might.

The surrounding poisonous mist gathered behind him, forming a green giant that was over a hundred feet tall, and it was none other than his domain spirit.

The spirit domain's entire body was giving off fierce poison law power fluctuations, and its speed wasn't hampered by much as it opened its mouth to devour the bolt of golden lightning.

However, before Tie Yu even had a chance to catch his breath, a golden flying sword suddenly shot out of the poisonous mist in front of him, and it was none other than one of Han Li's Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

Some green spots had already appeared on the sword, but it was still incredibly fast as it flew a lap around Tie Yu's head like lightning.

Tie Yu's expression instantly stiffened, following which his head fell to the side.

Han Li flicked a finger through the air in an expressionless manner, releasing a streak of golden sword qi, which pierced into Tie Yu's head, causing it to explode like a watermelon and completely destroying the soul inside.

Tie Yu's headless body began to plummet out of the sky as a geyser of blood erupted out of its neck, but it was caught by a burst of azure light released by Han Li.

In the wake of Tie Yu's demise, the green domain spirit's body quickly began to dissipate, and it let loose one final indignant roar before it disintegrated into nothingness.

Han Li made a hand seal, and a ball of golden light flew back to him, containing the eighteen Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, as well as a green bow and nine arrows.

The flying swords had all been corroded to a certain extent by the green spirit domain, but not to a very severe extent, and Han Li stowed the flying sword, the bow, and the arrows away into his Profound Heavenly Gourd, then withdrew his time spirit domain as well.

A few moments later, all of the golden light and poisonous mist in the sky faded away, and Shi Chuankong appeared beside Han Li with a wide smile as he praised, "I am truly in awe of your incredible power, Fellow Daoist Li."

In the distance, all of Tie Yu's subordinates were looking on with incredulous expressions.

The late-High Zenith Stage Tie Yu had just been slain by an early-High Zenith Stage human cultivator!

In the next instant, someone let loose a panicked roar, and everyone fled into the distance.

A cold look flashed through Han Li's eyes as he prepared to set off after them.

By killing Tie Yu, they had made an enemy out of one of the Ten Hazards, so all of these people had to be killed as well.

"Take a rest, Fellow Daoist Li. Leave these people to me," Shi Chuankong said with a faint smile, then set off after the fleeing devilish beings as a streak of dark purple light.

Meanwhile, Han Li turned his attention back to Tie Yu's headless body, and after recovering a green storage bracelet, he released several balls of crimson flames that set the body alight, instantly incinerating it into ashes.

Chapter 781: Intercepted

After taking a pill, Han Li injected his spiritual sense into the green storage bracelet, and several minutes later, an elated look suddenly appeared on his face as he raised a hand to make a grabbing motion, upon which a piece of gray bone appeared in his grasp.

It was an object similar to a jade slip, and it contained a map of the Ten Hazards Mountain Range.

Right at this moment, a streak of dark purple light flew back from afar, then reverted back into Shi Chuankong.

"I've taken care of all of them, and I was able to perform a soul search technique on one of them. They were all subordinates of the Golden Rhinoceros King, one of the Ten Hazards, and the man you just killed is called Tie Yu, one of the Golden Rhinoceros King's most prized subordinates," Shi Chuankong informed.

"I see. Take a look at this, it's a map of the Ten Hazards Mountain Range that I found in Tie Yu's storage bracelet," Han Li replied as he handed the gray bone to Shi Chankong.

An elated look appeared on Shi Chuankong's face upon hearing this.

"That's great! We'll finally be able to know where we're going now."

However, his elation was then replaced with a grim expression as he continued, "I've heard that the Golden Rhinoceros King is an extremely violent and vindictive man. Now that we've killed his subordinates, he'll most likely be sending more people after us soon, so let's get out of here."

Han Li raised no objections to this, and the two of them flew away into the distance, vanishing out of sight in the blink of an eye.

……

At the Golden Rhinoceros King's cave abode.

Inside a resplendent golden hall, the Golden Rhinoceros King suddenly kicked aside the seductive maidservant who was massaging his leg, then stood up with such force that his flabby rolls trembled as he hurled the golden chalice in his hand viciously onto the ground.

The chalice was instantly smashed on the ground, spilling out all the red wine inside.

The maidservants around him immediately kowtowed to the ground while trembling in fear, not even daring to raise their heads for fear of meeting the same fate as the chalice.

"That useless fool! Someone go check if Tie Yu's head is still intact. If it is, then bring it back to me, and I'll place it at the foot of the stairs so I can step on it every day!" the Golden Rhinoceros King roared in his comical, high-pitched voice, but no one dared to display any amusement.

Around a dozen of his subordinates outside the palace immediately gave an affirmative response before hurriedly departing, but the Golden Rhinoceros King was still feeling furious as he whirled around to grab onto a golden chalice before hurling that one onto the ground as well.

A brawny man clad in a suit of golden chainmail armor stepped forward from the side of the hall, then extended a respectful bow as he said, "Don't be angry, my king. I'm willing to succeed where Tie Yu has failed and claim Shi Chuankong's head for you."

The man had a similar build to the Golden Rhinoceros King, but as opposed to flabby rolls, his body was one that consisted solely of bands of thick muscle. His facial features were also quite similar to those of a human, with the exception of his sharp fangs and his nose, the latter of which resembled a ball of black coal.

The Golden Rhinoceros King's expression eased slightly at the sight of the man, and a contemplative look appeared in his eyes as he turned his gaze to another man, this one dressed in a white robe.

It was a tall man with a sword strapped to his back, he had a snake-like head with only a pair of small holes in the place of a nose. There was a cold look in his eyes, and he resembled an icy statue.

"If he's managed to kill even Tie Yu, then this Shi Chuankong must have some tricks up his sleeve. I suppose that makes sense, given the compensation that Shi Zhanfeng was willing to offer me in exchange for his head. Tong Yu, Yin Yu, go after them together, and try to capture him alive," the Golden Rhinoceros King said.

The brawny Tong Yu took a glance at the white-robed man, then said, "There's no need for that, my king, I can get the job done on my own."

"Do I need you to tell me what to do?" the Golden Rhinoceros King asked in a cold voice as his eyes narrowed slightly.

A hint of fear flashed through Tong Yu's eyes as he hurriedly replied, "I wouldn't dare, my king."

"Why are we capturing him alive, my king?" Yin Yu asked.

"Only by keeping him alive can I use him as leverage in negotiations with Shi Zhanfeng. I'm going to require additional compensation now that even Tie Yu has fallen," the Golden Rhinoceros King explained as he grabbed onto one of his maidservants and began fondling her.

"Alright, I'll make sure to capture him alive," Yin Yu replied with a nod.

"You can go now," the Golden Rhinoceros King instructed, and the two promptly departed.

……

Several days later.

An inconspicuous ball of silver light was glowing within a dense forest in the Ten Hazards Mountain Range that was enshrouded in purple mist, and there were faint spatial fluctuations emanating from the silver light.

Inside the ball of silver light, Han Li and Shi Chuankong were standing across from each other, while laying in between them was a charred octopus-like carcass that was several hundred feet long. The creature had hundreds of tentacles, but most of them had already been severed at this point.

"I can't believe it took us this long to take down a mere True Immortal Stage Hundred Tentacle Beast!" Shi Chuankong mused as he aimed a kick at the charred carcass.

"It possessed some abilities that made it very difficult to track down. If it wasn't for your spatial spirit domain, it'd most likely still be eluding us right now," Han Li said.

"Alright, now that we've harvested its demon core, we should continue on our way. The Golden Rhinoceros King isn't just going to let us go free," Shi Chuankong said.

"Let's travel on my flying carriage from here onward. We can fly at a higher altitude to avoid being harrassed by these demon beasts," Han Li replied with a nod, and he summoned a green jade flying carriage as he spoke.

Shi Chuankong nodded in response as he withdrew his spirit domain, then hopped onto the flying carriage, which sped away as a streak of green light.

However, the carriage had only traveled several dozen kilometers before drawing to an abrupt halt.

Two figures were standing in mid-air up ahead, namely a brawny man in a suit of golden armor and a tall white-robed man.

"I don't think they're here for a friendly chat," Shi Chuankong mused with furrowed brows. "They didn't even bring any small fry with them this time."

Han Li examined the two men momentarily to find that the golden-armored man was at the late-High Zenith Stage, while the white-robed man was at the pinnacle of the High Zenith Stage, and both of their auras were far more powerful than Tie Yu's.

"Which one of you killed Tie Yu?" Tong Yu asked.

"Are you here to avenge him?" Han Li scoffed.

"I just want to know who killed that idiot," Tong Yu replied with an amused expression.

"That won't be difficult at all for you to find out. Once you're dead, you can go and ask him yourself in the afterlife," Shi Chuankong said with a faint smile.

Tong Yu took a glance at Shi Chuankong, then turned his gaze to Han Li as he said to Yin Yu, "We have to keep that one alive. I'm not very good when it comes to finesse, so I'll leave him to you, but I'll gladly take care of this one."

Yin Yu slowly drew his sword, neither nodding in agreement nor shaking his head to refuse this arrangement.

Tong Yu seemed to have already grown accustomed to this, and he stomped a foot down onto the space below, upon which he abruptly vanished from the spot amid a resounding boom.

Han Li's pupils contracted slightly at the sight of Tong Yu's astonishing speed, and he instantly stowed his green jade flying carriage away before launching himself forward.

A streak of azure light crashed into a streak of black light three hundred feet away amid an earth-shattering boom, and Han Li felt as if he had crashed into a mountain, one that was only continuing to gather momentum over time in waves.

Initially, he was able to remain firm in opposition, but as the waves of force compounded upon one another, he began to struggle more and more, and finally, with the seventh wave of compounding force, he was finally sent flying back through the air.

Shi Chuankong was just about to enter the fray when a streak of white swordlight suddenly appeared before descending toward his head.

He immediately dodged to the side, but as the streak of swordlight descended, it began to suck in the surrounding world's origin qi, expanding further and further in size like a snowball rolling down a snowy mountain, causing the nearby space to warp around it.

Shi Chuankong could feel a burst of tremendous suction force surging out of the streak of swordlight, and he hurriedly made a hand seal to conjure up a spatial barrier to keep the suction force at bay, following which he sprang back in retreat.

The spatial barrier was instantly torn to shreds by the streak of swordlight, but at this point, Shi Chuankong had already retreated to a safe distance away, and after steadying himself, he flipped a hand over to summon a silver spear.

Meanwhile, Yin Yu was glowering at him like a hunter observing his prey.

At the same time, Tong Yu and Han Li were clashing against each other over and over again, and just like their first clash, the longer they remained in opposition against one another, the more momentum Tong Yu was able to build up.

Han Li could sense law power fluctuations emanating from Tong Yu's body, but he couldn't fathom what type of law powers these were.

However, he had found a solution to the problem, which was to only engage in brief clashes against Tong Yu before disengaging himself to search for another opportunity to strike.

However, despite Tong Yu's rough appearance, he was a very shrewd combatant, and that, coupled with his incredible speed, meant that Han Li was unable to find any holes in his defense.

Chapter 782: Fierce Battle

"You think that you can handle me just by keeping our clashes brief?" Tong Yu scoffed as wisps of black qi spilled out from the gaps in his suit of armor, forming a cloud of black mist that encompassed his entire body.

All of the devilish qi in the surrounding area also surged into the cloud of black mist, and all of a sudden, Han Li found himself enshrouded within it as well.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, but before he had a chance to do anything, a fist was coming straight at him with tremendous power.

He raised an arm to defend himself, but another fist suddenly came swinging at him from the left.

Before he had a chance to shield himself, he was struck by a heavy blow to the chest, and he gave a muffled groan as he was sent flying through the air.

The cloud of black mist continued to cling to him, and several more punches arrived at once, striking him in the temple, the back of the head, the chest, and other vital regions.

Every single one of these punches packed tremendous force, and they struck him with resounding booms.

Han Li could feel his own immortal spiritual power circulation becoming hampered by the blows,and he hurriedly channeled his true spirit bloodline to conjure up a suit of Xuanwu armor.

The punches fell upon the suit of armor in a torrential barrage, and while the suit of Xuanwu armor did cushion the blows somewhat, they were still far from pleasant to deal with.

Han Li activated his Infernal Devilish Eyes as he swept his gaze across the surrounding black mist, but he was surprised to discover that he couldn't see Tong Yu within it.

All he could see were thousands of fists formed by black mist hurtling toward him from all directions, and it was no wonder that he couldn't defend himself.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he summoned his Mantra Axis Scripture, and as soon as all of the oncoming fists entered the golden ripples released by the axis, they were instantly slowed down to a crawl.

Han Li swept his gaze over them to discover that they numbered in the tens of thousands, and a faint smile appeared on his face as he flipped a hand over to summon an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword.

Immediately thereafter, he shot forward through the air with sword in hand, and the lightning patterns on the sword were flashing incessantly. Following the injection of Bone Rinsing Golden Lightning, the Divine Devilbane Lightning in the sword had attained lightning law powers, making it far more formidable than before.

Thick arcs of golden lightning erupted through the air in all directions, tearing through the surrounding black mist.

All of the black fists that were struck by the golden lightning instantly disintegrated into black mist, and their auras completely vanished.

Han Li continued to scour his surroundings with his Infernal Devilish Eyes, but all he could see was a boundless expanse of black devilish qi in all directions.

A hint of frustration began to well up in Han Li's heart upon seeing this. While he had managed to restrict the devilish qi with his Mantra Treasured Axis, they were completely impervious to his sword qi and lightning-based attacks.

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to him, and a fiery silver figure abruptly appeared on his shoulder.

If I can't cut you, then I'll just burn you!

The fiery silver figure instantly transformed into a silver fire raven at Han Li's behest, and Han Li withdrew his Mantra Treasured Axis as the fire raven flew straight into the cloud of black mist.

Huge waves of silver flames swept through the air, and the vast expanse of black mist began to rapidly shrink in the face of the scorching flames.

An agonized howl rang out as Tong Yu appeared within the black mist with multiple burns all over his entire body.

"What the hell is that thing?!"

Wisps of black mist slowly surged into his body as he spoke, healing the burns that had been inflicted by the Essence Fire Raven.

Han Li naturally wasn't going to answer the question, and he darted forward through the air while making a beckoning motion with his free hand.

The other seventeen Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords shot forth in unison, and as they approached Tong Yu, they released hundreds of sword projections that surrounded him from all directions.

At the same time, the Essence Fire Raven was hovering behind him, waiting to strike at the first sign of weakness.

Han Li was charging at Tong Yu in a full-frontal assault, while all of the surrounding sword projections converged toward him.

A hint of fury flashed through Tong Yu's eyes as he let loose a loud roar, and a layer of black light instantly erupted out of his body, forming a spirit domain that instantly encompassed Han Li and all of the flying swords.

In the instant that the flying swords and sword projections pierced into the spirit domain, all of them began to tremble violently, and they were enveloped by layers upon layers of devilish qi.

After being ensnared within the black mist, the sword projections quickly turned a lifeless gray color, and the spiritual power within them was completely exhausted, following which they disintegrated into nothingness.

The seventeen Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords had also been caught within bands of black mist, and even though they were also being rapidly sapped of their spiritual qi, they continued to struggle against their bindings.

At the same time, plumes of black mist began to wrap themselves around Han Li like black serpents before slowly contracting.

The black mist was gradually turning gray while taking on the form of Han Li's outline, and it appeared as if he were being turned into an immobile statue.

The Essence Fire Raven immediately flew toward Han Li with silver flames surging out of its body upon seeing this, but it was intercepted by Tong Yu, who made a hand seal with a cold sneer on its face, conjuring up a pair of giant hands formed by black sand, which joined their palms together to trap the Essence Fire Raven between them.

Immediately thereafter, Tong Yu swept a sleeve through the air to release a golden talisman that fell upon the giant hands, and the talisman instantly vanished, following which several long strings of strange runes appeared over the black hands to tie them together.

A burst of formidable restrictive power then surged out of the giant hands, and despite the Essence Fire Raven's best efforts, it was unable to struggle free as the fiery power radiating from its body was firmly contained by the peculiar energy fluctuations being released by the runes.

On the other side, Shi Chuankong was being forced back into retreat by the formidable sword qi unleashed by Yin Yu, and at this point, he was already very far from Han Li.

He could see what was happening in Han Li's battle out of the corner of his eye, and a sense of despair began to set in.

"Don't make this more difficult for yourself than it has to be. Your companion may have mastered the laws of time, but there's no way he can oppose Tong Yu. Our king instructed us to capture you alive, so just come back with us to meet your brother. If you surrender now, you can be spared of torment, but if you continue to resist, then I'll amputate your limbs, then torture you to my heart's content before taking you back," Yin Yu said with a cold expression.

"My brother? So it really was Shi Zhanfeng. What compensation did he offer your king in exchange for my life? I'm willing to give three times the compensation if you let me go," Shi Chuankong proposed as he forced a smile onto his own face.

"If you want to negotiate, then you can negotiate with our king. I'm just here to kill," Yin Yu replied in a cold voice.

"In that case, can you get Fellow Daoist Tong Yu to stop so I can go and see your king with my companion?" Shi Chuankong negotiated, while a silver lute appeared in his grasp, concealed within his baggy sleeve.

However, his sneaky tactics failed to trick Yin Yu, and a cold look flashed through the latter's eyes as he slashed his longsword through the air, unleashing hundreds of streaks of white swordlight that formed a giant mountain before crashing down upon Shi Chuankong.

Shi Chuankong was just about to dart back in retreat when he felt a sharp pain in his knees, and he looked down to discover that two sharp streaks of transparent sword qi had emerged, seemingly out of thin air, before instantly piercing through his knees.

That split-second delay made it impossible for him to evade the oncoming attack, so he had no choice but to raise the Virata Lute in front of him before strumming its strings with one hand.

The silver light emanating from the lute trembled as the space above it warped and twisted, then compressed together to oppose the vast mountain of swordlight.

A string of resounding booms rang out as the spatial power summoned by the Virata Lute clashed incessantly against the streaks of swordlight, and the compressed space was being rapidly whittled away, while only the outermost layer of swordlight had been eradicated.

Right as Shi Chuankong was about to be overwhelmed, an earth-shattering boom suddenly rang out in the distance.

Yin Yu's brows furrowed slightly as he turned in that direction, just in time to see Han Li abruptly rush out of the gray statue within Tong Yu's spirit domain, holding an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword in one hand and a green gourd in the other.

Tong Yu was very much taken aback to see this, but he reacted very quickly, lashing out with his fists.

A relentlessly stream of devilish qi was released from his fists, and it was compounding upon itself in layers with each punch that was thrown, forming a layered wall of devilish qi that hurtled directly toward Han Li.

Chapter 783: Experience

In the face of Tong Yu's formidable attack, Han Li didn't retaliate with his sword or his fists. Instead, he merely tossed the green gourd forward, and a green vortex emerged from the mouth of the gourd, then released a beam of dark green light that struck the wall of devilish qi.

The destructive law powers within the beam of green light were released, and the wall of devilish qi was instantly destroyed.

At the same time, Han Li channeled his Reversal True Axis ability, allowing him to reach Tong Yu in the blink of an eye before swinging his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword down upon Tong Yu's head.

Tong Yu was very startled by this turn of events, and his body immediately began to disintegrate into devilish qi again.

Unbeknownst to him, this was exactly what Han Li had been aiming for.

Han Li thrust a palm into the underside of the Profound Heavenly Gourd, and a green vortex instantly re-emerged from its mouth, releasing a burst of tremendous suction force.

Plumes of devilish qi were instantly drawn into the gourd, and by the time Tong Yu realized that he had fallen for a trap, it was already too late.

In the blink of an eye, he was sucked into the space within the gourd, and the dozens of Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords inside immediately swarmed the cloud of devilish qi, forcing it into the gourd's second internal space.

Immediately thereafter, a blood-curdling howl rang out from within the gourd.

Han Li raised the gourd, then tipped it upside-down before gently shaking it, and a pile of mangled remains fell out of the green vortex onto the ground.

Even though Tong Yu possessed a High Zenith Stage nascent soul, there was nowhere for it to escape in the Profound Heavenly Gourd, and it was destroyed by the destructive law powers inside. At this point, all that remained of Tong Yu was a golden storage ring, which was still hovering in the first space within the gourd.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and in response to Tong Yu's sudden demise, Yin Yu was much more surprised than angry.

All of a sudden, he forced his longsword with tremendous power, and the spatial barrier conjured up by the Virata Lute was instantly destroyed by the mountain of sword qi.

Shi Chuankong felt a burst of fearsome power descend upon him, and he plummeted out of the sky before crashing into a mountain down below.

A resounding boom rang out as a large section of the mountain was shattered, causing a massive avalanche.

Shi Chuankong flew out of the dust and debris, stroking a white mark that had been sliced into the Virata Lute with a pained expression, yet before he had a chance to do anything else, he was caught by a giant white serpentine tail.

In the wake of Tong Yu's demise, Yin Yu displayed no intention to avenge him, choosing to prioritize Shi Chuankong's capture instead.

However, as soon as he turned to depart, he immediately felt the entire world slow down around him, and he looked around to discover that he had been caught within Han Li's time spirit domain.

"Isn't it a little rude of you to be leaving without a word like this?" Han Li asked in an indifferent voice as he appeared in Yin Yu's path, and the Essence Fire Raven was hovering behind him.

"Tong Yu should've never been defeated by you. You only won because he underestimated you," Yin Yu said in an expressionless manner.

"You're right, but aren't you making the same mistake?" Han Li chuckled.

Yin Yu's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and right at this moment, a series of pillars of golden and silver light rose up from the mountains down below, then converged high up in the sky to form an enormous array.

Immediately thereafter, Yin Yu was struck by a sense of drowsiness, and the flow of air in the space ahead of him slowed down even further. At the same time, he felt as if he had been caught within countless shackles, making him feel extremely heavy and sluggish.

His tail reflexively loosened slightly in response to these alarming changes, and Shi Chuankong was able to struggle free from his bindings.

"Are you alright?" Han Li asked as he approached Shi Chuankong while holding a glowing jade pendant.

Shi Chuankong was also holding a glowing jade pendant, and he threw up a mouthful of blood, then hurriedly replied, "I'm fine. Let's put an end to this as soon as possible while he's still trapped in the array."

Han Li wasted no time upon hearing this, bringing his palms together with the jade pendant in between them before injecting his time law powers into it. Shi Chuankong also did the same, except he was injecting spatial law powers into his pendant.

Under their combined efforts, the surrounding array began to glow brighter and brighter, and the time and spatial law power fluctuations emanating from it also became more and more formidable.

Yin Yu could feel the flow of time around him slowing down further and further, while the tremendous compression force acting upon him became more and more unbearable. However, his sluggish spiritual sense made it impossible for him to react, reducing him to a helpless sitting duck.

A string of dull thumps rang out as the space around him began to collapse, and the space within the array was caving in toward the center, further exacerbating his woes.

It was only going to take a few more minutes for the space within the array to completely collapse, at which point Yin Yu's body and nascent soul would be crushed. Furthermore, thanks to the time-slowing effect of Han Li's time law powers, this was going to be an extremely long and drawn-out process, subjecting Yin Yu to a slow and torturous death.

However, such a powerful array couldn't be unleashed without a price. Han Li and Shi Chuankong had each summoned a treasure that contained their respective law powers, and both of those treasures were going to be destroyed in this process.

On top of that, the more formidable the target trapped within the array was, the longer the array would take to operate, thereby expending more of Han Li and Shi Chuankong's law powers.

This was why they hadn't unleashed the array from the very beginning, instead choosing only to activate it after one of the two assailants had been slain. Only then could they ensure that they would have sufficient law powers to support the array until the target was eradicated.

At the moment, Han Li was still looking fairly comfortable, but Shi Chuankong was already sweating profusely.

He had exerted himself quite severely in his earlier battle against Yin Yu, thereby expending far more spatial law powers than anticipated, and he was struggling to keep up.

Inside the array, the space continued to compress, and at this point, Yin Yu's tail had already been flattened, while some of his ribs had also been snapped and caved in.

At this rate, it wouldn't be long before all of his bones were snapped, and at that point, he would be truly powerless to resist.

However, right at his moment, Shi Chuankong's spatial law power reserves were completely exhausted, and the silver light emanating from the jade pendant in his hand instantly faded.

The entire array also ceased operating, and at the exact same moment, the two treasures acting as the cores of the array on the two mountains below exploded.

The entire array began to fall apart, and an alarmed look appeared on Han Li's face as he immediately stowed his jade pendant away without any hesitation before sweeping a sleeve through the air, sending eighteen Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords hurtling directly toward Yin Yu.

However, Yin Yu had already been freed from the array at this point, and a giant waterfall of sword qi cascaded down from the heavens at his behest, scattering all of the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords before also razing a tall mountain down below to the ground.

By the time Han Li summoned his flying sword back to his side, the waterfall of sword qi had already faded, while Yin Yu was nowhere to be seen.

Han Li summoned his Essence Fire Raven back to his side, then turned to Shi Chuankong to discover that the front of his robe was drenched in blood, while his aura was very unstable, clearly indicating that he had suffered very severe injuries.

With a sweep of his sleeve, he released a burst of azure light to support Shi Chuankong, who was looking rather unsteady on his feet, and a wry smile appeared on Shi Chuankong's face as he said, "It's going to take some time before I recover from these injuries. What a pity that we let one get away..."

"We're already very fortunate to have survived this ordeal at all," Han Li said.

"You are truly a man of many talents, Brother Li. If we had followed my plan and focused solely on fleeing, perhaps we wouldn't have been caught so early, but at the very most, we would've still been intercepted after just a few more days, and we would've been in a far less advantageous situation," Shi Chuankong said.

"I've been hunted many times in the past, and with experience comes insight. Sometimes, it's better to set up a surprise ambush rather than fleeing with no concrete plan. Time is of the essence, so let's get out of here. Next time, it'll most likely be the Golden Rhinoceros King coming after us in person," Han Li said.

Shi Chuankong nodded in response, while Han Li summoned his green jade flying carriage, and both of them flew onboard.

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to Han Li, and he swept a sleeve through the air to release a few puppets, then adhered several talismans onto each of them.

"Brother Shi, pick a few of these puppets and leave your aura on them," Han Li instructed.

Shi Chuankong immediately realized what Han Li was doing, and he chuckled, "It seems like experience really does pay off in situations like these. Having said that, I don't think this is going to be a very effective ruse."

"Like you said, it's just a ruse. If it works, then that's great, but if not, it's not like we lose anything," Han Li replied with a smile.

With that, the two of them left their auras on the puppets, following which the puppets darted away in different directions at their behest.

After that, the green jade flyng carriage flew away into the distance as a streak of green light.

Chapter 784: On the Run

Several days later, in the Golden Rhinoceros King's cave abode.

The floor of the palace was littered with smashed chalices and ornaments, while all of the guards and maidservants were kneeling on the ground, trembling with fear.

Yin Yu's head was lowered, making it impossible to see his expression, and it seemed that he was carrying some severe injuries.

After venting his fury, the Golden Rhinoceros King sat down onto his golden chair, and his eyes were slightly narrowed as he asked, "So you're saying that Tong Yu was killed by the early-High Zenith Stage human cultivator accompanying Shi Chuankong?"

"My king, that man has mastered the laws of time, and in conjunction with Shi Chuankong's spatial law powers..."

"Are you trying to make excuses for yourself?" the Golden Rhinoceros King interjected in a cold voice.

"Not at all, my king," Yin Yu hurriedly replied in a fearful voice.

"Forget it, it was Tong Yu's fault for underestimating the targets. If the two of you had worked together to begin with, the outcome could've been different," the Golden Rhinoceros King sighed.

He swept a sleeve through the air as he spoke, releasing a purple plate, which released a burst of radiant purple light to form a purple array.

A purple-robed man appeared within the array, and it was none other than Shi Zhanfeng.

"Judging from your expression, it doesn't seem like things have gone well, Fellow Daoist Golden Rhinoceros," Shi Zhanfeng said as he raised an eyebrow.

"Is this how you do business, Your Highness? Why did you not warn me about that High Zenith Stage human cultivator accompanying Shi Chuankong? Two of my most prized subordinates have fallen to that man!" the Golden Rhinoceros King accused in a cold voice.

Shi Zhanfeng faltered slightly upon hearing this, and a surprised look appeared in his eyes as he replied, "It was never my intention to withhold such information from you, Fellow Daoist Golden Rhinoceros. I did inform you that my brother was being accompanied by an early-High Zenith Stage human cultivator, but I had no idea what he was capable of. Surely a mere High Zenith cultivator isn't too much for you to handle."

"If he was just an ordinary early-High Zenith cultivator, then he would already be dead by now, but he's mastered the laws of time, and that, combined with your brother's spatial law powers, make them far more difficult to deal with," the Golden Rhinoceros King harrumphed coldly.

"Is that so? Are they still within your territory right now?" Shi Zhanfeng asked.

"Why do you ask that? If they're out of my territory, are you going to turn and strike a deal with that black weasel? In that case, is our deal still in effect? Two of my most prized disciples have already perished for this cause. If you're not going to honor our deal, then I'm afraid that I'll have to visit you in Night Sun City for a chat," the Golden Rhinoceros King said in a cold voice.

"Don't be in such a hurry to threaten me, Fellow Daoist Golden Rhinoceros. If they're still on your territory, then feel free to kill them, and I'll double the compensation that I promised you," Shi Zhanfeng said.

"In addition to that, I want you to help me suppress the black weasel's forces for the foreseeable future. If you can promise me that, I'll go after them in person and ensure that they're wiped out of existence," the Golden Rhinoceros King countered.

"Deal," Shi Zhanfeng immediately agreed.

The Golden Rhinoceros King swept a sleeve through the air to dispel the array, then instructed, "Yin Yu, go and prepare the carriage. I'll be hunting for our targets myself."

……

Half a month later, a green jade flying carriage was flying through the air over a mountain in the Ten Hazards Mountain Range.

Han Li and Shi Chuankong were standing on the carriage, looking around with slightly tense expressions.

"Brother Li, you've already been piloting this carriage for over half a month, how about I take your place for a bit so you can have a rest?" Shi Chuankong proposed.

"There's no need for that, this is not very taxing for me at all. You're still yet to fully recover from your injuries, so it would be best for us to leave this place as soon as possible," Han Li replied.

"There's no need to be too wary, Brother Li. We've already changed directions several times in the past half a month, and we've also suppressed our auras this entire time. Additionally, we haven't even dared to release our spiritual sense, so there's no way they'll be able to find us. Besides, it won't be long until we get out of the Golden Rhinoceros King's territory, and once that happens..."

All of a sudden, Shi Chuankong's voice trailed off here, and a wry smile appeared on Han Li's face as he sighed, "You just had to speak it into existence, didn't you?"

A giant golden carriage had appeared tens of thousands of kilometers behind them. It was an extremely ornate three-story carriage that was riddled with shimmering golden gemstones that were glowing radiantly.

The carriage was drawn by ten golden winged horses clad in suits of golden armor, and it was rapidly gaining on Han Li's flying carriage.

Around the carriage were hundreds of half-human, half beast beings that were also clad in suits of golden armor, and a grim look appeared on Shi Chankong's face as he mused, "The Golden Rhinoceros King really has come after us in person."

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he immediately made a hand seal, upon which his immortal spiritual power surged into the green jade flying carriage in a frenzy, causing it to accelerate dramatically.

The Golden Rhinoceros King was standing behind the railing on the third floor of the carriage, and he gave a cold harrumph upon seeing this.

He then abruptly swept a sleeve through the air, and the nine golden dragons embroidered onto his robe began to glow radiantly.

Immediately thereafter, the nine golden dragons flew out of his robe before making their way into his sleeve, and the sleeve instantly swelled to hundreds of times its original size, aiming to devour the space up ahead like a gargantuan mouth.

The nine golden dragons within the sleeve were forging ahead as quickly as they could, and it took them less than twenty seconds to cover the distance of tens of thousand of kilometers.

All of a sudden, Han Li and Shi Chuankong felt a shadow descend upon them, followed by a burst of tremendous pressure, and the green jade flying carriage immediately began to sway in an unsteady fashion.

Immediately thereafter, a gold vortex appeared within the Golden Rhinoceros King's sleeve, releasing bursts of tremendous suction force that caused the flying carriage to slow down significantly.

Shi Chuankong's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, while Han Li yelled in an urgent voice, "Grab onto my shoulder, Brother Shi!"

In the next instant, a layer of golden light erupted out of his body, forming a golden spirit domain that encompassed the entire surrounding area in a radius of several hundred kilometers.

Enshrouded within the time spirit domain, the giant sleeve instantly slowed down, but in the next instant, the Golden Rhinoceros King let loose a loud roar, upon which a burst of formidable suction force erupted out of the golden vortex within the sleeve.

The time spirit domain rippled violently in the face of this burst of power, while the golden sleeve continued to descend upon Han Li and Shi Chuankong at its original speed.

In this dire situation, Han Li grabbed tightly onto the flying carriage while channeling his Reversal True Axis ability, and in the blink of an eye, the carriage had traveled to thousands of kilometers away.

All the Golden Rhinoceros King saw was a blur flash before his eyes, following which he discovered that his sleeve had fallen upon nothing but empty air.

A bewildered look appeared on Shi Chuankong's face seeing this, and he immediately combined his immortal spiritual power with Han Li's, helping Han Li to accelerate the flying carriage even further.

"After them!" the Golden Rhinoceros King roared, and he conjured up a giant whip of golden light before lashing out at the rear ends of the ten winged horses up ahead.

The rear ends of the ten horses were struck in unison, and the golden armor plates were instantly shattered, while deep gashes were inflicted onto their bodies.

However, the ten horses didn't even dare to utter a single sound as they flapped their wings with all their might, pursuing the green jade flying carriage as quickly as they could.

Up ahead, Han Li didn't dare to let his guard down in the slightest, and he continued to channel his Reversal True Axis ability.

So incredible was his speed that the gap between the two flying carriages was gradually beginning to widen.

Shi Chuankong was ecstatic to see this, but he then caught a glimpse of Han Li's pale complexion, and he realized that maintaining such an incredible speed while carrying a flying carriage along had to have been extremely taxing on him.

Sure enough, Han Li was only able to keep this up for a short while longer before the surrounding time spirit domain dissipated, but thankfully, at this point, the terrain up ahead was already beginning to change.

The vegetation in the forest was gradually becoming sparser, while the terrain was also becoming flatter, transitioning from tall mountains to short hills.

"We're about to reach the Black Weasel King's territory, Brother Li. He and the Golden Rhinoceros King are sworn enemies, so there's no way he'll let the Golden Rhinoceros King into his territory, which means we'll be safe as soon as we get there," Shi Chuankong yelled in an elated voice.

"Don't let your guard down. We're dealing with a Great Encompassment cultivator here," Han Li said as he continued to fly onward as quickly as he could.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a burst of peculiar energy fluctuations suddenly emerged behind them, following which a spirit domain abruptly stretched over a distance of tens of thousands of kilometers to encompass them within it.

Immediately thereafter, the giant golden carriage in the distance suddenly plummeted out of the sky along with the ten winged horses as the Golden Rhinoceros King launched himself forward at an incredible speed.

Inside his own spirit domain, the Golden Rhinoceros King was able to cover a distance of tens of thousands of kilometers with just a single step, and before Han Li and Shi Chuankong had a chance to do anything, a giant golden foot was already stomping down upon them.

A sense of powerlessness welled up in Han Li's heart in the face of the mountainous spiritual pressure crashing down from above, and he discovered that he wasn't even able to channel his Reversal True Axis ability anymore.

The Golden Rhinoceros King's fearsome spiritual pressure instantly filled the entire surrounding space, and it was too late to do anything.